[{"key": 1, "position": "Cloud Security Engineer", "company": "Frame.io", "date": "30 Sep 2021", "question": "1- Describe the most innovative project I lead 2- How would my team members describe me 3- AWS Cloud Security questions", "answer": []}, {"key": 2, "position": "Security Engineer", "company": "Twitch", "date": "29 Sep 2021", "question": "cannot discuss due to NDA", "answer": []}, {"key": 3, "position": "Software Engineer - Security", "company": "Salesforce", "date": "28 Sep 2021", "question": "A junior engineer asked me a few cultural fit questions and then dived into system design for 40 min. He asked me to design Doordash. + Uber backend, Had a good conversation. But i felt the interviewer did not have much experience. He knew the basic stuff of NoSQL vs RDS, Caching, LB etc. Overall the tech screen was good.", "answer": []}, {"key": 4, "position": "Security Engineer", "company": "CSC", "date": "20 Sep 2021", "question": "How would I empty an airplane filled with jelly beans.", "answer": []}, {"key": 5, "position": "Security Engineer", "company": "BayCare Health System", "date": "17 Sep 2021", "question": "Where do you see yourself in 5 years?", "answer": []}, {"key": 6, "position": "Information Security Engineer", "company": "GeniusRx", "date": "9 Sep 2021", "question": "The 2 ladies in HR kept talking about the company history and \"personalities\" but had no questions. The only question was \"do you have any question for me\" to which I asked a couple of questions and both ladies were completely clueless.", "answer": ["IT showed up to the interview with their beds in the background (zoom call) . Sheets unmade and dirty clothes on the floor. Seemed like a bunch of unprofessional and lazy individuals out to accomplish nothing. I dont think this company is going places."]}, {"key": 7, "position": "Information Security Engineer", "company": "Safelite AutoGlass", "date": "8 Sep 2021", "question": "Mostly typical interview question for a position like this.", "answer": ["I thin I answered them well."]}, {"key": 8, "position": "Network Security Engineer", "company": "Infosys", "date": "7 Sep 2021", "question": "Technology related questions and domain related questions", "answer": []}, {"key": 9, "position": "Vehicle Security Engineer", "company": "Nuro", "date": "28 Aug 2021", "question": "What do you hope to gain out of this position?", "answer": []}, {"key": 10, "position": "Information Security Engineer", "company": "Citizens", "date": "27 Aug 2021", "question": "Take me through your career from the start to present day and how you got to where you are today.", "answer": []}, {"key": 11, "position": "Security Engineer", "company": "Check Point Software Technologies", "date": "25 Aug 2021", "question": "They were very interested in my cloud background given the focus on their cloud family of products, CloudGuard.", "answer": []}, {"key": 12, "position": "Cyber Security Engineer", "company": "AT&T", "date": "24 Aug 2021", "question": "What is your experience in configuring log collection?", "answer": []}, {"key": 13, "position": "Applications Security Engineer", "company": "Allstate", "date": "19 Aug 2021", "question": "Describe the difference in Hashing and Cryptography.", "answer": []}, {"key": 14, "position": "Entry Level Cyber Security Engineer", "company": "General Atomics", "date": "4 Aug 2021", "question": "Cookie cutter interview. Tell me about yourself.", "answer": []}, {"key": 15, "position": "Security Engineer", "company": "Apple", "date": "4 Aug 2021", "question": "What is SQL injection? How do you mitigate it?", "answer": []}, {"key": 16, "position": "Cyber Security Engineer", "company": "Lindsay Corporation", "date": "4 Aug 2021", "question": "Can you describe what your ideal incident response process would entail?", "answer": []}, {"key": 17, "position": "Concierge Security Engineer", "company": "Arctic Wolf", "date": "30 Jul 2021", "question": "We expect you to \u201cfail\u201d when you\u2019re new. Describe a time when you failed and what you did after.", "answer": []}, {"key": 18, "position": "Concierge Security Engineer", "company": "Arctic Wolf", "date": "30 Jul 2021", "question": "You\u2019re the brand new CISO of a small company and want to secure your endpoints. What is your first step?", "answer": []}, {"key": 19, "position": "Concierge Security Engineer", "company": "Arctic Wolf", "date": "30 Jul 2021", "question": "Describe the difference between an IPS, IDS and Firewall; how would you use them?", "answer": []}, {"key": 20, "position": "Senior Information Security Engineer", "company": "Skedulo", "date": "28 Jul 2021", "question": "Describe your experience with risk assessment and compliance frameworks.", "answer": []}, {"key": 21, "position": "Pre Sales Security Engineer", "company": "Tanium", "date": "27 Jul 2021", "question": "Very basic cybersecurity knowledge and overall depth.", "answer": ["They were standard stuff."]}, {"key": 22, "position": "Security Operations Engineer", "company": "Blend", "date": "23 Jul 2021", "question": "Security, Python, Automation, Detection, Networking.", "answer": []}, {"key": 23, "position": "Application Security Engineer", "company": "Red Ventures", "date": "20 Jul 2021", "question": "How would you automate security scanning? Describe a role that involved that automation?", "answer": ["Provided about 4 different examples how I was currently conducting automation via Burp, zap, qualys and snyk"]}, {"key": 24, "position": "Security Software Engineer", "company": "SpaceX", "date": "20 Jul 2021", "question": "How much do you know about different encryption schemes?", "answer": []}, {"key": 25, "position": "Offensive Security Engineer", "company": "Zoom Video Communications", "date": "8 Jul 2021", "question": "Hands-on knowledge, scenarios, and code reading.", "answer": ["Through experience."]}, {"key": 26, "position": "Cyber Security Engineer", "company": "BlueCross BlueShield of Tennessee", "date": "3 Jul 2021", "question": "I am not allowed to discuss the specific questions, but if you look at the job description it will set you up for success.", "answer": ["Just be yourself :-)"]}, {"key": 27, "position": "Network Security Engineer", "company": "Orange Business Services", "date": "2 Jul 2021", "question": "Basic network basics security basics fortigate", "answer": []}, {"key": 28, "position": "IT Security Engineer", "company": "Acuity Insurance", "date": "28 Jun 2021", "question": "A common one that seemed to come up a few times was regarding how you view security practices.", "answer": ["Answering it will various things like, least privilege, layered approach, etc opened a lot of discussion and gave me a chance to show how much I knew about broad best practices or my stance on things in the field."]}, {"key": 29, "position": "IT Security Engineer", "company": "Socure", "date": "24 Jun 2021", "question": "basic cyber security questions and self introduction.", "answer": []}, {"key": 30, "position": "IT Security Engineer", "company": "Socure", "date": "24 Jun 2021", "question": "basic cyber security questions and self introduction.", "answer": []}, {"key": 31, "position": "Security Operations Engineer", "company": "Workato", "date": "9 Jun 2021", "question": "Work experience related questions", "answer": []}, {"key": 32, "position": "Senior Security Engineer", "company": "GitLab", "date": "4 Jun 2021", "question": "What\u2019s your background and experience with SIEM and SOAR tools?", "answer": []}, {"key": 33, "position": "Application Security Engineer", "company": "Snap", "date": "30 May 2021", "question": "The question were mainly on Cross site request forgery.", "answer": []}, {"key": 34, "position": "Lead Security Engineer", "company": "Collabera", "date": "27 May 2021", "question": "How do you deal with conflict.", "answer": []}, {"key": 35, "position": "Security Engineer", "company": "Plume Design", "date": "26 May 2021", "question": "Questions around my previous work and setting up secure practices for networking team and so on", "answer": []}, {"key": 36, "position": "Product Security Engineer", "company": "Box", "date": "21 May 2021", "question": "Generic, mostly non-technical questions. Lost my train of thought", "answer": []}, {"key": 37, "position": "Cyber Security Engineer", "company": "Forcepoint", "date": "20 May 2021", "question": "What are some of the problems a workstation may not connect to a network?", "answer": ["Multiple of things can affect the workstation from not connecting. Such as if it was on the domain, is the IP address correct, is the NIC setup the right way, or if the firewall is blocking it from connecting."]}, {"key": 38, "position": "Cyber Security Engineer", "company": "Faith Technologies Incorporated", "date": "17 May 2021", "question": "How do you set up the devscops model? What are your recommendations to mature the security posture of the organization? How do you fit into the team?", "answer": []}, {"key": 39, "position": "Security Engineer", "company": "Salesforce", "date": "7 May 2021", "question": "OWASP top 10, Remediation techniques and latest vulnerability trend", "answer": []}, {"key": 40, "position": "Info Security Engineer", "company": "Wells Fargo", "date": "7 May 2021", "question": "Explain data level encryption. What is PKI and certificate management.", "answer": []}, {"key": 41, "position": "Senior Security Site Reliability Engineer", "company": "Arkose Labs", "date": "4 May 2021", "question": "What's important to lead the team?", "answer": ["To be able to relate to the engineers at a level that makes feel safe and secure."]}, {"key": 42, "position": "Security Engineer", "company": "Synopsys", "date": "1 May 2021", "question": "questions were related to networking.", "answer": []}, {"key": 43, "position": "Network Security Engineer", "company": "Rackspace Technology", "date": "29 Apr 2021", "question": "where u wanna see yourself in next 3-5 years", "answer": []}, {"key": 44, "position": "Product Security Engineer", "company": "Fortress Information Security", "date": "28 Apr 2021", "question": "What are the differences and why would you use one set of analysis tools over the other.", "answer": []}, {"key": 45, "position": "Security Engineer", "company": "Motley Fool", "date": "26 Apr 2021", "question": "Which specific security systems did you personally implement? Which specific security systems did you personally manage? What challenges have you encountered in your prior security work and how did you overcome them?", "answer": []}, {"key": 46, "position": "Cyber Security Engineer", "company": "DataRemote", "date": "26 Apr 2021", "question": "technical and personal, nothing out of the ordinary", "answer": []}, {"key": 47, "position": "Security Solutions Engineer (Professional Services)", "company": "Threat Stack", "date": "20 Apr 2021", "question": "Some very basic networking questions (standard ports for certain activities) as well as some basic command line commands (Windows/Linux) for the screening call.", "answer": []}, {"key": 48, "position": "Security Engineer Intern", "company": "Abarca", "date": "19 Apr 2021", "question": "What is a wrong impression people have gotten from you and how have you proved them wrong?", "answer": []}, {"key": 49, "position": "Security Engineer", "company": "ShorePoint", "date": "12 Apr 2021", "question": "Scenario-based questions for penetration testing/red teaming", "answer": ["With a scenario-based answer borne from years of experience in this field"]}, {"key": 50, "position": "Security Engineer", "company": "ShorePoint", "date": "12 Apr 2021", "question": "Scenario-based questions for penetration testing/red teaming", "answer": ["With a scenario-based answer borne from years of experience in this field"]}, {"key": 51, "position": "Security Engineer", "company": "Lincoln Financial Group", "date": "10 Apr 2021", "question": "Essentially was asked to detail up my previous positions", "answer": []}, {"key": 52, "position": "Security Engineer", "company": "Acumen Security", "date": "8 Apr 2021", "question": "What my home setup was to keep up with penetration testing.", "answer": []}, {"key": 53, "position": "Security Engineer", "company": "PrudentRx", "date": "7 Apr 2021", "question": "What technologies I have worked on in the past", "answer": []}, {"key": 54, "position": "Security Engineer", "company": "Amazon", "date": "6 Apr 2021", "question": "What challenges did you face in previous jobs and how did you overcome them?", "answer": []}, {"key": 55, "position": "Senior Cloud Network Security Engineer", "company": "Netskope", "date": "30 Mar 2021", "question": "Networking basics Networking troubleshooting Network Design Network Security fundamentals Network Security scenarios Technical deep dive into NG firewalls, Proxies, Load Balancers & VPNs", "answer": []}, {"key": 56, "position": "Cloud Security Engineer", "company": "Verkada", "date": "29 Mar 2021", "question": "What is a route reflector for?", "answer": []}, {"key": 57, "position": "IT system security engineer", "company": "SAP NS2", "date": "24 Mar 2021", "question": "It was more of a conversational interview", "answer": ["Tell me about your self"]}, {"key": 58, "position": "Cyber Security Engineer", "company": "Penn State", "date": "19 Mar 2021", "question": "Owasp top 10, csa, firewalls", "answer": ["Correxrly"]}, {"key": 59, "position": "Security Engineer", "company": "Milhouse Engineering & Construction", "date": "19 Mar 2021", "question": "What tools do you recommend for x?", "answer": []}, {"key": 60, "position": "Security Engineer", "company": "Haven Life", "date": "17 Mar 2021", "question": "A) Security tools I worked with in the past", "answer": []}, {"key": 61, "position": "Offensive Security Engineer", "company": "Zoom Video Communications", "date": "16 Mar 2021", "question": "If I know the difference between pentesting and red teaming. Experience with web app testing tools. Scripting/coding experience (in-depth, we actively analyzed code in an exercise) Basic security features and capabilities of PC (I said I was not Mac-heavy in experience) Attack vectors such as XSS, CSRF, injection, RFI, etc. Reporting and findings Communication ability and style (verbally and written)", "answer": []}, {"key": 62, "position": "Offensive Security Engineer", "company": "Zoom Video Communications", "date": "16 Mar 2021", "question": "Why I wanted to work for Zoom specifically.", "answer": ["I did my research to make sure the job I was seeking aligned with my values and professional growth goals. I looked in to the CEO, I read about culture and other employee experiences, I researched work/life balance. I also read about the company's revenue and growth metrics and other business's commentaries on the work they do here. I made sure this was a place I would belong and wanted to belong. I also, since I work in information security, researched their outlook and buy-in to security to see if my job is an important asset to the company or if I'd be fighting an uphill battle everyday to prove the worth fo the work I do. Security is obviously a top priority for everyone as Zoom, so it was a match made in infosec heaven."]}, {"key": 63, "position": "Senior Cyber Security Engineer", "company": "Bluestaq", "date": "15 Mar 2021", "question": "A less serious interview question I was asked was Marvel or DC?", "answer": ["There is no right answer to this question of course but I chose Marvel."]}, {"key": 64, "position": "Information Security Engineer", "company": "Los Alamos National Laboratory", "date": "8 Mar 2021", "question": "What are the steps in RMF.", "answer": ["I outlined the process of RMF lifecycle"]}, {"key": 65, "position": "Principal Cloud Security Engineer", "company": "Palo Alto Networks", "date": "5 Mar 2021", "question": "n/a", "answer": []}, {"key": 66, "position": "Security Engineer", "company": "Zoom Video Communications", "date": "4 Mar 2021", "question": "The questions during the interview were related to the job role and my experience. They mostly dived into remediating vulnerabilities and lot of follow up questions with different business requirements.", "answer": []}, {"key": 67, "position": "Security Engineer I", "company": "Amazon", "date": "26 Feb 2021", "question": "Technical: Hashing vs. Encryption? Symmetric vs Asymmetric? Examples of each? OWASP Top 10 and how to prevent them Hashing scenario problem Authentication scenario problem Session management scenario problem (CSRF) Certificate Authority DNS Recent hacks/news around cybersecurity Behavioral: Why Amazon? Tell me about a goal and the steps you took the accomplish Tell me about a time you went through a personal obstacle or challenge Tell me about your favorite project Tell me about a time when you took on something you weren\u2019t required to do", "answer": []}, {"key": 68, "position": "Security Engineer", "company": "6sense", "date": "26 Feb 2021", "question": "Scenario based questions about OWASP security. Mitigations. AWS environments. improvements on overall security structure. SSDLC process, tools specific questions on implementations. DevsecOps. What happens if you type google in the browser and the possible threats.", "answer": []}, {"key": 69, "position": "Cyber-Security Engineer | Pen Tester", "company": "Praetorian", "date": "25 Feb 2021", "question": "What is the command-line option to set the source port for a nmap scan?", "answer": ["-g or --source-port"]}, {"key": 70, "position": "Security Engineer", "company": "Redfin", "date": "23 Feb 2021", "question": "Coding interview was the focus.", "answer": []}, {"key": 71, "position": "Cyber Security Engineer", "company": "Invictus International Consulting", "date": "22 Feb 2021", "question": "RMF was the main focus / very technical /", "answer": ["I answered extremely well (the internal guy got the job) just be aware of the scenario interview fodder. That appears to be a part of their HR Game"]}, {"key": 72, "position": "Senior Applications Security Engineer", "company": "Zoom Video Communications", "date": "19 Feb 2021", "question": "The most interesting questions were walking them through my process of performing web and mobile application assessments, as well as walking them through exploiting several CVEs I had. Finally there was some C and python code review, looking for standard bugs in C (Largely memory corruption related) and some web specific logic bugs.", "answer": []}, {"key": 73, "position": "Cloud Security Engineer", "company": "Oscar Health", "date": "16 Feb 2021", "question": "Q. Basic Questions that were related to my resume.", "answer": []}, {"key": 74, "position": "Security Engineer", "company": "Amount", "date": "16 Feb 2021", "question": "Q. Mostly questions related to my resume Q. Difference between XSS and CSRF? Q. Why you want to make the move?", "answer": []}, {"key": 75, "position": "Security Engineer", "company": "AppFolio", "date": "16 Feb 2021", "question": "Recruiter Call: Q. Tell me about yourself Q. About the company Q. Your past experience Hiring Manager Round: Q. All questions were related to the tools and technologies that I mentioned on my resume.", "answer": []}, {"key": 76, "position": "Security Engineer", "company": "Datadog", "date": "15 Feb 2021", "question": "Q. security best practises, behavioral questions in third round", "answer": []}, {"key": 77, "position": "Security Software Engineer", "company": "Qualcomm", "date": "11 Feb 2021", "question": "tell me about what your concentration", "answer": []}, {"key": 78, "position": "Staff Security Engineer", "company": "The Home Depot", "date": "6 Feb 2021", "question": "Technical Questions are all product related as their Teams specialize in product placements. Management meeting: Tell me about a hardship you had to overcome with underperforming team members and how did you manage the situation? What was the outcome, and what did you do to help the person?", "answer": []}, {"key": 79, "position": "Senior Security Engineer", "company": "Zoom Video Communications", "date": "5 Feb 2021", "question": "Questions on Splunk, Linux, and Python", "answer": []}, {"key": 80, "position": "Staff Security Engineer", "company": "VMware", "date": "1 Feb 2021", "question": "How key is used to sign the msg?", "answer": ["private key"]}, {"key": 81, "position": "Security Engineer", "company": "Forcepoint", "date": "26 Jan 2021", "question": "Look up default Security questions on the internet and they will be very close. Know basic networking and how to configure firewalls. Know how to work with Qradar, and nessus.", "answer": ["All questions we situational, no way to cram for it. Just get good experience. If you dont have it, you wont get a job here."]}, {"key": 82, "position": "Security Engineer", "company": "Check Point Software Technologies", "date": "25 Jan 2021", "question": "What is your biggest strength?", "answer": ["work ethic"]}, {"key": 83, "position": "IT Systems Security Engineer", "company": "BAE Systems USA", "date": "21 Jan 2021", "question": "What are your strongest skillsets?", "answer": []}, {"key": 84, "position": "Information Security Engineer", "company": "Mastercard", "date": "21 Jan 2021", "question": "Threat Modeling, standard security questions. Some behavioral questions on how you dealt with senior management and communicated risk.", "answer": []}, {"key": 85, "position": "Application Security Engineer", "company": "Verizon Media", "date": "19 Jan 2021", "question": "the engineer clearly wanted me to come to some sort of pre-conceived key distribution system that I was supposed to come up with on a white board given extremely vague requirements.", "answer": []}, {"key": 86, "position": "Security Engineer", "company": "New Relic", "date": "18 Jan 2021", "question": "What is a Server Side Request Forgery attack?", "answer": ["A vulnerability in a web server that exists due to a lack of malicious user input detection, sanitation, and validation checks. SSRF vulnerabilities don't validate the user provided URL endpoints before processing/calling the URL endpoints. This allows a bad-actor to make requests to bogon IP addresses (127.0.0.1, 169.254.0.0/16, fe80::1, etc) which often can force the web server to reveal sensitive data and website administration pages that only run on localhost to a bad-actor on the public internet."]}, {"key": 87, "position": "Security Engineer Or Contractor Only", "company": "Kubota Tractor", "date": "18 Jan 2021", "question": "Industry standard questions that every candidate expect to be asked", "answer": []}, {"key": 88, "position": "Security Engineer Or Contractor Only", "company": "Kubota Tractor", "date": "18 Jan 2021", "question": "Tell me about yourself ?", "answer": ["I told them about my self"]}, {"key": 89, "position": "Cyber Security Engineer", "company": "Vistra Energy", "date": "15 Jan 2021", "question": "From a security standpoint, iPhone or Android?", "answer": ["iPhone for security means because they control hardware, and their app store controls software."]}, {"key": 90, "position": "Senior Security Engineer", "company": "Bright Health", "date": "15 Jan 2021", "question": "What motivates you to be inspired? (This one says it all, they are looking for the right candidates not just one that fills a roll).", "answer": ["I am inspired by the opportunity to make a difference, I am inspired by needs I can meet and by the challenges that I encounter that help me grow along the way."]}, {"key": 91, "position": "Cloud Security Engineer", "company": "Booz Allen Hamilton", "date": "12 Jan 2021", "question": "What my experience with specific technologies were", "answer": []}, {"key": 92, "position": "Security Engineer Intern", "company": "Adobe", "date": "12 Jan 2021", "question": "Why Adobe? Be prepared to answer a variety of security situations.", "answer": []}, {"key": 93, "position": "Security Engineer Intern", "company": "Adobe", "date": "12 Jan 2021", "question": "Why Adobe? Be prepared to answer a variety of security situations.", "answer": []}, {"key": 94, "position": "Information Security Engineer", "company": "Honey", "date": "12 Jan 2021", "question": "Run of the mill security questions.", "answer": []}, {"key": 95, "position": "Information Security Engineer", "company": "Honey", "date": "12 Jan 2021", "question": "Run of the mill security questions.", "answer": []}, {"key": 96, "position": "Cyber Security Engineer", "company": "Trustwave", "date": "11 Jan 2021", "question": "Describe what are egghunters and their use in exploit development. Can you describe the different segments on a debugger? How's your proficiency on IDA? Can you describe how you would find bugs on an x86 binary?", "answer": []}, {"key": 97, "position": "Security Engineer", "company": "Flatiron Health", "date": "11 Jan 2021", "question": "Give me an example of a CTF challenge that you worked on", "answer": []}, {"key": 98, "position": "Security Engineer", "company": "Microsoft", "date": "10 Jan 2021", "question": "Tell me what was the most recent code you wrote?", "answer": []}, {"key": 99, "position": "Information Security Engineer", "company": "Google", "date": "5 Jan 2021", "question": "What is traceroute? Explain it in details.", "answer": []}, {"key": 100, "position": "Software Engineer - Security Response", "company": "Microsoft", "date": "3 Jan 2021", "question": "I was asked about various web application vulnerabilities and how to mitigate them. The questions were asked form the CWE Top 25 and OWASP Top 10.", "answer": []}, {"key": 101, "position": "Cyber Security Engineer", "company": "Cerner", "date": "2 Jan 2021", "question": "No Interview question because I never reached through that process.", "answer": []}, {"key": 102, "position": "Hardware Security Engineer", "company": "NVIDIA", "date": "23 Dec 2020", "question": "give u a case and ask you find security flaw", "answer": []}, {"key": 103, "position": "Senior Security Engineer", "company": "Praetorian", "date": "17 Dec 2020", "question": "Why are you looking to leave your current role?", "answer": []}, {"key": 104, "position": "Security Systems Engineer", "company": "University of Redlands", "date": "17 Dec 2020", "question": "what protocol does DNS use", "answer": ["It use UDP protocol and port 53"]}, {"key": 105, "position": "Security Operations Engineer", "company": "Splunk", "date": "8 Dec 2020", "question": "Questions were related to my background and seemed to be more about getting to know me as a person.", "answer": ["Honestly", "Any specifics?"]}, {"key": 106, "position": "Security Engineer", "company": "Affirm", "date": "7 Dec 2020", "question": "Tell me about yourself/ previous exp.", "answer": ["linkedin", "In these sorts of interviews you really need to drill down and understand what the interviewer is looking for. A good way to simulate a real interview experience is to do a mock with one of the Affirm Security Engineer experts on Prepfully, rated super strongly on TrustPilot... prepfully.com/practice-interviews"]}, {"key": 107, "position": "Security Engineer", "company": "Hopin", "date": "1 Dec 2020", "question": "General security questions about OWASP, security automation, pentesting.", "answer": []}, {"key": 108, "position": "Network Security Engineer", "company": "Facebook", "date": "30 Nov 2020", "question": "Networking and security questions Coding algorithm question", "answer": []}, {"key": 109, "position": "Security Developer", "company": "General Motors (GM)", "date": "23 Nov 2020", "question": "Tell about two repetitive task that you have at your work? what is week cipher? Tell about the security mechanism that you have used for webservice and API ? I have application that is running on the server, and you see some attack in you application from specific system you need configure security without disturb this server, how did you do that?", "answer": []}, {"key": 110, "position": "Senior Cyber Security Engineer", "company": "3M", "date": "18 Nov 2020", "question": "My accomplishments from my previous positions and how I handled difficult managers.", "answer": []}, {"key": 111, "position": "Security Engineer", "company": "iCIMS", "date": "16 Nov 2020", "question": "Tell me about a time or experience you had with X product and what you used to solve a problem with the solution?", "answer": []}, {"key": 112, "position": "Security Engineer", "company": "iCIMS", "date": "16 Nov 2020", "question": "How do you stay up to date with the latest in Security Trends?", "answer": []}, {"key": 113, "position": "Security Operations Engineer", "company": "Updox", "date": "16 Nov 2020", "question": "What do you do if your upper management doesn't support security objectives?", "answer": ["I answered that you present the risks by outlining security incident likelihoods and impacts. If qualitative analysis does not sway upper management, quantitative methods can be used to better illustrate the potential for negative financial impact to the business. I also added that in the end, it is upper managements role (CISO, et al) to accept security risk...which they seemed to disagree with."]}, {"key": 114, "position": "Security Operations Engineer", "company": "Updox", "date": "16 Nov 2020", "question": "What is your preferred data classification framework?", "answer": ["Gave a non-committal answer explaining that is very organization specific. Told them that I believe data classification should not be overly complicated if they want buy-in from all parts of the business - especially for SMBs that are growing."]}, {"key": 115, "position": "Security Engineer", "company": "Pampered Chef", "date": "12 Nov 2020", "question": "Basic HR questions for initial phone screen.", "answer": []}, {"key": 116, "position": "Security Engineer", "company": "Pampered Chef", "date": "12 Nov 2020", "question": "Basic HR questions for initial phone screen.", "answer": []}, {"key": 117, "position": "Security Engineer", "company": "Couchbase", "date": "8 Nov 2020", "question": "Behavioral and Code reviews are the main questions", "answer": []}, {"key": 118, "position": "Security Engineer", "company": "Moffitt Cancer Center", "date": "6 Nov 2020", "question": "They will mention things on your resume to make sure you know what you're talking about.", "answer": ["I had a couple things on there that I was in the process of learning, so I had them on my resume (when I really shouldn't have). My answer wasn't nearly as solid as I would have liked. make sure you can back up every skill on your resume well."]}, {"key": 119, "position": "Security Engineer", "company": "Moffitt Cancer Center", "date": "6 Nov 2020", "question": "They will mention things on your resume to make sure you know what you're talking about.", "answer": ["I had a couple things on there that I was in the process of learning, so I had them on my resume (when I really shouldn't have). My answer wasn't nearly as solid as I would have liked. make sure you can back up every skill on your resume well."]}, {"key": 120, "position": "Security Engineer", "company": "ReliaQuest", "date": "2 Nov 2020", "question": "What are some port numbers and their functions", "answer": []}, {"key": 121, "position": "Security Engineer", "company": "Niantic", "date": "29 Oct 2020", "question": "Various questions focused on cloud security and client security.", "answer": ["Through questions like this, interviewers are mostly trying to test your skillset (and its relevance to the role) as robustly as possible, so be prepared for multiple offshoots and followups. It could be a useful exercise to do mocks with friends or colleagues in Niantic to get a real sense of what the interview is actually like. Alternatively Prepfully has a ton of Niantic Security Engineer experts who provide mock interviews for a pretty reasonable amount. prepfully.com/practice-interviews"]}, {"key": 122, "position": "Security Engineer", "company": "ReliaQuest", "date": "28 Oct 2020", "question": "Linux heavy on the technical interview, foundational knowledge really. Trying to gauge experience.", "answer": []}, {"key": 123, "position": "Security Engineer", "company": "Procore Technologies", "date": "25 Oct 2020", "question": "General talk about experience and interest in switching. Nothing outstanding and some focus on my current company focus", "answer": []}, {"key": 124, "position": "Security Assurance Engineer", "company": "FactSet", "date": "14 Oct 2020", "question": "There was a whiteboard question asking me to implement a block cipher at a high level.", "answer": []}, {"key": 125, "position": "Principal Security Engineer", "company": "Zipwhip", "date": "12 Oct 2020", "question": "Conducting Threat Modeling on a given scenario", "answer": []}, {"key": 126, "position": "Principal Security Engineer", "company": "Zipwhip", "date": "12 Oct 2020", "question": "How to secure multiple AWS accounts", "answer": []}, {"key": 127, "position": "Software Engineer- Security", "company": "Salesforce", "date": "9 Oct 2020", "question": "1 interview w/recruiter, 1 technical interview w/engineer, 1 technical interview w/would-be manager.", "answer": []}, {"key": 128, "position": "Application Security Engineer", "company": "Facebook", "date": "7 Oct 2020", "question": "Take an integer array of unknown size and return true if any 3 numbers add up to 0", "answer": ["Didn't really answer it. Kind of lost the desire to move forward after the opening question."]}, {"key": 129, "position": "Systems Software Security Engineer", "company": "NVIDIA", "date": "6 Oct 2020", "question": "Find security bugs in given code", "answer": []}, {"key": 130, "position": "Systems Software Security Engineer", "company": "NVIDIA", "date": "6 Oct 2020", "question": "With a given number, find the least number of operations needed to make the number. Only 3 types of operation are allowed: +1, -1, *2. Try to optimize your code", "answer": []}, {"key": 131, "position": "Systems Software Security Engineer", "company": "NVIDIA", "date": "6 Oct 2020", "question": "Technical whiteboard discussion on topics found during reviewing the resume", "answer": []}, {"key": 132, "position": "Systems Software Security Engineer", "company": "NVIDIA", "date": "6 Oct 2020", "question": "Question related queue using array in C", "answer": []}, {"key": 133, "position": "Information Security Engineer", "company": "Indeed", "date": "2 Oct 2020", "question": "How would you communicate and collaborate with other individuals?", "answer": []}, {"key": 134, "position": "Information Security Engineer", "company": "Indeed", "date": "2 Oct 2020", "question": "Examine this data flow diagram and these API structures and describe the security controls and questions you would ask someone", "answer": []}, {"key": 135, "position": "Security Engineer Intern", "company": "Expedia Group", "date": "19 Sep 2020", "question": "Describe a time facing difficulties , If ressources was available what project do you want ro build, What can prevent a web app to be available if the server is running perfectly Well known protocol", "answer": []}, {"key": 136, "position": "Information Security Engineer", "company": "Snap", "date": "3 Sep 2020", "question": "Do you have any questions for me - Right off the cuff", "answer": ["It's essential to demonstrate that you can really go deep... there are plenty of followup questions and (sometimes tangential) angles to explore. There's a lot of Information Security Engineer experts who've worked at Snap, who provide this sort of practice through mock interviews. There's a whole list of them curated on Prepfully. prepfully.com/practice-interviews"]}, {"key": 137, "position": "Information Security Engineer", "company": "Snap", "date": "3 Sep 2020", "question": "Explain ssl or ssh and break it down in as much detail as you can.", "answer": ["In these sorts of interviews you really need to drill down and understand what the interviewer is looking for. A good way to simulate a real interview experience is to do a mock with one of the Snap Information Security Engineer experts on Prepfully, rated super strongly on TrustPilot... prepfully.com/practice-interviews"]}, {"key": 138, "position": "Senior Principal Security Engineer", "company": "iTCO Solutions", "date": "21 Aug 2020", "question": "Can you talk on the phone?", "answer": []}, {"key": 139, "position": "Security Engineer Position", "company": "GoDaddy", "date": "7 Aug 2020", "question": "What port does ping use", "answer": ["None"]}, {"key": 140, "position": "Security Engineer Position", "company": "GoDaddy", "date": "7 Aug 2020", "question": "Describe your perfect job and what is a good fit?", "answer": ["Done"]}, {"key": 141, "position": "Security Engineer", "company": "GoDaddy", "date": "2 Aug 2020", "question": "what is role based access control?", "answer": []}, {"key": 142, "position": "Security Engineer", "company": "Sysmex America", "date": "24 Jul 2020", "question": "Questions about work history. Description of job/role. Questions about personality and value you can bring.", "answer": []}, {"key": 143, "position": "Cyber Security Engineer", "company": "Novanta", "date": "11 Jul 2020", "question": "Why I wanted to take on this job?", "answer": ["Because of their global presence, it give an opportunity to enhance the skill"]}, {"key": 144, "position": "Security Engineer", "company": "DigitalOcean", "date": "3 Jul 2020", "question": "System design -- know internal systems well", "answer": ["There's a lot of elements to typically cover in these questions, clarifications, scoping, making sure you're answering the actual question the interviewer is looking for you to answer, etc. Could be worth doing a mock interview with one of the Prepfully DigitalOcean Security Engineer experts... they've worked in the role so they clearly know how to get through the interview. prepfully.com/practice-interviews"]}, {"key": 145, "position": "Information Security Engineer", "company": "Sure", "date": "1 Jul 2020", "question": "Not going to spoil it. ;-)", "answer": []}, {"key": 146, "position": "Security Engineer", "company": "Palo Alto Networks", "date": "20 Jun 2020", "question": "cannot share due to nda", "answer": []}, {"key": 147, "position": "Application Security Engineer", "company": "Facebook", "date": "13 Jun 2020", "question": "1. Reflected XSS, DOM based XSS 2. How do you prevent CSRF 3. Question about tools that you developed", "answer": ["optional"]}, {"key": 148, "position": "Security Engineer", "company": "Amazon", "date": "11 Jun 2020", "question": "Basic questions: what is encryption, how does authentication work, describe Unix fundamentals, how does Hashing work, describe how a for loop works.", "answer": ["Answered all their questions with precise detail apparently that wasn\u2019t enough for them."]}, {"key": 149, "position": "Java Security Developer", "company": "SAP Fieldglass", "date": "2 Jun 2020", "question": "1.overloading vs overriding. 2. Private constructor. 3.REST APIs -Diff GET vs POST 4.Normalization. 5.What are the indexes. 6.Will views be updated if we update table.", "answer": []}, {"key": 150, "position": "IT Security Engineer", "company": "NIKE", "date": "26 May 2020", "question": "What is your favorite Nike Shoe", "answer": ["The ones that I am wearing. Nike Air Max Axis. Make sure you are sporting the brand and you know why you are wearing it."]}, {"key": 151, "position": "Security Engineer", "company": "Amazon", "date": "25 May 2020", "question": "Security fundamental questions: OWASP top10, crypto algorithms, network protocols, one project in detail from your resume (I explained password cracker) Penetration testing, log monitoring, server security hardening questions (all were scenario-based) previous experience and projects", "answer": []}, {"key": 152, "position": "Senior Product Security Engineer", "company": "Tanium", "date": "6 May 2020", "question": "Basic questions around web application security.", "answer": []}, {"key": 153, "position": "Security Engineer", "company": "Common Securitizton Solutions", "date": "6 May 2020", "question": "Very technical interview", "answer": ["technical answers"]}, {"key": 154, "position": "Applications Security Engineer", "company": "HBO", "date": "4 May 2020", "question": "Detail Experience thus far on previous experiences and detail steps and process of Pen Test", "answer": []}, {"key": 155, "position": "Principal Security Engineer", "company": "Oracle", "date": "3 May 2020", "question": "Tell me a time you overcame a hostile co-worker", "answer": []}, {"key": 156, "position": "Security Engineer", "company": "Workday", "date": "6 Apr 2020", "question": "Some of OWASP top 10 issues", "answer": []}, {"key": 157, "position": "Cyber Security Engineer", "company": "Xandr", "date": "19 Mar 2020", "question": "OWASP Top 10, Basic Linux questions, basic IT non-cyber security questions", "answer": ["It's essential to demonstrate that you can really go deep... there are plenty of followup questions and (sometimes tangential) angles to explore. There's a lot of Cyber Security Engineer experts who've worked at Xandr, who provide this sort of practice through mock interviews. There's a whole list of them curated on Prepfully. prepfully.com/practice-interviews"]}, {"key": 158, "position": "Security Engineer", "company": "Expedia Group", "date": "16 Mar 2020", "question": "Can you explain why we need NIST framework", "answer": ["I explained NIST framework and its use"]}, {"key": 159, "position": "Senior Security Engineer", "company": "OCC", "date": "5 Mar 2020", "question": "There were no questions that were in any way unusual or memorable.", "answer": []}, {"key": 160, "position": "Cyber Security Engineer", "company": "Sandia National Laboratories", "date": "28 Feb 2020", "question": "What does SCOT stand for?", "answer": ["Sandia Cyber Omni Tracker"]}, {"key": 161, "position": "Security Engineer", "company": "Amazon", "date": "18 Feb 2020", "question": "Can two files generate same checksum?", "answer": ["Yes", "Can you elaborate more questions", "Can two files generate the same checksum? Yes, but only if the contents are identical. Even if we change a single word in a Microsoft Word document or a value in an Excel document, the checksum will be different", "Yes, Hash Collisions."]}, {"key": 162, "position": "Product Security Engineer", "company": "Squarespace", "date": "17 Feb 2020", "question": "How does HTTPS work?", "answer": []}, {"key": 163, "position": "Security Engineer", "company": "Tillster", "date": "13 Feb 2020", "question": "At one point a lead dev asked me about my Kubernetes and Dockers experience. I replied \"I don't know much about it, but I am not a developer.\" His response/question was \"Well have you ever used Linux in your life?\"...", "answer": ["I replied \"I don't know much about it, but I am not a developer.\" His response/question was \"Well have you ever used Linux in your life?\""]}, {"key": 164, "position": "Security Operations Engineer", "company": "Blend", "date": "12 Feb 2020", "question": "The questions focused mostly on my current work, as well as my career goals and what I wanted to do next. They were mostly concerned of ensuring that the role was a good fit for us both - a breath of fresh air. I wasn't asked anything which was irrelevant to the role - no coding challenges, no trick questions.", "answer": ["Honesty and transparency. At the end of the day, I really felt like they hired based on genuine fit."]}, {"key": 165, "position": "Cyber Security Engineer", "company": "Darktrace", "date": "11 Feb 2020", "question": "What steps would you take to troubleshoot if you're done setting up the system and when you run a final test you realize it's not connected to the internet?", "answer": ["Check that you're pinging the right IP, check the cables to make sure they are not lose, make sure that the port is configured correctly, ask for help from a coworker, as local IT team for help."]}, {"key": 166, "position": "Cyber Security Engineer", "company": "ENSCO", "date": "5 Feb 2020", "question": "Explain at one given point in time where you were presented a problem and how did you resolve the issue?", "answer": []}, {"key": 167, "position": "Senior Security Engineer", "company": "Onna Technologies", "date": "1 Feb 2020", "question": "In all fairness (because my negative rating could be taken as retaliation), I have to say that the team members who interviewed me were respectful and kind, and their questions were thoughtful (as opposed to the typical and mundane interview questions that don\u2019t reflect a genuine interest in the applicant\u2019s profile and work history).", "answer": []}, {"key": 168, "position": "Security Sales Engineer", "company": "Continental Resources (Massachusetts)", "date": "27 Jan 2020", "question": "General about my background and what the role entailed", "answer": []}, {"key": 169, "position": "Principal Security Engineer", "company": "Empower Retirement", "date": "22 Jan 2020", "question": "What would you do if you found an infected host on your network and how would you stop it's spread? (No details were given on what tools or equipment the customer may have)", "answer": ["I would isolate the host from the network so that it is unable to spread the infection. I would analyze the host to see if I could find the attack vector such as email virus, phishing attack, infected file, etc.). Check the firewalls for any logs that may show the attack vector. - (The manager kept saying I was wrong about this because I didn't specify the specific Cisco AMP threat detection product and simply mentioned firewall logs, but I didn't know that AMP was a part of their network. He kept beating me up on this point and we agreed to disagree)"]}, {"key": 170, "position": "Cloud Security Engineer", "company": "Uber", "date": "16 Jan 2020", "question": "Algorithms and data structures", "answer": ["Although this is a cloud security position, I was asked about algorithms and data structures."]}, {"key": 171, "position": "Applications Security Engineer", "company": "Coveros", "date": "13 Jan 2020", "question": "What experience do you have implementing security into the DevOps process?", "answer": []}, {"key": 172, "position": "Applications Security Engineer", "company": "Coveros", "date": "13 Jan 2020", "question": "Do you have experiencing scripting out the CI/CD process?", "answer": []}, {"key": 173, "position": "Applications Security Engineer", "company": "Coveros", "date": "13 Jan 2020", "question": "Tell me about your experience with DevSecOps ?", "answer": []}, {"key": 174, "position": "Applications Security Engineer", "company": "Coveros", "date": "13 Jan 2020", "question": "What's your experience with DAST/SAST Tools?", "answer": []}, {"key": 175, "position": "Applications Security Engineer", "company": "Coveros", "date": "13 Jan 2020", "question": "What is the OWASP Top 10? What's your experience working with it?", "answer": []}, {"key": 176, "position": "Applications Security Engineer", "company": "Coveros", "date": "13 Jan 2020", "question": "Tell me about your experience securing cloud services?", "answer": []}, {"key": 177, "position": "Applications Security Engineer", "company": "Coveros", "date": "13 Jan 2020", "question": "Do you know what a threat model is? Tell me about it.", "answer": ["Threat modeling is a process which looks at attack vectors and vulnerabilities and helps to prioritize remediation and protection. Where do you put your app security money."]}, {"key": 178, "position": "Cyber Security Engineer", "company": "Epic", "date": "13 Jan 2020", "question": "Would you be okay with relocation?", "answer": ["Yes."]}, {"key": 179, "position": "Infrastructure Security Engineer", "company": "WeWork", "date": "12 Jan 2020", "question": "What are some concerns surrounding IoT motion sensor security?", "answer": []}, {"key": 180, "position": "Cyber Security Engineer", "company": "Sentar", "date": "11 Jan 2020", "question": "Experience, knowledge towards job and prior job experience. RMF experience", "answer": ["Told them my work experience in accordance with requirements of job"]}, {"key": 181, "position": "Cloud Security Engineer", "company": "Deloitte", "date": "3 Jan 2020", "question": "What is the difference between intranet and internet and give an application of the same.", "answer": []}, {"key": 182, "position": "Software Security Engineer", "company": "Viasat", "date": "31 Dec 2019", "question": "What is SYN/ACK and how does it work", "answer": []}, {"key": 183, "position": "Security Engineer", "company": "Cisco Systems", "date": "22 Dec 2019", "question": "Core Security-Based questions. Along with Resume questions", "answer": []}, {"key": 184, "position": "Applications Security Engineer", "company": "Salesforce", "date": "25 Nov 2019", "question": "Among many other things, we talked through the OWASP top ten - more discussing the concepts, less any kind of recitation.", "answer": ["I made sure I was able to tie each one to specific things to do or not to in code and infrastructure, and to tie it to specific things I'd experienced or worked on in my other jobs."]}, {"key": 185, "position": "Information Security Engineer", "company": "Apex Systems", "date": "25 Nov 2019", "question": "It was a thorough review of my resume and general quiz of different security tools.", "answer": []}, {"key": 186, "position": "Information Security Engineer", "company": "J.P. Morgan", "date": "9 Nov 2019", "question": "Common ways of malware infection and persistence, analysis of a compromised system related to them.", "answer": []}, {"key": 187, "position": "Information Security Engineer", "company": "J.P. Morgan", "date": "9 Nov 2019", "question": "NTFS filesystem metadata analysis, journal, and usn logs, deleted files, metadata inconsistency", "answer": []}, {"key": 188, "position": "Information Security Engineer", "company": "J.P. Morgan", "date": "9 Nov 2019", "question": "Windows API hooks, user mode, kernel mode, address tables, splicing, detection.", "answer": []}, {"key": 189, "position": "Information Security Engineer", "company": "J.P. Morgan", "date": "9 Nov 2019", "question": "Network traffic and capture analysis in relation to the compromised system, describe a process, what are you going to look for in the first place, how are you going to identify and deal with the encrypted traffic.", "answer": []}, {"key": 190, "position": "Information Security Engineer", "company": "J.P. Morgan", "date": "9 Nov 2019", "question": "Fileless malware, ways of infection and persistence, detection on the already compromised system.", "answer": []}, {"key": 191, "position": "Information Security Engineer", "company": "J.P. Morgan", "date": "9 Nov 2019", "question": "You got the memory dump of a potentially compromised system, how are you going to approach its analysis.", "answer": []}, {"key": 192, "position": "Information Security Engineer", "company": "J.P. Morgan", "date": "9 Nov 2019", "question": "Suspicious email analysis walk through, headers, content, attachments, static/dynamic analysis, verdict, signature creation.", "answer": []}, {"key": 193, "position": "Senior Security Engineer", "company": "Cruise", "date": "7 Nov 2019", "question": "Given an environment in which multiple identity providers and directories exist, which do you pick as the source of truth? Why?", "answer": ["Lots of discussion about architecture, data flows, and advantages/disadvantages of different approaches."]}, {"key": 194, "position": "Senior Applications Security Engineer", "company": "ICE Mortgage Technology", "date": "6 Nov 2019", "question": "What would your current peers say about your work?", "answer": []}, {"key": 195, "position": "Security Engineer", "company": "100x", "date": "6 Nov 2019", "question": "a crypto, proof of work, let's talk about how wallet addresses are made question", "answer": []}, {"key": 196, "position": "Security Engineer", "company": "100x", "date": "6 Nov 2019", "question": "a programming question (I forget the details)", "answer": []}, {"key": 197, "position": "Security Engineer", "company": "100x", "date": "6 Nov 2019", "question": "low level systems", "answer": []}, {"key": 198, "position": "Lead Security Engineer", "company": "Bolt", "date": "4 Nov 2019", "question": "How would you design a secrets storage service?", "answer": []}, {"key": 199, "position": "Security Engineer", "company": "Tinder", "date": "31 Oct 2019", "question": "Difference in residual and inherent risk, storage of passwords, where do you see yourself in five to ten years, etc.", "answer": ["Varied", "The key in these questions is to cover the fundamentals, and be ready for the back-and-forth with the interviewer. Might be worth doing a mock interview with one of the Tinder or ex-Tinder Security Engineer experts on Prepfully? They give real-world practice and guidance, which is pretty helpful. prepfully.com/practice-interviews"]}, {"key": 200, "position": "Senior Security Engineer", "company": "Comcast", "date": "30 Oct 2019", "question": "Questions were scenario based. Some involved the challenges the team was currently facing. Overall was pleasant and didn't feel like I was being grilled. Felt more of a conversation among equals. I would recommend this team.", "answer": []}, {"key": 201, "position": "IT Security Engineer", "company": "Copart", "date": "23 Oct 2019", "question": "What is your daily routine at work?", "answer": []}, {"key": 202, "position": "IT Security Engineer", "company": "Copart", "date": "23 Oct 2019", "question": "SQL injection and its prevention.", "answer": []}, {"key": 203, "position": "IT Security Engineer", "company": "Copart", "date": "23 Oct 2019", "question": "Few other cyber attacks and their prevention.", "answer": []}, {"key": 204, "position": "Security Engineer", "company": "Jane Street", "date": "20 Oct 2019", "question": "what if i said i didn't want to use 2FA because all my passwords were unique and I was good at identifying phishing attempts.", "answer": ["pride comes before the fall - there was no such thing as a dumb question until someone asked this question."]}, {"key": 205, "position": "Software Security Engineer", "company": "Corelight", "date": "18 Oct 2019", "question": "What happens to data shared by multiple processes which communicates?", "answer": ["It depends if you have underlying mechanisms to manage concurrency and consistency, by default you can get inconsistencies in your data."]}, {"key": 206, "position": "Security Engineer- Detection and Response (Threat Intelligence)", "company": "100x", "date": "16 Oct 2019", "question": "What would my approach be to looking at incident response", "answer": []}, {"key": 207, "position": "Software Developer, IT Engineer, Security Analyst", "company": "COUNTRY Financial", "date": "14 Oct 2019", "question": "How did you deal with conflicts while working in a team?", "answer": ["Listen to what has to say and then make a decision that befites the company the most."]}, {"key": 208, "position": "Information Security Engineer", "company": "Accenture", "date": "13 Oct 2019", "question": "Personality and development questions", "answer": []}, {"key": 209, "position": "Information Security Engineer", "company": "Accenture", "date": "13 Oct 2019", "question": "Professional Development and what you want to do questions", "answer": []}, {"key": 210, "position": "Information Security Engineer", "company": "Accenture", "date": "13 Oct 2019", "question": "Technical questions regarding CIA triad, OSI model, proxy, VPN, NIST/FIPS documentation.", "answer": []}, {"key": 211, "position": "Information Security Engineer", "company": "Northwest Bank", "date": "9 Oct 2019", "question": "How would you begin to secure a network?", "answer": []}, {"key": 212, "position": "Applications Security Engineer", "company": "Workfront", "date": "3 Oct 2019", "question": "What headers are there when viewing HTTP requests?", "answer": ["Host, User-Agent, Encoding, Cookie"]}, {"key": 213, "position": "Security Consulting Engineer(Software Engineer)", "company": "Cisco Systems", "date": "3 Oct 2019", "question": "What are the 3 pillars of object-oriented programming?", "answer": ["Inheritance, Polymorphism and Encapsulation"]}, {"key": 214, "position": "Security Engineer", "company": "Wayfair", "date": "2 Oct 2019", "question": "Talk about XSS? What is WAF and how should it be implemented? Why would you use Metasploit?", "answer": []}, {"key": 215, "position": "Applications Security Engineer", "company": "Patientco", "date": "27 Sep 2019", "question": "General interview questions about software engineering, devops, and security. Talking about solving problems", "answer": ["It was a conversation."]}, {"key": 216, "position": "Security Engineer", "company": "DigitalOcean", "date": "25 Sep 2019", "question": "They use the STAR method. Tell me about a time when ____ ?", "answer": []}, {"key": 217, "position": "Information Security Engineer", "company": "Global Payments", "date": "24 Sep 2019", "question": "what is tcp how does it work", "answer": ["just answer the question"]}, {"key": 218, "position": "Cloud Security Engineer", "company": "Abacus Insights", "date": "20 Sep 2019", "question": "Can you explain a security incident you've handled recently? Start from initial detection all the way through remediation. What steps did you take to prevent this from happening again?", "answer": []}, {"key": 219, "position": "Cloud Security Engineer", "company": "Abacus Insights", "date": "20 Sep 2019", "question": "Can you describe a technical project you worked on recently? This led to many follow-up questions ranging from process, to technical details.", "answer": []}, {"key": 220, "position": "Cloud Security Engineer", "company": "Abacus Insights", "date": "20 Sep 2019", "question": "Describe a scenario in which you brought your security POV to a discussion with devs. What influence did you have? How did you approach it? Why did you pitch X instead of Y? Can you explain the technical details of the discussion?", "answer": []}, {"key": 221, "position": "Cyber Security Engineer", "company": "MITRE", "date": "18 Sep 2019", "question": "What's your Superpower?", "answer": []}, {"key": 222, "position": "Cyber Security Engineer", "company": "Allstate", "date": "18 Sep 2019", "question": "Where would you see yourself in 5 years?", "answer": []}, {"key": 223, "position": "Security Engineer", "company": "Amazon", "date": "17 Sep 2019", "question": "Explain about PKI, OWASP top 10 - SQL, XSS, CSRF, SSRF, Threat modeling of POS system Amazon leadership questions", "answer": ["I had a good background in PKI but i was able to scratch only the surface for OWASP top 10, threat modeling."]}, {"key": 224, "position": "Senior Applications Security Engineer", "company": "Zapier", "date": "14 Sep 2019", "question": "Describe Same Origin Policy.", "answer": []}, {"key": 225, "position": "Senior Network Security Engineer", "company": "PangoMedia", "date": "12 Sep 2019", "question": "A question that came up a few time was: \"What do you like to do for fun?\"", "answer": ["This caught me a bit off guard however I expressed my personal interests and it was interesting."]}, {"key": 226, "position": "Security Engineer - Vulnerability Management", "company": "PIMCO", "date": "12 Sep 2019", "question": "Tell me about your self", "answer": []}, {"key": 227, "position": "Senior Security Engineer", "company": "SES", "date": "11 Sep 2019", "question": "Experience with Vulnerability Management", "answer": []}, {"key": 228, "position": "Network Security Engineer", "company": "State Farm", "date": "5 Sep 2019", "question": "Name and describe the OSI model.", "answer": ["Gave them the 4-5 layers that I knew off the top of my head, and a rough order. They accepted it and were happy with the detail I added."]}, {"key": 229, "position": "Software Security Engineer", "company": "Yelp", "date": "27 Aug 2019", "question": "Number to English words", "answer": []}, {"key": 230, "position": "Software Security Engineer", "company": "Yelp", "date": "27 Aug 2019", "question": "Load balancer with weights", "answer": []}, {"key": 231, "position": "Software Security Engineer", "company": "Yelp", "date": "27 Aug 2019", "question": "send/receive love message", "answer": []}, {"key": 232, "position": "Product Security Engineer", "company": "Salesforce", "date": "21 Aug 2019", "question": "Explain and write code for binary tree search?", "answer": ["Brainstormed a little bit and wrote in Java."]}, {"key": 233, "position": "IT Security Engineer", "company": "Gap Inc.", "date": "20 Aug 2019", "question": "Tell me about your automation experience, interviewer did most of the talking about future projects and ask yes or no questions", "answer": ["Explained previous projects, answered \"yes\" for most things"]}, {"key": 234, "position": "Information Security Engineer", "company": "Linux Academy", "date": "20 Aug 2019", "question": "What are you most proud of? What are you ashamed of? How well do you know Ruby, Docker, etc...", "answer": []}, {"key": 235, "position": "Security Engineer", "company": "General Motors (GM)", "date": "19 Aug 2019", "question": "Describe work security work you are working on now.", "answer": ["Describe Big Data security solution with Apache Ranger"]}, {"key": 236, "position": "Information Security Engineer", "company": "Ixaris", "date": "19 Aug 2019", "question": "My experience on the subject matter", "answer": ["I did give a synopsis of my career vis-a-vis the question."]}, {"key": 237, "position": "Information Security Engineer", "company": "Herc Rentals", "date": "16 Aug 2019", "question": "Questions about overall organizational security and app security. Tools used, etc...", "answer": []}, {"key": 238, "position": "Applications Security Engineer", "company": "Malwarebytes", "date": "15 Aug 2019", "question": "Mainly concentrated on Security of application development.", "answer": []}, {"key": 239, "position": "Applications Security Engineer", "company": "Wayfair", "date": "15 Aug 2019", "question": "security of upload feature", "answer": []}, {"key": 240, "position": "Security Engineer", "company": "Prime Therapeutics", "date": "12 Aug 2019", "question": "What's one time you messed up and how did you fix it.", "answer": ["Gave an example from my previous job"]}, {"key": 241, "position": "Systems Security Engineer", "company": "Salesforce", "date": "10 Aug 2019", "question": "describe kerberos", "answer": []}, {"key": 242, "position": "Security Engineer", "company": "J.P. Morgan", "date": "3 Aug 2019", "question": "Why should we pay you reimbursement?", "answer": []}, {"key": 243, "position": "Security Engineer", "company": "Booz Allen Hamilton", "date": "21 Jul 2019", "question": "How many years of experience do you have?", "answer": []}, {"key": 244, "position": "Security Engineer", "company": "NIKE", "date": "21 Jul 2019", "question": "Basic stuff - pay, why nike, etc", "answer": []}, {"key": 245, "position": "Senior Network Security Engineer", "company": "Mutual of Enumclaw Insurance", "date": "18 Jul 2019", "question": "I was asked to describe some of the projects I worked on in my position with my current employer. I was asked specific questions about my experience working in a team environment. There were also several questions on my experience with network and security devices, specifically devices used at Mutual of Enumclaw (Cisco, F5, Aruba, etc). There were specific technical questions about Cisco devices and a whiteboard network diagram.", "answer": []}, {"key": 246, "position": "Cyber Security Engineer", "company": "MITRE", "date": "17 Jul 2019", "question": "What does cyber mean to you?", "answer": []}, {"key": 247, "position": "Information Security Engineer", "company": "Wawa", "date": "15 Jul 2019", "question": "What levels of the NIST framework did I understand based on their use of the framework?", "answer": ["I asked them additional questions related to their network and provided them the answers from my point of view."]}, {"key": 248, "position": "F5 Security Engineer", "company": "SkyePoint Decisions", "date": "15 Jul 2019", "question": "How would you troubleshoot the F5 if a customer is unable to access a website? How would you verify traffic? What IP's does the F5 use for backend communication ? What is \"x-forwarded-for\" use for on the F5 ? Where do you apply the load balancing pool ? How would you test if a port is open from the F5 ?", "answer": []}, {"key": 249, "position": "Security Engineer", "company": "Revolut", "date": "15 Jul 2019", "question": "Home task - kind of CTF with 5(3 mandatory and 2 bonus) tasks. Technical interview - system design.", "answer": []}, {"key": 250, "position": "Security Engineer", "company": "Google", "date": "7 Jul 2019", "question": "There were a lot of domain related questions and follow up questions accordingly", "answer": []}, {"key": 251, "position": "Security Engineer", "company": "Uber", "date": "25 Jun 2019", "question": "Please look through the code example and point out as many vulns as you can.", "answer": ["I pointed out as many vulns as i could and the interviewer gave me hints to help get the last few"]}, {"key": 252, "position": "Security Engineer", "company": "Booz Allen Hamilton", "date": "25 Jun 2019", "question": "Why am I leaving my current position.", "answer": ["Looking for new opportunities to strengthen my knowledge."]}, {"key": 253, "position": "Information Security Engineer", "company": "Southeastern Grocers", "date": "21 Jun 2019", "question": "Technical questions, design and experience expressions", "answer": []}, {"key": 254, "position": "Security Engineer", "company": "Google", "date": "18 Jun 2019", "question": "Had two really simple and easy scripting question during the onsite interview", "answer": []}, {"key": 255, "position": "Security Engineer", "company": "Google", "date": "18 Jun 2019", "question": "Really high level of questions like how you will protect a network, and dive really deep into details according to your answers. You have to really understand everything you said to catch up with the following question interviewers asked.", "answer": []}, {"key": 256, "position": "Security Engineer", "company": "Salesforce", "date": "17 Jun 2019", "question": "A mix of technical and situational question related to the position. I can not provide specific questions due to an NDA with Salesforce.", "answer": []}, {"key": 257, "position": "Security Technology Engineer", "company": "Accudata Systems, Inc.", "date": "12 Jun 2019", "question": "What kind of position are you looking for?", "answer": ["Security Technology Engineer"]}, {"key": 258, "position": "Enterprise Security and BCP Engineer", "company": "Orange County's Credit Union", "date": "30 May 2019", "question": "I was asked about my experience related to the job.", "answer": []}, {"key": 259, "position": "Enterprise Security and BCP Engineer", "company": "Orange County's Credit Union", "date": "30 May 2019", "question": "If you could have a super power (invisibility or flying) which would you choose and why?", "answer": []}, {"key": 260, "position": "Security Engineer", "company": "Uber", "date": "24 May 2019", "question": "integer bit palindrome", "answer": ["how many question does the coding interview consists of?", "Only one"]}, {"key": 261, "position": "Security Engineer", "company": "Uber", "date": "24 May 2019", "question": "what is public key cryptography", "answer": []}, {"key": 262, "position": "Security Engineer", "company": "Dell Technologies", "date": "16 May 2019", "question": "how access control is tested ?", "answer": []}, {"key": 263, "position": "Security Software Engineer", "company": "DigitalOcean", "date": "14 May 2019", "question": "How would you detect a DDOS attack? How does the kernel know which function to call for the user? How would you go about reverse-engineering a custom protocol packet?", "answer": []}, {"key": 264, "position": "Network Security Engineer", "company": "Susquehanna International Group (SIG)", "date": "13 May 2019", "question": "Everything from basics. Vlans, Subnetting, HSRP, STP, BGP etc.", "answer": []}, {"key": 265, "position": "Security Engineer", "company": "Delta Dental Plans Association", "date": "13 May 2019", "question": "Can you tell me how you did the pentest in steps and which tools you think is useful and why?", "answer": []}, {"key": 266, "position": "IT Security Operations Engineer", "company": "Cloudflare", "date": "10 May 2019", "question": "Explain the working of DNS", "answer": []}, {"key": 267, "position": "Senior Infrastructure Security Engineer", "company": "Salesforce", "date": "1 May 2019", "question": "Describe your experience moving to Agile and how you use it today and what pros and cons have you experienced?", "answer": []}, {"key": 268, "position": "Principal Product Security Engineer", "company": "Salesforce", "date": "30 Apr 2019", "question": "How do you stay up to date with industry trends and modern research in one of the fastest evolving technical fields(cybersecurity) that exists?", "answer": ["I've positioned myself to have a strong set of mentors built over time through social events and conferences, a healthily curated twitter list of actual pioneers and leaders(this isn't to be mistaken with self proclaimed \"thought leaders\"), and constant practice. I treat security skills as you do art or music, and on top of learning/knowing something you must practice it to fully understand the quirks and edge cases."]}, {"key": 269, "position": "Security Engineer (Ecosystems)", "company": "Atlassian", "date": "25 Apr 2019", "question": "You have a pipeline for Docker images. How would you design everything to ensure the proper security checks? (Question changed to exclude discussion of what you'd use to implement these checks, to focusing on asking about how to design the policies, engagement model, and staff responsibilities)", "answer": []}, {"key": 270, "position": "Cyber Security Engineer", "company": "Johns Hopkins University Applied Physics Laboratory", "date": "24 Apr 2019", "question": "How do you deal with a situation where there isn't a straight forward plan?", "answer": ["I said I ask around and talk to my technical lead, then make progress, then go back and verify."]}, {"key": 271, "position": "Systems Security Engineer", "company": "Centene", "date": "10 Apr 2019", "question": "Describe the TCP three-way handshake.", "answer": []}, {"key": 272, "position": "Senior Security Services Engineer", "company": "CyberArk", "date": "9 Apr 2019", "question": "What is Vlan, trunk. What ports used for common protocols as ssh, ldap. what is GPO and how to update those from Win workstation. How to change unix password, how to recover root password on Nix machine. difference between TCP/UDP, TCP negotiation steps.", "answer": []}, {"key": 273, "position": "Senior Cyber Security Engineer", "company": "Raytheon Technologies", "date": "6 Apr 2019", "question": "Typical coding questions relative to low level driver driver development. Where variables exist in memory and their basic data types.", "answer": []}, {"key": 274, "position": "Applications Security Engineer", "company": "Entefy", "date": "5 Apr 2019", "question": "Do you want a job as a QA engineer>?", "answer": ["No, I applied for a security position. Don't waste my time."]}, {"key": 275, "position": "Security Engineer", "company": "Mr. Cooper", "date": "5 Apr 2019", "question": "Describe the CPU architecture of 32 Bit and 64 Bit, and which is better ?? Do you have UNIX experience What are the 7 layers of the OSI Model? Describe how the OSI model in steps how you would reach google.com from your browser?", "answer": ["These questions didn't have anything to do with the role I applied for? None of my experience on my resume was discussed, and it was a waste of time. Either the hiring manager was afraid of my diverse background skill set, or they already had someone in mind for the role...In other words, it could have been a fake interview!!!"]}, {"key": 276, "position": "Network Security Engineer", "company": "Copper River Family of Companies", "date": "4 Apr 2019", "question": "None. Recruiters avoid answering questions about compensation and scope of work. If someone is you hire is supposedly intelligent and skilled enough to design, build, and troubleshoot large, complex networks, do you think you will trick them into working on the cheap? Even if you did, how long do you think anyone with half a brain would stay? Did you see your horrible reviews?", "answer": []}, {"key": 277, "position": "Information Security Engineer", "company": "Trustmark", "date": "3 Apr 2019", "question": "Give an example of an issue you overcame with a coworker.", "answer": []}, {"key": 278, "position": "Software Security Engineer", "company": "Google", "date": "30 Mar 2019", "question": "what is the most serious security problem in our studied area?", "answer": []}, {"key": 279, "position": "Security Engineer", "company": "CGI", "date": "29 Mar 2019", "question": "How familiar was I with compliance protocols and security tools.", "answer": []}, {"key": 280, "position": "Network Security Engineer", "company": "NetCraftsmen", "date": "28 Mar 2019", "question": "They were standard questions. They want to see if you are a \"cultural\" fit.", "answer": ["This company only gives monthly paychecks. Based on that I declined the position. They will not volunteer this info upfront so don't forget to ask"]}, {"key": 281, "position": "Security Engineer", "company": "Microsoft", "date": "27 Mar 2019", "question": "What is the volume of Internet traffic transferred over public networks every day?", "answer": []}, {"key": 282, "position": "Security Incident Response Engineer", "company": "SAS Institute", "date": "22 Mar 2019", "question": "My level of knowledge related to SAS products.", "answer": []}, {"key": 283, "position": "Security Engineer", "company": "RSA Security", "date": "22 Mar 2019", "question": "Mostly resume relevant questions. You mention X on your resume, *insert detailed knowledge question*. Some questions around 'what would you do in X situation.' Good mix of technical as well as business acumen questions. What do you like most about your job, what do you dislike.", "answer": []}, {"key": 284, "position": "Cyber Security Engineer", "company": "The Aerospace Corporation", "date": "22 Mar 2019", "question": "Mostly high level and a few requiring specific technical experience", "answer": []}, {"key": 285, "position": "Information Security Engineer", "company": "Paxos", "date": "15 Mar 2019", "question": "Here's a laptop - Write a script that prints the first 25 primes in any language.", "answer": []}, {"key": 286, "position": "Information Security Engineer", "company": "Paxos", "date": "15 Mar 2019", "question": "Explain SSL", "answer": []}, {"key": 287, "position": "Information Security Engineer", "company": "Paxos", "date": "15 Mar 2019", "question": "What are some quick IT Sec wins - Can you encrypt everything at rest?", "answer": []}, {"key": 288, "position": "Linux Security Software Engineer", "company": "Qualcomm", "date": "9 Mar 2019", "question": "First Phone Screen - OS questions, Data structures, Security questions, Buffer Overflow, Memory Leak, Explain projects in your Resume, Semaphore vs Mutex", "answer": []}, {"key": 289, "position": "Senior Security Engineer", "company": "Presidio", "date": "8 Mar 2019", "question": "How do you configure syslog logging from the command line", "answer": []}, {"key": 290, "position": "Security Engineer", "company": "Cadre Information Security", "date": "6 Mar 2019", "question": "Do you have direct experience with CheckPoint products?", "answer": []}, {"key": 291, "position": "Applications Security Engineer", "company": "Travelers", "date": "6 Mar 2019", "question": "How do you ensure the development team knows the seriousness of the vulnerabilities reported?", "answer": []}, {"key": 292, "position": "Applications Security Engineer", "company": "Travelers", "date": "6 Mar 2019", "question": "How do we implement SSDLC in a CI/CD scenario", "answer": []}, {"key": 293, "position": "Applications Security Engineer", "company": "MX", "date": "5 Mar 2019", "question": "Describe your current role and what you are looking for in this role.", "answer": []}, {"key": 294, "position": "Cloud Security Engineer", "company": "Allstate", "date": "3 Mar 2019", "question": "What is an AWS placement group", "answer": ["A placement group is a way to have infrastructure live on the same hardware so you have the lowest latency possible."]}, {"key": 295, "position": "Security Engineer", "company": "Check Point Software Technologies", "date": "27 Feb 2019", "question": "What is TCP/IP", "answer": []}, {"key": 296, "position": "Security Engineer", "company": "Check Point Software Technologies", "date": "27 Feb 2019", "question": "Do you know what SaaS is?", "answer": ["Software as a service"]}, {"key": 297, "position": "Security Engineer", "company": "Check Point Software Technologies", "date": "27 Feb 2019", "question": "Can you describe a task where the customer was difficult and how did you handle it?", "answer": []}, {"key": 298, "position": "Security Engineer", "company": "Check Point Software Technologies", "date": "27 Feb 2019", "question": "What is the difference between a router and a firewall?", "answer": []}, {"key": 299, "position": "Security Engineer", "company": "Check Point Software Technologies", "date": "27 Feb 2019", "question": "Are you willing to relocate.", "answer": ["YOU MUST BE WILLING TO RELOCATE. I was not."]}, {"key": 300, "position": "Security Engineer", "company": "CSAA Insurance Group, a AAA Insurer", "date": "25 Feb 2019", "question": "Should you compress data before or after you encrypt?", "answer": ["Compress before so data compression works better. After encryption data will be randomly shuffled so the compression will not work as well."]}, {"key": 301, "position": "Security Vulnerability Management Engineer", "company": "Airbnb", "date": "21 Feb 2019", "question": "How would you handle an engineer downgrading the severity of a vulnerability just to extend the SLA?", "answer": ["Discuss the criteria for categorizing the vulnerability severity in the first place, emphasize that a downgrade merely to extend SLA isn't appropriate, come up with a plan to more accurately categorize vulnerabilities in the future so the downgrade issue doesn't come up as much."]}, {"key": 302, "position": "Security Engineer", "company": "Infosys", "date": "14 Feb 2019", "question": "Question on Recursion", "answer": []}, {"key": 303, "position": "Endpoint Security Engineer", "company": "Salesforce", "date": "13 Feb 2019", "question": "Do you prefer to work in a group or individually", "answer": []}, {"key": 304, "position": "Security Engineer", "company": "The Blackstone Group", "date": "9 Feb 2019", "question": "What do you like doing after work?", "answer": []}, {"key": 305, "position": "Security Engineer", "company": "The Blackstone Group", "date": "9 Feb 2019", "question": "How would you fix (insert broken product here )", "answer": ["Can\u2019t divulge the product but I spent about 5 minutes going over best practices for a smooth deployment"]}, {"key": 306, "position": "Security Engineer", "company": "The Blackstone Group", "date": "9 Feb 2019", "question": "What\u2019s your greatest weakness?", "answer": []}, {"key": 307, "position": "Cyber Security Engineer", "company": "NBCUniversal", "date": "5 Feb 2019", "question": "Why NBCUNIVERSAL", "answer": []}, {"key": 308, "position": "Security Engineer", "company": "Ping Identity", "date": "29 Jan 2019", "question": "technology stack questions (familiarity with Java, static analysis, ...)", "answer": []}, {"key": 309, "position": "Security Engineer", "company": "Coinbase", "date": "29 Jan 2019", "question": "Basic informational questions", "answer": []}, {"key": 310, "position": "Senior Security Engineer", "company": "Voleon", "date": "29 Jan 2019", "question": "Mainly just Linux technical trivia questions with some challenge questions specific to security implementation.", "answer": ["From a technical standpoint, it would be good to study up on Linux storage, networking and root kit detection. Also brush up on data encoding / decoding in various formats."]}, {"key": 311, "position": "Information Security Engineer", "company": "Teradata", "date": "23 Jan 2019", "question": "Tell us what projects you've been working on", "answer": []}, {"key": 312, "position": "Security Engineer", "company": "ReliaQuest", "date": "17 Jan 2019", "question": "Using an analogy, explain how DNS works.", "answer": ["It basically records the domin names and which ip address is assigned to them when a user makes a request the database runs to get the the name associated to the IP address the user is inquiring about."]}, {"key": 313, "position": "Security Engineer", "company": "ReliaQuest", "date": "17 Jan 2019", "question": "What 3 devices/programs would you want to be collecting logs from in a SIEM?", "answer": ["Solarwind,ibm qradar,mcafee"]}, {"key": 314, "position": "Security Engineer III", "company": "Mercury Systems", "date": "15 Jan 2019", "question": "How would I best handle a difficult situation if there was no one around to help?", "answer": []}, {"key": 315, "position": "Security Engineer III", "company": "Mercury Systems", "date": "15 Jan 2019", "question": "What is my experience and background with help desk, or customer service?", "answer": []}, {"key": 316, "position": "Security Engineer III", "company": "Mercury Systems", "date": "15 Jan 2019", "question": "What is my experience and background with Security?", "answer": []}, {"key": 317, "position": "Security Engineer III", "company": "Mercury Systems", "date": "15 Jan 2019", "question": "What type of experience do I have with the military?", "answer": []}, {"key": 318, "position": "Senior Security Engineer", "company": "GitLab", "date": "11 Jan 2019", "question": "Why you want to work at Gitlab?", "answer": []}, {"key": 319, "position": "Senior Security Engineer", "company": "GitLab", "date": "11 Jan 2019", "question": "I had no security related questions at all. What code have you written?", "answer": []}, {"key": 320, "position": "Senior Security Engineer", "company": "Recurly", "date": "5 Jan 2019", "question": "What port is X, what port is Y what is IPtables", "answer": []}, {"key": 321, "position": "Cyber Security Engineer", "company": "NIO", "date": "26 Dec 2018", "question": "What do you see as the weakest links in vehicle cyber security and how would you fix that?", "answer": []}, {"key": 322, "position": "Information Systems Security Engineer", "company": "CGI", "date": "26 Dec 2018", "question": "few technical questions, more about overall capabilities, experience and knowledge. Based experience in projects completed and level of contracts", "answer": ["based on my current experiences and processes."]}, {"key": 323, "position": "Security Engineer", "company": "First Citizens Bank", "date": "22 Dec 2018", "question": "Describe technology and experience", "answer": []}, {"key": 324, "position": "Security Engineer", "company": "AT&T", "date": "8 Dec 2018", "question": "What is ARP?", "answer": ["Address Resolution Protocol. It maps an IP to a physical machine."]}, {"key": 325, "position": "Senior Security Engineer", "company": "Mastercard", "date": "4 Dec 2018", "question": "Are you able to work independently?", "answer": ["Yes"]}, {"key": 326, "position": "Principal Security Engineer", "company": "Schlolastic", "date": "4 Dec 2018", "question": "Are you capable of writing a policy?", "answer": []}, {"key": 327, "position": "Information Security Engineer", "company": "J2 Global", "date": "29 Nov 2018", "question": "Do you want this position? Because the CISO doesn't have the ability to make a hiring decision at this company.", "answer": []}, {"key": 328, "position": "Senior Security Engineer", "company": "Salesforce", "date": "28 Nov 2018", "question": "What am I looking for in my next role.", "answer": ["I am looking to be surrounded by technology enthusiasts that appreciate collaboration."]}, {"key": 329, "position": "Infrastructure Security Engineer", "company": "Cloudflare", "date": "28 Nov 2018", "question": "Focused around security architecture reviews", "answer": []}, {"key": 330, "position": "Cyber Security Engineer", "company": "J.P. Morgan", "date": "28 Nov 2018", "question": "Tell us about your last project... how did you solve XYZ implementation problem in your software?", "answer": ["I would answer this but both question and answer would de-anonymize me most certainly."]}, {"key": 331, "position": "Cyber Security Engineer", "company": "J.P. Morgan", "date": "28 Nov 2018", "question": "What is behind the current change in career you are seeking?", "answer": ["\"I want to experience more collaboration, roll up my sleeves and 'get my hands dirty' again. I feel a little isolated in my current role, and there are so many exciting things happening I have decided to seek the right opportunity within a larger organization to fuel personal and professional growth.\""]}, {"key": 332, "position": "Cyber Security Engineer", "company": "Darktrace", "date": "21 Nov 2018", "question": "Know basic cybersecurity ish, traceroute, ping, TCP/IP, UDP troubleshooting, threats, vulnerabilities etc", "answer": ["I did not know how to explain a traceroute and that was very bad."]}, {"key": 333, "position": "Cyber Security Engineer", "company": "Darktrace", "date": "21 Nov 2018", "question": "General questions about resume, background, tell me about yourself, why do you want to work in cybersecurity, tell me about a time you experienced a challenge and had to pick up a new skill quickly.", "answer": []}, {"key": 334, "position": "Product Security Engineer", "company": "Cloudflare", "date": "13 Nov 2018", "question": "Security design questions, analyzing code for vulnerabilities, some networking fundamentals, and a lot of behavioral/moral/personal questions.", "answer": []}, {"key": 335, "position": "Cyber Security Engineer", "company": "Raytheon Technologies", "date": "11 Nov 2018", "question": "What are you looking for in this position?", "answer": []}, {"key": 336, "position": "Security Engineer", "company": "Proficio", "date": "11 Nov 2018", "question": "Tell me about yourself", "answer": []}, {"key": 337, "position": "Senior Network Design and Security Engineer", "company": "Undisclosed", "date": "9 Nov 2018", "question": "1. Describe BGP. 2. Tell us about network troubleshooting you have done in the past. 3. In wireshark, what does icmp 3 indicate?", "answer": []}, {"key": 338, "position": "Systems Security Engineer", "company": "Salesforce", "date": "7 Nov 2018", "question": "Mostly based on the field and the experience and handling different scenarios.", "answer": []}, {"key": 339, "position": "Senior Network Security Engineer", "company": "Fortinet", "date": "6 Nov 2018", "question": "TCP/IP, BGP, IPSEC", "answer": []}, {"key": 340, "position": "Security Engineer", "company": "Security Innovation", "date": "2 Nov 2018", "question": "How does HTTPS work? How is TLS and Diffie Helman used, and what steps are involved in the process and what happens at each point?", "answer": ["HTTPS takes the well-known and understood HTTP protocol, and simply layers a SSL/TLS (hereafter referred to simply as \u201cSSL\u201d) encryption layer on top of it. Servers and clients still speak exactly the same HTTP to each other, but over a secure SSL connection that encrypts and decrypts their requests and responses. The SSL layer has 2 main purposes: Verifying that you are talking directly to the server that you think you are talking to Ensuring that only the server can read what you send it and only you can read what it sends back Diffie-Hellman is used in SSL/TLS, as \"ephemeral Diffie-Hellman\" (the cipher suites with \"DHE\" in their name; see the standard). What is very rarely encountered is \"static Diffie-Hellman\" (cipher suites with \"DH\" in their name, but neither \"DHE\" or \"DH_anon\"): these cipher suites require that the server owns a certificate with a DH public key in it, which is rarely supported for a variety of historical and economical reasons, among which the main one is the availability of a free standard for RSA (PKCS#1) while the corresponding standard for Diffie-Hellman (x9.42) costs a hundred bucks, which is not much, but sufficient to deter most amateur developers. Diffie-Hellman is a key agreement protocol, meaning that if two parties (say, the SSL client and the SSL server) run this protocol, they end up with a shared secret K. However, neither client or server gets to choose the value of K; from their points of view, K looks randomly generated. It is secret (only them know K; eavesdroppers on the line do not) and shared (they both get the same value K), but not chosen. This is not encryption. A shared secret K is good enough, though, to process terabytes of data with a symmetric encryption algorithm (same K to encrypt on one side and decrypt on the other), and that is what happens in SSL. There is a well-known asymmetric encryption algorithm called RSA, though. With RSA, the sender can encrypt a message M with the recipient's public key, and the recipient can decrypt it and recover M using his private key. This time, the sender can choose the contents M. So your question might be: in a RSA world, why do we bother with AES at all ? The answer lies in the following points: There are constraints on M. If the recipient's public key has size n (in bytes, e.g. n = 256 for a 2048-bit RSA key), then the maximum size of M is n-11 bytes. In order to encrypt a longer message, we would have to split it into sufficiently small blocks, and include some reassembly mechanism. Nobody really knows how to do that securely. We have good reasons to believe that RSA on a single message is safe, but subtle weaknesses can lurk in any split-and-reassembly system and we are not comfortable with that. It is already bad enough with symmetric ciphers, where the mathematical situation is simpler. Even if we could handle the splitting-and-reassembly, there would be a size expansion. With a 2048-bit RSA key, an internal message chunk has size at most 245 bytes, but yields, when encrypted, a 256-byte sequence. This wastes our lifeforce, i.e. network bandwidth. Symmetric encryption incurs only a bounded overhead (well, SSL adds a slight overhead proportional to the data size, but it is much smaller than what would occur with a RSA-only protocol). Compared to AES, RSA is slow as Hell. We really like to have the option of using key agreement protocols like DH instead of RSA. In older times (before 2001), RSA was patented but not DH, so the US government was recommending DH. Nowadays, we want to be able to switch algorithms in case one becomes broken. In order to support key agreement protocols, we need some symmetric encryption, so we may just as well use it with RSA. It simplifies implementation and protocol analysis."]}, {"key": 341, "position": "Cyber Security Engineer", "company": "Coalfire", "date": "1 Nov 2018", "question": "explain pki and how it is used to encrypt and validate emails", "answer": ["this was the hardest question they asked. everything else was a joke."]}, {"key": 342, "position": "Cloud Security Engineer", "company": "Netskope", "date": "29 Oct 2018", "question": "Networking questions L4-L7, Security Ciphers, Linux, Logical reasoning question and understanding of the CASB space and the Netskope product", "answer": []}, {"key": 343, "position": "Network Security Engineer", "company": "Neustar", "date": "22 Oct 2018", "question": "My interest to join Neustar", "answer": ["Be confident on anything you say"]}, {"key": 344, "position": "Senior Cloud Security Engineer", "company": "ViacomCBS Streaming", "date": "17 Oct 2018", "question": "How would you secure the following resources in the cloud?", "answer": []}, {"key": 345, "position": "Information Security Engineer, Senior", "company": "Panasonic Avionics Corporation", "date": "17 Oct 2018", "question": "After the telephonic round, in onsite interview. I was asked questions on technologies I have not worked on and are not even mentioned on my resume.", "answer": ["Anyway I was asked to go to Lake Forest, California for a face to face interview and was told all the expenses are covered and will be reimbursed. Flight tickets were booked by them and also the the hotel was booked by them. The interview was next day and the flight back from LA. I beard a total of $230 that included lunch, dinner and Uber travels but was never reimbursed despite being told that everything is covered. Upon returning I provided them the receipts and requested for the reimbursement on Aug 20th, 2018 (Interview was on 17th Aug). I was told that they are processing the request and I will soon receive the check in mail. Fast forward a month and after a million of emails exchange they still had the audacity to lie that my check was still under process. Eventually, I was contacted by one of the person from Accounts department asking for more information and told me that it usually takes 1-2 weeks after he approves but didn\u2019t receive anything till date. Today marks the 2 month anniversary when I was interviewed at the cost of my own hard earned money and still no check. I have learnt a lesson that I should not just believe if it is a renowned company, the work culture will be good as well. I should have researched more and should have made an educated decision of whether or not I should work for such people. I believe it is a blessing in disguise that I was not offered the job. I guess if I have to struggle so much to get reimbursed for such a small amount ($230), how could I even imagine of getting paid. This process made my soured my interview experience and I would not recommend this company to anyone personally. If anyone still wants to go please be ready to shell out money from your own pocket as there is no guarantee you will get it back."]}, {"key": 346, "position": "Cyber Security Engineer", "company": "Lockheed Martin", "date": "16 Oct 2018", "question": "Tell us about a time when you made a suggestion to a superior that he or she accepted.", "answer": []}, {"key": 347, "position": "Cloud Security Engineer", "company": "Booz Allen Hamilton", "date": "16 Oct 2018", "question": "Basic questions for a solutions architect. What do you know about encryption? Also a lot of behavioral question and tell me about yourself questions.", "answer": []}, {"key": 348, "position": "Security Operations Engineer", "company": "LogicMonitor", "date": "15 Oct 2018", "question": "Use any language you want to hit an API and pull specific information.", "answer": []}, {"key": 349, "position": "Senior Product Security Engineer", "company": "Salesforce", "date": "15 Oct 2018", "question": "Questions surrounding infrastructure, in depth OWASP (and how to fix/remediate), code review, penetration testing methodology, threat modeling, applied cryptography (TLS, symmetric vs. asymmetric, cipher strengths), communication style.", "answer": []}, {"key": 350, "position": "Cyber-Security Engineer | Pen Tester", "company": "Marriott International", "date": "6 Oct 2018", "question": "Questions were completely out of the job description", "answer": []}, {"key": 351, "position": "Security Engineer", "company": "Comcast", "date": "28 Sep 2018", "question": "Tell me about a project you are proud of", "answer": []}, {"key": 352, "position": "Security Engineer", "company": "Tinder", "date": "9 Sep 2018", "question": "what will you do to harden the Mac OSX once given it to you fresh out of the box?", "answer": []}, {"key": 353, "position": "Security Engineer", "company": "Tinder", "date": "9 Sep 2018", "question": "do you have any questions for me given we only have two minutes left?", "answer": []}, {"key": 354, "position": "Security Engineer", "company": "Tinder", "date": "9 Sep 2018", "question": "what would you do if someone calls claiming he has malware on his mac?", "answer": []}, {"key": 355, "position": "Security Engineer", "company": "Tinder", "date": "9 Sep 2018", "question": "what compensation range are you comfortable with?", "answer": ["Through questions like this, interviewers are mostly trying to test your skillset (and its relevance to the role) as robustly as possible, so be prepared for multiple offshoots and followups. It could be a useful exercise to do mocks with friends or colleagues in Tinder to get a real sense of what the interview is actually like. Alternatively Prepfully has a ton of Tinder Security Engineer experts who provide mock interviews for a pretty reasonable amount. prepfully.com/practice-interviews"]}, {"key": 356, "position": "Applications Security Engineer", "company": "Snap", "date": "9 Sep 2018", "question": "The questions revolved around different application security areas , coding and somewhat system design", "answer": ["I tried rooftop slushie mentioned above and it was pretty helpful. I recommend it."]}, {"key": 357, "position": "Security Engineer", "company": "MetLife", "date": "6 Sep 2018", "question": "White boarded a packet flow from one network connected by VPN to another network.", "answer": ["Had to map out the ip packet information from start to finish as it traversed many networking devices."]}, {"key": 358, "position": "Information Security Engineer", "company": "Clover", "date": "4 Sep 2018", "question": "questions from resume", "answer": ["I explained about the tasks of that jobs and accomplishments"]}, {"key": 359, "position": "Security Engineer", "company": "Credit Karma", "date": "28 Aug 2018", "question": "White board coding and Security concepts", "answer": ["I tried rooftop slushie mentioned above and it was pretty helpful. I recommend it.", "There's a lot of elements to typically cover in these questions, clarifications, scoping, making sure you're answering the actual question the interviewer is looking for you to answer, etc. Could be worth doing a mock interview with one of the Prepfully Credit Karma Security Engineer experts... they've worked in the role so they clearly know how to get through the interview. prepfully.com/practice-interviews"]}, {"key": 360, "position": "Information Systems Security Engineer", "company": "Somos", "date": "27 Aug 2018", "question": "what is an advantage of a domain?", "answer": ["Central management and organization of a group of devices, users, and resources.", "This question was obviously asked by someone who knows nothing about security. What is an advantage of a domain? What type of domain were they asking about? Physical? The name in a DNS? A logically separated environment? You are lucky you were not hired. The VP in charge is unethical and intolerable. Most people there don't like or trust him but he is protected by the COO.", "On the contrary, that question can only be understood by an applicant who knows that \u201cDomain\u201d here refers to applying the ISO 27001 standard. It has nothing to do with your website.", "The interviewer definitely knew what he was asking."]}, {"key": 361, "position": "Applications Security Engineer", "company": "Ancestry", "date": "22 Aug 2018", "question": "I'm not sure if this is publicly shareable information.", "answer": []}, {"key": 362, "position": "Security Engineer", "company": "ACI Worldwide", "date": "16 Aug 2018", "question": "What times can you block off for the interview?", "answer": ["Stop wasting my time."]}, {"key": 363, "position": "Senior Security Engineer", "company": "EZLynx", "date": "10 Aug 2018", "question": "Experience with Endpoint Protection", "answer": ["Explained my experience with AntiMalware, Antivirius, Antispyware policies, Scan frequencies, DLP methods, DLP policies, Host and Network DLP policy setups."]}, {"key": 364, "position": "Senior Security Engineer", "company": "EZLynx", "date": "10 Aug 2018", "question": "My experience with Cisco Firewalls, IDS/IPS", "answer": ["I gave him details about my experience with Cisco FTDs, ASAs the default rules setup in IDS/IPS modes, The implicit deny rules, the way objects are created and mapped to Policies or rules."]}, {"key": 365, "position": "Software Security Engineer", "company": "Booz Allen Hamilton", "date": "6 Aug 2018", "question": "How to ROP?", "answer": ["Just talk about the basics of ROP. How its used. Why its used. I talked about the x86 platform."]}, {"key": 366, "position": "Security Engineer", "company": "Under Armour", "date": "16 Jul 2018", "question": "They wanted to see if I could build and implement a web-based service on the fly. This task can be performed by a competent programmer, so I assume they got one. Task: White board a program in your favorite programming language, write it, run it, secure it and criticize it. Instruction was to create web service, google web, enter a&b, and service calc c=a/b, Return value from website. This interview occurred *before* the massive data breach, so not sure if this is in practice anymore.", "answer": ["Wrote from a template and performed as instructed with protest noted. Recommend outsourcing this kind of screening to HR experts such as indeed.com."]}, {"key": 367, "position": "Information Security Engineer", "company": "ThousandEyes", "date": "12 Jul 2018", "question": "All kind of security questions, the question kept going deeper and deeper so the interviewer had an idea about my true knowledge ans skill set", "answer": []}, {"key": 368, "position": "Enterprise IT Security Engineer", "company": "Intrado", "date": "9 Jul 2018", "question": "Explain how traceroute works", "answer": []}, {"key": 369, "position": "Enterprise IT Security Engineer", "company": "Intrado", "date": "9 Jul 2018", "question": "What port does ping use", "answer": []}, {"key": 370, "position": "Security Engineer", "company": "Qubole", "date": "27 Jun 2018", "question": "Most of the questions came from my resume. Apart from that few on securing cloud infrastructure/ docker containers. Past security related projects and enhancements.", "answer": []}, {"key": 371, "position": "Security Engineer", "company": "Acquia", "date": "22 Jun 2018", "question": "How would you secure an EC2?", "answer": ["Keep packages up to date, install a waf to check connections, bot detection, use a stable os like CentOS, use roles instead of keys, principle of least privilege, enable cloudtrail, use cloudwatch to monitor logs, send logs to a splunk server, and external monitoring like newrelic."]}, {"key": 372, "position": "Security Engineer", "company": "eVigilant Security", "date": "20 Jun 2018", "question": "Did I know CAD", "answer": ["Yes"]}, {"key": 373, "position": "Security Engineer", "company": "Salesforce", "date": "18 Jun 2018", "question": "Explain the OSI model.", "answer": ["Describe Spectre and Meltdown and what happens on the kernal leve?"]}, {"key": 374, "position": "Lead Information Security Engineer", "company": "Salesforce", "date": "18 Jun 2018", "question": "Various technical and scenario based questions, mainly generic and focused on concepts, exploit classes and protocols, not tooling.", "answer": []}, {"key": 375, "position": "Network Security Engineer", "company": "Sungard Availability Services", "date": "18 Jun 2018", "question": "Questions were based on a deep understanding of protocols and open to conversation in exploring answers.", "answer": []}, {"key": 376, "position": "Security Engineer", "company": "Salesforce", "date": "15 Jun 2018", "question": "Questions about cloud experience, scripting, automation, etc", "answer": []}, {"key": 377, "position": "Security Engineer", "company": "New Relic", "date": "11 Jun 2018", "question": "What security measures would you put in place for a brand new video streaming service? Elaborate on each item.", "answer": []}, {"key": 378, "position": "Security Engineer", "company": "New Relic", "date": "11 Jun 2018", "question": "Given a particular message you need to convey, how would you draft out a mass email to all developers in the org.", "answer": []}, {"key": 379, "position": "Security Engineer", "company": "Hotwire", "date": "7 Jun 2018", "question": "How would you protect a host on the same network/equipment/switch. Prevent communication, etc.", "answer": ["There are many ways but one of the methods is to implement Private Vlans..."]}, {"key": 380, "position": "Security Solutions Engineer", "company": "Cisco Systems", "date": "6 Jun 2018", "question": "List the layers to the OSI model and describe each layer.", "answer": ["A router"]}, {"key": 381, "position": "Applications Security Engineer", "company": "Procore Technologies", "date": "5 Jun 2018", "question": "Scenario based questions, and Why would i handle that way and how else can i handle? What tools would I prefer over the others and Why? In depth questions of every element in my resume.", "answer": ["Experience based; providing good examples to support my approach."]}, {"key": 382, "position": "Applications Security Engineer", "company": "Procore Technologies", "date": "5 Jun 2018", "question": "Scenario based questions, and Why would i handle that way and how else can i handle? What tools would I prefer over the others and Why? In depth questions of every element in my resume.", "answer": ["Experience based; providing good examples to support my approach."]}, {"key": 383, "position": "Cyber Security Engineer", "company": "TEKsystems", "date": "5 Jun 2018", "question": "Compositions of Splunk and troubleshooting methodologies", "answer": ["Answer such questions like you would in your own industry. How would you problem solve. Who would you contact based on the problem?"]}, {"key": 384, "position": "Senior Applications Security Engineer", "company": "Elementum", "date": "3 Jun 2018", "question": "OWASP top 10 knowledge. Questions around building out an app sec pipeline/process.", "answer": []}, {"key": 385, "position": "Senior Applications Security Engineer", "company": "Cavirin", "date": "3 Jun 2018", "question": "OWASP top 10 knowledge. Cloud security domain knowledge.", "answer": []}, {"key": 386, "position": "Cyber Security Engineer", "company": "AT&T", "date": "29 May 2018", "question": "explain the RMF process", "answer": []}, {"key": 387, "position": "Product Security Engineer", "company": "Salesforce", "date": "29 May 2018", "question": "What is FIDM used for?", "answer": []}, {"key": 388, "position": "Security Engineer", "company": "Autodesk", "date": "26 May 2018", "question": "SQL injection, Threat Modelling, CSRF, XSS, SSL, Buffer overflow, Cryptography", "answer": []}, {"key": 389, "position": "Security Engineer", "company": "Amazon Lab126", "date": "19 May 2018", "question": "Leadership principles and whiteboard exercises", "answer": []}, {"key": 390, "position": "Security Engineer", "company": "Amazon Lab126", "date": "19 May 2018", "question": "NDA", "answer": []}, {"key": 391, "position": "Information Security Engineer", "company": "Produce Pro Software", "date": "8 May 2018", "question": "Why would i want to work with them.", "answer": []}, {"key": 392, "position": "Information Security Engineer", "company": "Guaranteed Rate", "date": "7 May 2018", "question": "Guaranteed Rate asked me to describe a situation in which I'd failed and what I'd taken away from that experience.", "answer": []}, {"key": 393, "position": "Security Operations Engineer", "company": "DigitalOcean", "date": "5 May 2018", "question": "How to find persistent threats?", "answer": ["Increasing monitoring and detective capabilities of your network infrastructure is critical for identifying APT threats"]}, {"key": 394, "position": "Security Operations Engineer", "company": "DigitalOcean", "date": "5 May 2018", "question": "How do you integrate yourself into a new team?", "answer": []}, {"key": 395, "position": "Security Operations Engineer", "company": "DigitalOcean", "date": "5 May 2018", "question": "How do you like to work with others?", "answer": []}, {"key": 396, "position": "Security Operations Engineer", "company": "DigitalOcean", "date": "5 May 2018", "question": "How to monitor for malware?", "answer": []}, {"key": 397, "position": "Security Operations Engineer", "company": "DigitalOcean", "date": "5 May 2018", "question": "A time when a TTP worked better than an IOC.", "answer": []}, {"key": 398, "position": "Security Operations Engineer", "company": "DigitalOcean", "date": "5 May 2018", "question": "What is the coolest malware or hack you have researched or analyzed.", "answer": []}, {"key": 399, "position": "Security Operations Engineer", "company": "DigitalOcean", "date": "5 May 2018", "question": "Tell us about a time when you worked with team members on a challenging project.", "answer": []}, {"key": 400, "position": "Applications Security Engineer", "company": "LinkedIn", "date": "3 May 2018", "question": "Leetcode Qs., Design, Behavioral", "answer": ["Stick to Leetcode"]}, {"key": 401, "position": "Product Security Engineer", "company": "Salesforce", "date": "25 Apr 2018", "question": "They asked me to describe the difference between encryption and hashing.", "answer": ["Encryption is invertible, while hashing is a one-way function. Hashing is often used to store credentials, while any information that is encrypted will eventually be decrypted and examined in plain text."]}, {"key": 402, "position": "Senior Product Security Engineer", "company": "Salesforce", "date": "23 Apr 2018", "question": "What are the different types of blind SQL injections?", "answer": ["The type of blind SQL injection I'm most familiar with is timing based. The other type is content based also referred to as binary blind SQL injection."]}, {"key": 403, "position": "Senior Security Engineer", "company": "Joyent", "date": "20 Apr 2018", "question": "How do you implement SNORT,", "answer": []}, {"key": 404, "position": "Software Security Engineer", "company": "Microsoft", "date": "18 Apr 2018", "question": "Multiple kind of questions, both technical and personal.", "answer": []}, {"key": 405, "position": "Security Engineer", "company": "Box", "date": "16 Apr 2018", "question": "Usual application security stuff and one interview round with DS coding.", "answer": []}, {"key": 406, "position": "Staff Applications Security Engineer", "company": "Box", "date": "15 Apr 2018", "question": "Product based security architecture and pseudo coding exercise", "answer": []}, {"key": 407, "position": "Information Security Engineer", "company": "Cloudflare", "date": "11 Apr 2018", "question": "Things and such?", "answer": ["Yes."]}, {"key": 408, "position": "Security Engineer", "company": "LinkedIn", "date": "10 Apr 2018", "question": "The engineer/manager asked 2-3 technical questions after I talk about work experience in the past.", "answer": []}, {"key": 409, "position": "Information Security Engineer", "company": "CynergisTek", "date": "10 Apr 2018", "question": "Where do you see yourself over the next five years?", "answer": ["without a job"]}, {"key": 410, "position": "Network Security Engineer", "company": "United Natural Foods", "date": "10 Apr 2018", "question": "What experience do you have with Firepower", "answer": ["I have extensive experience with firepower - I have implemented it and have been using it daily for the past 6 years."]}, {"key": 411, "position": "Security Engineer", "company": "Parkland Health & Hospital System", "date": "9 Apr 2018", "question": "What type of controls / CONOPs would you suggest to protect patient data in  scenario?", "answer": []}, {"key": 412, "position": "Security Engineer, New Grad", "company": "Samsara", "date": "8 Apr 2018", "question": "System design: Design an employee timesheet system that allows workers to update their status (working, on break, not working) and view the hours worked in a day/week. Provide the database tables for this and the RESTful API for this application. Show how the developer would pass information to the RESTful APIs", "answer": []}, {"key": 413, "position": "Security Engineer, New Grad", "company": "Samsara", "date": "8 Apr 2018", "question": "Given 2 lists of tuples [(time1,time2),...] and [(time3,time4)], return a list of tuples of time ranges at which times intersect", "answer": []}, {"key": 414, "position": "Security Engineer, New Grad", "company": "Samsara", "date": "8 Apr 2018", "question": "Company related technical question involving ranges: Given a list of tuples of [(time,temp), ...], return a list of tuples of time ranges where temp is above 50.", "answer": []}, {"key": 415, "position": "Security Engineer, New Grad", "company": "Samsara", "date": "8 Apr 2018", "question": "Implement an LRU cache", "answer": []}, {"key": 416, "position": "Information Security Engineer", "company": "John Hancock", "date": "6 Apr 2018", "question": "Why don't you contact people back when you have directly reached out to them?", "answer": ["Lack of communication is the MO of this hiring manager."]}, {"key": 417, "position": "Cyber Security Engineer", "company": "ReliaQuest", "date": "4 Apr 2018", "question": "What can you tell me about ports?", "answer": ["I flubbed this question a little because it was such a broad question. But if you know the well known ports, how ports work, ect you should be fine."]}, {"key": 418, "position": "Software Engineer- Corporate Security", "company": "Facebook", "date": "4 Apr 2018", "question": "If you have to build security around your corporate network from scratch, how will you do it?", "answer": []}, {"key": 419, "position": "Security Engineer", "company": "1-800-FLOWERS.COM, Inc.", "date": "1 Apr 2018", "question": "How do you handle phishing attempts SQL Injections XSS", "answer": []}, {"key": 420, "position": "Senior Security Engineer", "company": "Goldman Sachs", "date": "31 Mar 2018", "question": "What have you done w/docker? What AWS experience do you have? Tell me: about Same origin policy about CORS how to store passwords in a web app how to build an authentication module\u2018 about Click jacking about Cert pinning - Why are we doing this? about Mobile (keystore) about Ssrf about Headers for modern browsers hsts/secure/etc/httponly about http pollution about XSRF - what if can\u2019t use nonces? What keeps you up at night? about XSS/XSRF/SQLi about Inter tier auth about Galois counter mode about Authenticated encryption about Docker container - security about fine grained vs coarse grained entitlements about PFS about Async vs Sync enc Top 5 thing to secure a web site about a recent Scripting story about a recent InfoSec story about Tcp vs udp behavior - when scanned if port is not bound", "answer": ["Mostly very well."]}, {"key": 421, "position": "Software Security Engineer", "company": "Cisco Systems", "date": "29 Mar 2018", "question": "Reverse a doubly-linked list.", "answer": ["What does it even mean reverse a double linked list it's a bidirectional , does it even make sense to reverse a link list"]}, {"key": 422, "position": "Senior Security Engineer", "company": "Rackspace Technology", "date": "23 Mar 2018", "question": "What did the recruiter tell you about this position?", "answer": []}, {"key": 423, "position": "Network Security Engineer", "company": "Susquehanna International Group (SIG)", "date": "23 Mar 2018", "question": "give me the difference between ACL and a Router ?", "answer": ["I gave an answer that i felt appropriate at that moment."]}, {"key": 424, "position": "Security Engineer", "company": "CSC", "date": "23 Mar 2018", "question": "They asked questions relating to the OSI model.", "answer": ["I answered the question correctly based on my studies."]}, {"key": 425, "position": "Senior Cyber Security Engineer", "company": "Lumen", "date": "22 Mar 2018", "question": "Why would you want to work for CenturyLink ?", "answer": []}, {"key": 426, "position": "Info Security Engineer", "company": "Bank of America", "date": "16 Mar 2018", "question": "\"Tell me about your professional history/go over your resume with us...\"", "answer": []}, {"key": 427, "position": "Information Security Engineer", "company": "Dean Foods", "date": "8 Mar 2018", "question": "Technical and personality based question, a lot of them were from my resume, like my past technical experiences and how to's", "answer": []}, {"key": 428, "position": "Information Security Engineer", "company": "TransUnion", "date": "8 Mar 2018", "question": "About my recent experience", "answer": []}, {"key": 429, "position": "IT Security Engineer", "company": "ConnectiveRx", "date": "7 Mar 2018", "question": "What vulnerability scanning tools do you use?", "answer": ["I have used both Qualys and Nessus. After doing an internal scan, of which I've done both unauthenticated and authenticated, I typically attempt to reduce the results for Operations teams for any vulnerabilities that may have mitigating factors in play; for instance a well-configured firewall in-between zones. I prefer to work with other teams and not create unnecessary work for them."]}, {"key": 430, "position": "IT Security Engineer", "company": "ConnectiveRx", "date": "7 Mar 2018", "question": "What SIEM do you use?", "answer": ["I currently use and am certified in LogRhythm."]}, {"key": 431, "position": "Senior Cyber Security Engineer", "company": "MITRE", "date": "5 Mar 2018", "question": "Presentation", "answer": ["What level position did you apply for and what salary did you say was your minimum?"]}, {"key": 432, "position": "Security Sales Engineer", "company": "Rapid7", "date": "3 Mar 2018", "question": "If you were going to attack a fortified castle, what is the first thing you would do?", "answer": []}, {"key": 433, "position": "Security Sales Engineer", "company": "Rapid7", "date": "3 Mar 2018", "question": "What is cross-site scripting?", "answer": []}, {"key": 434, "position": "Security Sales Engineer", "company": "Rapid7", "date": "3 Mar 2018", "question": "What is the difference between an exploit and a vulnerability?", "answer": []}, {"key": 435, "position": "Security Engineer", "company": "Salesforce", "date": "2 Mar 2018", "question": "Details around the advantages or disadvantages of different protocols, how would I handle different situations. Many of the questions we're situation based that didn't have a black and white answer and usually morphed into additional questions as the answer progressed in the situation.", "answer": []}, {"key": 436, "position": "Security Solution Engineer", "company": "Union Bank", "date": "1 Mar 2018", "question": "What related regulations do you know? Say something detailed about it.", "answer": []}, {"key": 437, "position": "Security Engineer", "company": "Amazon", "date": "19 Feb 2018", "question": "Do you have experience in writing REGEX?", "answer": ["Not an expert but to some extent"]}, {"key": 438, "position": "Senior Network Security Engineer", "company": "Providence Equity", "date": "14 Feb 2018", "question": "there were some technical questions - met with managers - cto - staff - hr- all great conversations. I thought I aced the whole process but was declined because I wasn't a good fit. from what I understand that is a common response from them - I would have liked actual feedback but there was none.", "answer": ["Q: what is your favorite color A:blue Q: why can't the network talk to the other A: vlans not passed over trunk and there is no gateway Q:how many networks in a /16 mask A:256"]}, {"key": 439, "position": "Applications Security Engineer", "company": "Paycom", "date": "7 Feb 2018", "question": "Fizz-Buzz problem on school campus, mostly behavioral on the Paycom campus.", "answer": []}, {"key": 440, "position": "Cyber Security Systems Engineer", "company": "Knight Point Systems", "date": "1 Feb 2018", "question": "What would I do if a system was not responding and running much slower than usual?", "answer": []}, {"key": 441, "position": "Senior Information Security Technology Engineer", "company": "BECU", "date": "30 Jan 2018", "question": "Nothing stands out. Mostly they were experiential questions like \"Have you worked with this product or that product?\"", "answer": []}, {"key": 442, "position": "Information Security Engineer", "company": "Handango", "date": "28 Jan 2018", "question": "What type of security products are your familiar with to protect e-commerce sites?", "answer": []}, {"key": 443, "position": "Security Engineer", "company": "Shape Security", "date": "24 Jan 2018", "question": "most of questions come from your resume. your project whether is possible to convert into a application", "answer": ["Can you please explain what you mean by the second part of your sentence", "The key in these questions is to cover the fundamentals, and be ready for the back-and-forth with the interviewer. Might be worth doing a mock interview with one of the Shape Security or ex-Shape Security Security Engineer experts on Prepfully? They give real-world practice and guidance, which is pretty helpful. prepfully.com/practice-interviews"]}, {"key": 444, "position": "Senior Security Engineer", "company": "Bluebeam", "date": "18 Jan 2018", "question": "Various questions about security which they didn't really know anything about, as they don't have anyone doing security engineering for them.", "answer": []}, {"key": 445, "position": "Security Engineer", "company": "Delta Air Lines", "date": "18 Jan 2018", "question": "'Tell me about a time where you had a job and failed and what were your actions?'", "answer": []}, {"key": 446, "position": "Security Engineer", "company": "Bluebeam", "date": "17 Jan 2018", "question": "Mostly questions about security and things they don't know anything about, since they have no one doing security for them.", "answer": ["I did better than anyone they will ever interview again."]}, {"key": 447, "position": "Senior Product Security Engineer", "company": "Salesforce", "date": "16 Jan 2018", "question": "The questions focused on application security concepts (browser security model, application vulnerabilities, etc.) and software engineering principles.", "answer": []}, {"key": 448, "position": "Information Security Engineer", "company": "Nissan North America", "date": "10 Jan 2018", "question": "I wasn\u2019t asked any except for vocabulary words that might possibly relate to the job.", "answer": ["See comments above"]}, {"key": 449, "position": "Security Infrastructure Engineer", "company": "Unity", "date": "5 Jan 2018", "question": "Whiteboard style questions about securing infrastructure and services, attack vectors, and technical processes.", "answer": []}, {"key": 450, "position": "Security Engineer", "company": "Palo Alto Networks", "date": "5 Jan 2018", "question": "Most questions are based on the projects listed on my resume so you should be familiar with your projects.", "answer": []}, {"key": 451, "position": "Senior Security Engineer", "company": "Salesforce", "date": "16 Dec 2017", "question": "I signed an NDA, so I am unable share interview questions.", "answer": ["n/a"]}, {"key": 452, "position": "Information Security Engineer", "company": "Northrop Grumman", "date": "8 Dec 2017", "question": "Demonstrate your cybersecurity skills in a lab environment.", "answer": ["Document and present your presentation to the panel."]}, {"key": 453, "position": "Security Engineer", "company": "Segment", "date": "27 Nov 2017", "question": "Basically threat modeling/design of a new service within the Segment environment", "answer": []}, {"key": 454, "position": "Security Engineer", "company": "Credit Karma", "date": "27 Nov 2017", "question": "OWASP Top 10. Remediations, identification, etc.", "answer": ["The key in these questions is to cover the fundamentals, and be ready for the back-and-forth with the interviewer. Might be worth doing a mock interview with one of the Credit Karma or ex-Credit Karma Security Engineer experts on Prepfully? They give real-world practice and guidance, which is pretty helpful. prepfully.com/practice-interviews"]}, {"key": 455, "position": "Applications Security Engineer", "company": "Twitch", "date": "27 Nov 2017", "question": "OWASP Top 10. Explanations, identification, remediation, etc.", "answer": []}, {"key": 456, "position": "Principal Information Security Engineer", "company": "Deem", "date": "27 Nov 2017", "question": "No unusual or difficult questions Pretty standard technical questions.", "answer": ["I explained about my experience and how I would manage all of the responsibilities of the role."]}, {"key": 457, "position": "Security Engineer", "company": "ReliaQuest", "date": "25 Nov 2017", "question": "Describe what a DMZ is", "answer": []}, {"key": 458, "position": "Cyber Security Engineer", "company": "Lockheed Martin", "date": "16 Nov 2017", "question": "Explain your familiarity with the DoD Information Assurance process (DIACAP). Explain how to implement vulnerability scans and how to mitigate threats and formulate risk into information which could be explained to management to formulate an opinion to accept or deny authorization to operate an IA Enabled device or system.", "answer": ["I presented them with the technical and administrative answers to their questions which ensured them that my subject matter expertise would be valuable to their risk based analysis approach to Information Assurance."]}, {"key": 459, "position": "Cyber Security Engineer", "company": "Best Buy", "date": "12 Nov 2017", "question": "Name as many common ports and their numbers.", "answer": ["22 SSH, 21 FTP, 53 DNS, 80 HTTP, etc. You get the idea."]}, {"key": 460, "position": "Network Security Operations Engineer", "company": "Salesforce", "date": "8 Nov 2017", "question": "What is a firewall, where do you deploy them? Dynamic routing protocols, explain their signifance in enterprise architecture? Signify security vulnerabilities and offer remediations ? Tell about recent ransomware attacks ? How do you do firewall policy auditing?", "answer": []}, {"key": 461, "position": "Cyber Security Engineer", "company": "The DigiTrust Group", "date": "25 Oct 2017", "question": "Technical questions relating to cyber security", "answer": []}, {"key": 462, "position": "Network Security Engineer", "company": "Infinite Resource Solutions", "date": "23 Oct 2017", "question": "basic network and security questions", "answer": ["answered all questions"]}, {"key": 463, "position": "Security Engineer", "company": "Salesforce", "date": "21 Oct 2017", "question": "Experience, examples of work that ties in the role few technical questions.", "answer": ["Calmly and gave examples along with addressing the different security questions about penetration tests and vulnerability assessment."]}, {"key": 464, "position": "Security Engineer", "company": "CloudPassage", "date": "18 Oct 2017", "question": "Why do you want to be on the vendor side of IT Security?", "answer": ["Its a very open and growing market, that doesn't seem to be going away any time soon, lots of room for profit."]}, {"key": 465, "position": "Senior Security Engineer", "company": "Lands' End", "date": "13 Oct 2017", "question": "Repeated questions with most interviewers: \"You are able and interested in relocating to Dodgeville?\"", "answer": ["Before visiting the campus I expressed my interest in relocating to the region between Dodgeville and Madison WI. After the onsite interviews, visiting the campus in Dodgeville, and Madision, I confirmed my commitment moving to Madison and working at the campus. A generous relocation benefit package provided the resources necessary to move household goods across the country to my new residence."]}, {"key": 466, "position": "Senior Security Engineer", "company": "Lands' End", "date": "13 Oct 2017", "question": "Repeated questions with most interviewers: \"You are able and interested in relocating to Dodgeville?\"", "answer": ["Before visiting the campus I expressed my interest in relocating to the region between Dodgeville and Madison WI. After the onsite interviews, visiting the campus in Dodgeville, and Madision, I confirmed my commitment moving to Madison and working at the campus. A generous relocation benefit package provided the resources necessary to move household goods across the country to my new residence."]}, {"key": 467, "position": "Cyber Security Engineer", "company": "Forcepoint", "date": "11 Oct 2017", "question": "What version of Forcepoint do you use? Whats your experience with DLP? Whats the most recent thing you have done? Any experience with machine learning or fingerprinting? Are you willing to relocate to TX?", "answer": ["Ha, what version of forcepoint? Too funny. Again the company has smart people in it but lead by empowered people who make all the wrong decisions."]}, {"key": 468, "position": "Security Engineer", "company": "DoorDash", "date": "11 Oct 2017", "question": "Basic questions on OWASP top 10 and general security concepts.", "answer": []}, {"key": 469, "position": "Senior Security Engineer", "company": "VMware", "date": "9 Oct 2017", "question": "I was shown code and asked to find the security issues in it", "answer": ["I found the security issues"]}, {"key": 470, "position": "Senior Cyber Security Engineer", "company": "Invictus International Consulting", "date": "2 Oct 2017", "question": "They described a policy challenge that was currently being felt by engineers within a customer staff.", "answer": []}, {"key": 471, "position": "Senior Security Engineer", "company": "Mixpanel", "date": "2 Oct 2017", "question": "How would I migrate very, very large (many TB) of user data from a bare-metal data center to AWS?", "answer": ["My preferred answer was a truck full of HDDs. Then I sketched out a way to do it in software.", "There's a lot of elements to typically cover in these questions, clarifications, scoping, making sure you're answering the actual question the interviewer is looking for you to answer, etc. Could be worth doing a mock interview with one of the Prepfully Mixpanel Senior Security Engineer experts... they've worked in the role so they clearly know how to get through the interview. prepfully.com/practice-interviews"]}, {"key": 472, "position": "Security Solutions Engineer", "company": "Cisco Systems", "date": "1 Oct 2017", "question": "Are you aware of the Equifax security breach? What caused it?", "answer": ["I was aware of the recent breach with Equifax, but was not entirely sure what caused it. I wagered a guess that it was some sort of exploit related to their web services server.", "Apache struts vulnerability was exploited. Struts REST supports XML using a programming library called XStream, which allows you to encode any sort of Java object into XML. XStream XML data can be manipulated by injecting the XML representation of Java objects into the request. An attacker would then take advantage of this to execute arbitrary code or shell commands in the context of the server running the XStream process."]}, {"key": 473, "position": "Security Solutions Engineer", "company": "Cisco Systems", "date": "1 Oct 2017", "question": "Can two different IP addresses connect to the same port on a given web server?", "answer": ["This was a weird question the way he framed it (which was different from how I wrote it here on Glassdoor). I believe the answer is yes, since as long as both IP addresses are trying to connect to the same service hosted on a given port, they will be able to do so. If both IP addresses are trying to connect to two different services on the same port, they will not be able to do so."]}, {"key": 474, "position": "Security Solutions Engineer", "company": "Cisco Systems", "date": "1 Oct 2017", "question": "What are the seven layers of the OSI model?", "answer": ["Physical, Data Link, Network, Transport, Session, Presentation, and Application in that order"]}, {"key": 475, "position": "Senior Security Sales Engineer", "company": "Rapid7", "date": "18 Sep 2017", "question": "Very basic questions about history, salary requirements, etc.", "answer": []}, {"key": 476, "position": "Security Engineer", "company": "Tile", "date": "16 Sep 2017", "question": "Describe how TLS works in layman's terms", "answer": []}, {"key": 477, "position": "Security Engineer", "company": "Tile", "date": "16 Sep 2017", "question": "How would you secure a hosted instance?", "answer": []}, {"key": 478, "position": "Security Engineer", "company": "Coupa Software Inc", "date": "14 Sep 2017", "question": "If I was willing to work at the office, and not from home.", "answer": []}, {"key": 479, "position": "Security Engineer", "company": "Raytheon Technologies", "date": "11 Sep 2017", "question": "How would you gain access to this locked phone in front of you?", "answer": []}, {"key": 480, "position": "Software Security Development Engineer", "company": "Chef Software", "date": "1 Sep 2017", "question": "Have you ever been in a mentor/teacher?", "answer": []}, {"key": 481, "position": "Software Security Development Engineer", "company": "Chef Software", "date": "1 Sep 2017", "question": "Why are you interested in working for Chef?", "answer": []}, {"key": 482, "position": "Associate IS Security Engineer", "company": "Amgen", "date": "31 Aug 2017", "question": "Name two threat actors and what would their motive be to steal information? What do you know about the WannaCry Ransomware? How is WannaCry different from Petya Ransomware? What is the difference of a stateful vs. stateless firewall?", "answer": []}, {"key": 483, "position": "Security Engineer", "company": "Abacode", "date": "29 Aug 2017", "question": "What have I done as a Security Engineer and what are my expectations", "answer": []}, {"key": 484, "position": "Security Automation Developer", "company": "BlackBerry", "date": "28 Aug 2017", "question": "Some questions on algorithms, data structure, and computer security.", "answer": []}, {"key": 485, "position": "Information Security Engineer III", "company": "United Wholesale Mortgage (UWM)", "date": "25 Aug 2017", "question": "Explain your role at your previous job.", "answer": []}, {"key": 486, "position": "Information Security Engineer III", "company": "United Wholesale Mortgage (UWM)", "date": "25 Aug 2017", "question": "Whats your experience with Next Gen firewalls?", "answer": []}, {"key": 487, "position": "Security Engineer I", "company": "ReliaQuest", "date": "22 Aug 2017", "question": "Asked a lot about logs such as types and security information pertaining to those logs. Also asked about data types on siems such as what you may be monitoring with a siem. Know what CIA stands for at least.", "answer": ["CIA stands for Confidentiality, integrity and availability, which is also known as a basic tenet of cyber security and is also known as the CIA triad"]}, {"key": 488, "position": "Applications Security Engineer", "company": "Allstate", "date": "21 Aug 2017", "question": "Why do you think this is the better opportunity?", "answer": []}, {"key": 489, "position": "Applications Security Engineer", "company": "Allstate", "date": "21 Aug 2017", "question": "When you moved to U.S., tell me how was the transition and when did you move.", "answer": []}, {"key": 490, "position": "Applications Security Engineer", "company": "Allstate", "date": "21 Aug 2017", "question": "How much you are making currently and how much do you expect.", "answer": []}, {"key": 491, "position": "Applications Security Engineer", "company": "Allstate", "date": "21 Aug 2017", "question": "Why you want to commute so much for this new job?", "answer": []}, {"key": 492, "position": "Applications Security Engineer", "company": "Allstate", "date": "21 Aug 2017", "question": "Whats your employment date/year for this job 5 years back?", "answer": []}, {"key": 493, "position": "Information Security Engineer", "company": "Regeneron", "date": "14 Aug 2017", "question": "Why do you like to work here?", "answer": []}, {"key": 494, "position": "Network Security Engineer", "company": "FireMon", "date": "7 Aug 2017", "question": "About a six question quiz. It's not designed for people to get all the answers right, it's designed to see how you think. Use any resources, any, internet, phone, applications on the laptop they'll give you, etc. In general they'll give you a Linux stack trace to analyze, a regex string to create a match for (regex101. Com), how to do something in Linux (tail - F), a code chunk to define what it does, they give you raw configuration files (text based config) for a firewall and ask you to describe details of rule X, Most people get between a 10 and 20 out of 30.", "answer": ["Just did the best I knew how. This isn't a normal Network Security Engineer position, it's resolving development issues with the various firewall manufacturers including direct client problem ticketing. All, of course, build around the FireMon application."]}, {"key": 495, "position": "Security Engineer", "company": "Infolock", "date": "31 Jul 2017", "question": "They asked me what I would do, in order, if I was troubleshooting a server with networking issues.", "answer": ["I went through how I would first check to see if the network stack was running in the OS, then the physical NIC, do a packet capture at the interface, ping external hosts, etc."]}, {"key": 496, "position": "Information Security Engineer", "company": "East West Bank", "date": "24 Jul 2017", "question": "If you could design your own network from scratch, without any limitations (monetary or arbitrary management decisions-wise) besides it being secure and functional, how would you design it?", "answer": ["Draw design on board and they will ask you why you did it that way."]}, {"key": 497, "position": "Senior Cyber Security Engineer", "company": "SailPoint Technologies", "date": "18 Jul 2017", "question": "What are positive reasons that you are looking to expand your career goals?", "answer": ["Unique position &amp; stable growth building on prior experience."]}, {"key": 498, "position": "Network Security Engineer", "company": "Salesforce", "date": "17 Jul 2017", "question": "Do you watch Silicon Valley?", "answer": ["Of course! They then asked if I am a \"Tabs, or Space guy.\" The correct answer here is Tabs. I feel like I will really enjoy working here."]}, {"key": 499, "position": "Information Security Engineer", "company": "Salesforce", "date": "17 Jul 2017", "question": "What is the different between a data owner and a data custodian?", "answer": ["In this situation, the owner(s) provided the data. It was my responsibility to exercise the data, while complying with all standards and policies."]}, {"key": 500, "position": "Applications Security Engineer", "company": "Cloudflare", "date": "5 Jul 2017", "question": "Password managers & CSRF", "answer": []}, {"key": 501, "position": "Information Security Engineer", "company": "Discover", "date": "1 Jul 2017", "question": "Previous experienced", "answer": ["Gave a brief overview about my experienced."]}, {"key": 502, "position": "Staff/Senior Staff Software Engineer (Internet Security)", "company": "Palo Alto Networks", "date": "30 Jun 2017", "question": "Describe what happens when you type www,google.com?", "answer": []}, {"key": 503, "position": "Staff/Senior Staff Software Engineer (Internet Security)", "company": "Palo Alto Networks", "date": "30 Jun 2017", "question": "How do you handle multiple tasks?", "answer": []}, {"key": 504, "position": "Security Engineer", "company": "Jet", "date": "29 Jun 2017", "question": "Could you use TCP in a scenario where the only requirement is to have an unreliable connection between the two remote machines? If yes, why? If no, how would you connect the two machines without using UDP?", "answer": []}, {"key": 505, "position": "Cyber Security Engineer", "company": "Northrop Grumman", "date": "27 Jun 2017", "question": "Technical: Prior experience with cyber security tool kits (vulnerability scanning, active exploitation, etc.). Some DoD-specific defense toolkit questions. Network knowledge, protocol-specific questions on encryption. Explain network topology/infrastructure experience. Defensive security suite questions (AV, security appliances, etc.). Personality questions: How do you handle difficult co-workers/egos in the workplace. Explain moments where you've been a leader in the workforce without being asked to lead/were in a formal leadership position. Other typical behavior/personality questions.", "answer": []}, {"key": 506, "position": "Cyber Security Engineer", "company": "Jobspring Partners", "date": "19 Jun 2017", "question": "What technologies are you familiar with?", "answer": []}, {"key": 507, "position": "Cyber Security Engineer", "company": "Jobspring Partners", "date": "19 Jun 2017", "question": "How far are you willing to commute?", "answer": []}, {"key": 508, "position": "Cyber Security Engineer", "company": "Jobspring Partners", "date": "19 Jun 2017", "question": "What was your salary?", "answer": []}, {"key": 509, "position": "Security Solutions Engineer", "company": "Cisco Systems", "date": "19 Jun 2017", "question": "Tell us about your experience is network security", "answer": []}, {"key": 510, "position": "Associate Security Engineer", "company": "Check Point Software Technologies", "date": "18 Jun 2017", "question": "Was expected to do 5 minute presentation on security related topic", "answer": ["I choose one of their products, as you can imagine that could be a double edged sword but it worked for me."]}, {"key": 511, "position": "Security Engineer", "company": "Tyson Foods", "date": "13 Jun 2017", "question": "A lot of technical questions relating to the job", "answer": ["Based on the experience and education that I have."]}, {"key": 512, "position": "Security Engineer", "company": "Riot Games", "date": "7 Jun 2017", "question": "What takes place on the back-end when you put a URL in the browser. Ex: google.com", "answer": ["browser asks OS for server's IP address on port 80 or 443 if https, OS makes a DNS lookup and replies the IP address to the browser, browser opens a TCP connection to server (this step is much more complex with HTTPS), browser sends the HTTP request through TCP connection browser receives HTTP response and may close the TCP connection, or reuse it for another request, After referencing the DNS which acts as an address book of IP's the proper call is answered and displays the page after decoding and interpreting the download."]}, {"key": 513, "position": "Cyber Security Engineer", "company": "Trane", "date": "2 Jun 2017", "question": "what activities you were involved with outside of classes?", "answer": []}, {"key": 514, "position": "Network Security Engineer", "company": "Infosys", "date": "28 May 2017", "question": "In which layers cisco asa works?", "answer": []}, {"key": 515, "position": "Software Security Engineer", "company": "IBM", "date": "25 May 2017", "question": "Previous experience,", "answer": ["Answer was well documented."]}, {"key": 516, "position": "Security Sales Engineer", "company": "Corero", "date": "22 May 2017", "question": "Assuming you are qualified and become the chosen candidate are you available to travel as needed and required within the US and internationally?", "answer": ["Yes"]}, {"key": 517, "position": "Senior Network Security Engineer", "company": "Salesforce", "date": "22 May 2017", "question": "What throughput statistics on a firewall meant.", "answer": ["The load capacity of traffic entering one interface and exiting another, measured both in packets per second, bandwidth, and total concurrent sessions."]}, {"key": 518, "position": "Information Systems Security Engineer", "company": "National Security Agency", "date": "17 May 2017", "question": "Why do you want to work for the NSA?", "answer": []}, {"key": 519, "position": "Principal Security Software Engineer", "company": "Dispersive Networks", "date": "16 May 2017", "question": "Tell me about your most recent assignment.", "answer": []}, {"key": 520, "position": "Principal Security Software Engineer", "company": "Dispersive Networks", "date": "16 May 2017", "question": "What do you use to debug your code?", "answer": []}, {"key": 521, "position": "Principal Security Software Engineer", "company": "Dispersive Networks", "date": "16 May 2017", "question": "What's your experience with memory leaks?", "answer": []}, {"key": 522, "position": "Security Engineer", "company": "NerdWallet", "date": "9 May 2017", "question": "Be ready to look at code and look for security issues/root cause around a given situation", "answer": []}, {"key": 523, "position": "Security Engineer", "company": "NerdWallet", "date": "9 May 2017", "question": "Design walkthrough on a whiteboard", "answer": []}, {"key": 524, "position": "IA Security Engineer", "company": "CGI", "date": "6 May 2017", "question": "Describe for us your understanding of the three-way handshake as it is viewed in Wireshark?", "answer": ["Syn-Syn Ack-Ack"]}, {"key": 525, "position": "Security Engineer", "company": "Addepar", "date": "2 May 2017", "question": "They asked me to demonstrate app-level security skills.", "answer": ["Mostly whiteboard work and a small, live computer demo they had set up."]}, {"key": 526, "position": "Software Security Engineer", "company": "Motorola Solutions", "date": "1 May 2017", "question": "Explain EJB and its advantages, annotations (compile-level and runtime level) What all programs can run on JVM? Advantages of Java.", "answer": []}, {"key": 527, "position": "Software Security Engineer", "company": "Motorola Solutions", "date": "1 May 2017", "question": "Different ways to reverse a string, find best day to buy and sell stocks if values are present in each index of the array. Different data structures used at diff. scenarios. REST API related questions.", "answer": []}, {"key": 528, "position": "Software Security Engineer", "company": "Motorola Solutions", "date": "1 May 2017", "question": "Various Security Related questions, Key management, Cloud Scale up, Design Application with Security in mind, Hashing and Encryption difference. Docker related questions", "answer": []}, {"key": 529, "position": "Information Security Engineer", "company": "Jet", "date": "28 Apr 2017", "question": "What was one time where you went above and beyond what was asked of you?", "answer": []}, {"key": 530, "position": "Security Engineer", "company": "HubSpot", "date": "25 Apr 2017", "question": "Break out the flow of a typical SSL exchange through each negotiation request and response.", "answer": []}, {"key": 531, "position": "Network Security Engineer", "company": "AM", "date": "25 Apr 2017", "question": "I had two rounds of interviews that were from easy to more in depth.", "answer": []}, {"key": 532, "position": "Cloud Support Engineer - Security", "company": "Amazon", "date": "24 Apr 2017", "question": "What are the differences between encryption, hashing and encoding and describe each process in detail.", "answer": ["Symmetric encryption: Both communicating parties will need a copy of the same key to decrypt and encrypt data. Asymmetric encryption (Public/Private key): Both parties will need each others public key. An encrypted message which is encrypted with a public key, can only be decrypted with each users private key which is kept hidden. The problem with this initial key exchange is that before the two parties exchange keys, they cannot communicate securely. This introduces the problem of a Man-In-The-Middle attack. Hashing is irreversible where as encryption is reversible. MD5 and SHA-1 are fairly common hashing types but are no longer considered secure. SHA-256 is considered much stronger. A salt which appends a random value to a password before it is hashed can be used to prevent having the same hashes in a database if two users happen to use the same password. This makes it more difficult to carry out dictionary or rainbow table attacks. Encoding converts data to a common form to be transferred over a medium in order to protect the integrity of the data."]}, {"key": 533, "position": "Platform Security Engineer", "company": "Mapbox", "date": "23 Apr 2017", "question": "How do you work with other teams?", "answer": []}, {"key": 534, "position": "Security Engineer", "company": "Amazon", "date": "21 Apr 2017", "question": "Involved coding questions as well.", "answer": ["what type of coding question ?"]}, {"key": 535, "position": "Network Security Engineer", "company": "Cisco Systems", "date": "18 Apr 2017", "question": "How would you filter xyz in wireshark", "answer": []}, {"key": 536, "position": "Security Engineer", "company": "WePay", "date": "17 Apr 2017", "question": "HackerRank challenge", "answer": []}, {"key": 537, "position": "Cyber Security Engineer", "company": "MITRE", "date": "15 Apr 2017", "question": "If you had the resources and authority, what would you do to improve Defensive Cyber Operations?", "answer": []}, {"key": 538, "position": "Senior Information Security Engineer", "company": "SWIFT", "date": "12 Apr 2017", "question": "Risk Management, Cloud and Security Development", "answer": []}, {"key": 539, "position": "Senior Information Security Engineer", "company": "SWIFT", "date": "12 Apr 2017", "question": "Salary, they were 30K off a normal DC salary for a Security Professional but had great benefits. Maybe a good for a Junior level venturing into their first Senior Level position", "answer": ["The salary was too low to consider the company. They wont attract top talent."]}, {"key": 540, "position": "Security Engineer", "company": "Palo Alto Research Center", "date": "8 Apr 2017", "question": "Why do you want to work for Xerox Parc ?", "answer": ["Xerox invented laser printers and ethernet. good enough for me"]}, {"key": 541, "position": "Security Engineer", "company": "Uber", "date": "8 Apr 2017", "question": "Questions on nmap -ss and nmap -st", "answer": ["Can you tell me what was your coding question?"]}, {"key": 542, "position": "Security Engineer", "company": "Red Balloon Security", "date": "4 Apr 2017", "question": "The first round i was given a steganography image second round i was given a ip based phone to decrypt message in it", "answer": []}, {"key": 543, "position": "Security Engineer", "company": "Red Balloon Security", "date": "4 Apr 2017", "question": "first round they sent me a steganography image and after decrypting it they sent me a ip based phone to my mailing address and asked me to decrypt the message in the phone", "answer": []}, {"key": 544, "position": "Security Engineer", "company": "Red Balloon Security", "date": "4 Apr 2017", "question": "1st round they sent me steganography image. after decrypting the image . the second round they sent me a ip based phone to my mailing address and asked me to decrypt the message in it.", "answer": []}, {"key": 545, "position": "Help Desk/Security Analyst/.NET Developer", "company": "Clayton Homes", "date": "31 Mar 2017", "question": "What do you know about Clayton Tell me about yourself What are your interests", "answer": []}, {"key": 546, "position": "Network Security Engineer", "company": "FireMon", "date": "29 Mar 2017", "question": "analyze stack trace and describe what happened", "answer": []}, {"key": 547, "position": "Network Security Engineer", "company": "FireMon", "date": "29 Mar 2017", "question": "analyze obscure configuration file and describe what it does", "answer": []}, {"key": 548, "position": "Security Engineer", "company": "Paxos", "date": "24 Mar 2017", "question": "Should we encrypt data at rest?", "answer": []}, {"key": 549, "position": "Security Engineer", "company": "Paxos", "date": "24 Mar 2017", "question": "Our DB was stolen/exfiltrated. It was secured with one round of sha256 with a static salt. What do we do now? Are we at risk? What do we change?", "answer": []}, {"key": 550, "position": "Security Engineer", "company": "Paxos", "date": "24 Mar 2017", "question": "How do I authenticate you and know you sent the message?", "answer": ["HMAC auth is the answer."]}, {"key": 551, "position": "Security Engineer", "company": "Paxos", "date": "24 Mar 2017", "question": "print out the first 25 odd numbers in any language.", "answer": []}, {"key": 552, "position": "Lead Solutions Engineer - Security Specialist", "company": "Salesforce", "date": "22 Mar 2017", "question": "Whiteboard a security concept and provide an explanation.", "answer": []}, {"key": 553, "position": "Information Security Engineer", "company": "Informatica", "date": "15 Mar 2017", "question": "What type of security programming languages do you prefer to use?", "answer": ["Python"]}, {"key": 554, "position": "Network Security Engineer", "company": "Hewlett Packard Enterprise | HPE", "date": "8 Mar 2017", "question": "Describe the OSI Model.", "answer": []}, {"key": 555, "position": "Security Engineer", "company": "Amazon", "date": "8 Mar 2017", "question": "General behavioral and project questions.", "answer": []}, {"key": 556, "position": "Cloud Security Engineer", "company": "Whole Foods Market", "date": "2 Mar 2017", "question": "Why did you apply for this role?", "answer": []}, {"key": 557, "position": "Security Operations Center Engineer", "company": "Joyent", "date": "2 Mar 2017", "question": "How does SSL work? How do web certificates for HTTPS work?", "answer": ["After the secure connection is made, the session key is used to encrypt all transmitted data. Browser connects to a web server (website) secured with SSL (https). ... Server sends a copy of its SSL Certificate, including the server's public key."]}, {"key": 558, "position": "Senior Security Engineer", "company": "Groupon", "date": "23 Feb 2017", "question": "Why would you be a good fit for Groupon and other basic experience based questions.", "answer": []}, {"key": 559, "position": "Senior Information Security Engineer", "company": "Ntrepid", "date": "21 Feb 2017", "question": "I was asked a variety of scenario based questions that I believe were aimed at getting some insight into my thought process. There were several components to the interview questions including technical, management, and leadership style questions.", "answer": ["I answered the questions based on how my experience applied to the situation and what I thought the best course of action was."]}, {"key": 560, "position": "Principal Security Engineer", "company": "Alert Logic", "date": "13 Feb 2017", "question": "Why have you moved around so much between jobs", "answer": ["Throughout my career like all of us recruiters all call and emailing continuously. While ignoring most, occasionally one has an interesting role description. The new &amp; interesting work combined with the incumbent company's lack of vision to take security beyond the basics causes me to jump. It's about interesting work, not more money or lack of company loyalty."]}, {"key": 561, "position": "Principal Security Engineer", "company": "Alert Logic", "date": "13 Feb 2017", "question": "It isn't a question; more so he brought down a game called Master Mind and makes you run through case conditions for logic and determining patterns.", "answer": []}, {"key": 562, "position": "Principal Security Engineer", "company": "Alert Logic", "date": "13 Feb 2017", "question": "What do you think of the new Alert Logic?", "answer": []}, {"key": 563, "position": "Network Security Engineer", "company": "CyberNSecurity Solutions", "date": "10 Feb 2017", "question": "Interview was hard and asking lot of question based security", "answer": ["I did not do well ."]}, {"key": 564, "position": "Information Security Engineer", "company": "Spectrum Health", "date": "10 Feb 2017", "question": "I was asked about my education and any internships that might help in the role", "answer": []}, {"key": 565, "position": "Information Security Engineer", "company": "Spectrum Health", "date": "10 Feb 2017", "question": "I was asked about current industry certifications", "answer": []}, {"key": 566, "position": "Information Security Engineer", "company": "Spectrum Health", "date": "10 Feb 2017", "question": "I was asked about HIPAA security and the difference between required and addressable components.", "answer": []}, {"key": 567, "position": "Information Security Engineer", "company": "Spectrum Health", "date": "10 Feb 2017", "question": "In the technical interview I was presented with a network diagram and asked to walk through it - describe the flow of data, the roles of various pieces if equipment and a determination of how it might be improved upon for a set of given circumstances", "answer": []}, {"key": 568, "position": "Security Engineer", "company": "D. E. Shaw & Co. - Investment Firm", "date": "9 Feb 2017", "question": "Do you know python? Diff btw that and bash shell.", "answer": ["Describe perfect forward secrecy."]}, {"key": 569, "position": "Security Engineer", "company": "D. E. Shaw & Co. - Investment Firm", "date": "9 Feb 2017", "question": "How would you install DLP hardware for email?", "answer": []}, {"key": 570, "position": "Security Engineer", "company": "D. E. Shaw & Co. - Investment Firm", "date": "9 Feb 2017", "question": "Public and private key vs symmetric encryption?", "answer": ["Is there a difference between a stack smack and heap attack?"]}, {"key": 571, "position": "Security Engineer", "company": "D. E. Shaw & Co. - Investment Firm", "date": "9 Feb 2017", "question": "How does Kerberos work?", "answer": ["How would you build a botnet?"]}, {"key": 572, "position": "Security Engineer", "company": "D. E. Shaw & Co. - Investment Firm", "date": "9 Feb 2017", "question": "What do you do if a user brings you a pc that is acting 'weird'? You suspect malware.", "answer": ["How to share a secret over the public internet?"]}, {"key": 573, "position": "Security Engineer", "company": "Securonix", "date": "7 Feb 2017", "question": "General profile based questions and some basic java questions", "answer": []}, {"key": 574, "position": "Senior Cyber Security Engineer", "company": "Forcepoint", "date": "4 Feb 2017", "question": "Would I be willing to relocate to", "answer": ["No"]}, {"key": 575, "position": "Cyber Security Engineer", "company": "Booz Allen Hamilton", "date": "30 Jan 2017", "question": "Describe the Risk Management Framework process and a project where you successfully implemented compliance with RMF.", "answer": []}, {"key": 576, "position": "Security Software Engineer", "company": "Yahoo", "date": "18 Jan 2017", "question": "BST traversal", "answer": ["Binary Search Traversal has three types, preorder (root-&gt;left subtree-&gt;right subtree). Inorder (left subtree-&gt;root-&gt;right subtree), and Postorder (left-&gt;right-&gt;root)"]}, {"key": 577, "position": "Cyber Security Engineer", "company": "Robert Half", "date": "18 Jan 2017", "question": "Standard personality type questions, how do you handle a difficult co-worker, etc.", "answer": []}, {"key": 578, "position": "Applications Security Engineer", "company": "balena", "date": "17 Jan 2017", "question": "Very basic stuff What is authentication vs Authorization Name spaces OAuth Threat modelling", "answer": []}, {"key": 579, "position": "Cyber Security Engineer", "company": "Taranet", "date": "17 Jan 2017", "question": "Technical questions about your experience and what type of work you did. What certifications are currently held. What goals you have.", "answer": []}, {"key": 580, "position": "IT Security Engineer", "company": "Xerox", "date": "9 Jan 2017", "question": "basic networking and windows, linux , internet , DNS, DHCP , Troubleshooting skills then go deep on mcafee products like anti virus and more on security basics and the difference between different kind of threats.", "answer": ["review the basic of the above skills"]}, {"key": 581, "position": "Security Engineer", "company": "Uber", "date": "1 Jan 2017", "question": "Describe your past experiences", "answer": ["I was wondering what was asked in the third coding round? Can you please share those details. How was the third interview structured?"]}, {"key": 582, "position": "Security Engineer", "company": "Uber", "date": "1 Jan 2017", "question": "Why are you interested in working at Uber?", "answer": ["Can you tell me what was your coding question?"]}, {"key": 583, "position": "Information Security Engineer", "company": "CACI International", "date": "26 Dec 2016", "question": "years of experience and experiential questions based on software used and scenarios", "answer": ["as accurately as possible"]}, {"key": 584, "position": "Security Engineer", "company": "Cisco Systems", "date": "22 Dec 2016", "question": "How do I adapt to change?", "answer": ["I love change! As long as it keep things interesting!"]}, {"key": 585, "position": "Security Engineer, Compliance Analyst", "company": "Facebook", "date": "10 Dec 2016", "question": "Some more business security related questions.", "answer": []}, {"key": 586, "position": "Security Engineer, Compliance Analyst", "company": "Facebook", "date": "10 Dec 2016", "question": "Brain teaser asking how to send a box with a diamond it in all the way across the country if the send and receiver have different keys.", "answer": ["Assuming you have two locks and only the key for one while the person across the country has the other, you could lock the diamond with the lock for which you have the key. Then enclose that box in another container which you lock for which you don't have the key (which the individual at the destination holds). When the box arrives at the destination, the individual with the key can unlock the first box, find the key for the enclosed box, open it and have the diamond. Shortcomings here are that you lose your key and are then incapable of using this system again for the next transfer unless you keep copies or the key is returned by the receiver."]}, {"key": 587, "position": "Security Engineer, Compliance Analyst", "company": "Facebook", "date": "10 Dec 2016", "question": "How'd you end up here talking to me today? (10 minute answer first given by manager then my turn)", "answer": []}, {"key": 588, "position": "Security Engineer, Compliance Analyst", "company": "Facebook", "date": "10 Dec 2016", "question": "What are the 6 aggregate functions of SQL?", "answer": ["MIN, MAX, SUM, COUNT (Total Values of a Column), AVG, COUNT(*) (Number of Rows in a Table)."]}, {"key": 589, "position": "Information Security Engineer", "company": "InteliSecure", "date": "7 Dec 2016", "question": "Describe your Experience, Describe your accomplishments, describe your weaknesses, where do you see your self in a few years?", "answer": []}, {"key": 590, "position": "Security Engineer", "company": "Booz Allen Hamilton", "date": "5 Dec 2016", "question": "What type of work environment would you dislike and why?", "answer": []}, {"key": 591, "position": "SOC Security Engineer", "company": "Las Vegas Sands", "date": "5 Dec 2016", "question": "What is a DDOS attack?", "answer": ["I described a DDOS attack."]}, {"key": 592, "position": "Security Engineer", "company": "Salesforce", "date": "1 Dec 2016", "question": "Open ended threat modeling questions.", "answer": []}, {"key": 593, "position": "Information Security Engineer", "company": "Mondo", "date": "30 Nov 2016", "question": "What kind of security frameworks have you had to adhere to in the past.", "answer": []}, {"key": 594, "position": "Information Security Engineer", "company": "NJVC", "date": "29 Nov 2016", "question": "How are you working in a team environment?", "answer": ["I have worked within a team environment all my life, I function better when I am a part of a team."]}, {"key": 595, "position": "Applications Security Engineer", "company": "DMI", "date": "28 Nov 2016", "question": "How do you deal with a constant negative person?", "answer": []}, {"key": 596, "position": "Security Engineer", "company": "Steampunk", "date": "21 Nov 2016", "question": "Name a difficult situation you ran into and how did you overcome it?", "answer": []}, {"key": 597, "position": "Information Security Engineer", "company": "Palantir Technologies", "date": "17 Nov 2016", "question": "Walk through a whiteboard scenario for your environment of choice (Win/Linux) in which compromising the network is the goal without use of social engineering techniques (phishing for credential harvesting, etc).", "answer": []}, {"key": 598, "position": "Security Engineer", "company": "Microsoft", "date": "16 Nov 2016", "question": "1. They asked me about pen-testing and tools used to perform pen tests. 2. They asked me to whiteboard my current projects and come up with security flaws in design. 3. They asked me OWASP and what I think was the most prominent vulnerability? 4. They asked if I had prior experience in working in security and have played CTFs. 5. Behavioral questions like what kind of team would you like to work in?", "answer": []}, {"key": 599, "position": "Senior Network Security Engineer", "company": "Verizon", "date": "15 Nov 2016", "question": "What were some of things you've accomplished at your previous company?", "answer": []}, {"key": 600, "position": "Security Engineer", "company": "Amazon", "date": "14 Nov 2016", "question": "Scenario based questions. \"How would you exploit a system with these protections applied?\"", "answer": []}, {"key": 601, "position": "Information Security Engineer", "company": "OHSU", "date": "13 Nov 2016", "question": "What is our mission statement? How would you handle a non-solvable conflict? If left alone in office with access to a computer, how would you exploit it? What is Change Management? Describe HTTPs and how it is used? What is the difference between HTTPS and SSL? Tell us about yourself? How do you handle conflicts? What is your opinion on the various past viruses and why? How do you harden a system? How to you elevate permissions?", "answer": []}, {"key": 602, "position": "Security Engineer", "company": "iHeartMedia", "date": "7 Nov 2016", "question": "1 team member for the position asked for me to describe the OSI model. Another team member for the position asked about Linux administration/monitoring and ways to update packages.", "answer": ["I gave a very brief overview of OSI layers and discussed the topic. I discussed specific commands in order to review running processes in linux distributions. I also discussed how a number of various update and installation packages can be leveraged in the linux CLI."]}, {"key": 603, "position": "Principal Security Engineer", "company": "ResMed", "date": "3 Nov 2016", "question": "Who wrote this book about TDD? (lol) What's the difference between a Principal and Sr Engineer? Other completely open ended questions about how would you secure these 2 systems, when tried to gather more information about the question, devs responded we are the ones interviewing with you, only we ask questions.", "answer": []}, {"key": 604, "position": "Cyber Security Engineer", "company": "Booz Allen Hamilton", "date": "2 Nov 2016", "question": "questions regarding the RMF process which is fairly new to the Department of Defense which had been DIACAP focused.", "answer": []}, {"key": 605, "position": "Junior Security Engineer", "company": "The MIL Corporation", "date": "31 Oct 2016", "question": "Have you used any penetration testing tools", "answer": ["No but i used penetration testing tools as kali linux or backtrack"]}, {"key": 606, "position": "Senior Applications Security Engineer", "company": "Netflix", "date": "25 Oct 2016", "question": "Scale..", "answer": []}, {"key": 607, "position": "Senior Network Security Engineer", "company": "Salesforce", "date": "23 Oct 2016", "question": "Difference between IPS and IDS", "answer": ["Again, this is a question you would see in a Network Security 101 class. Had to embarrass myself and answer this question."]}, {"key": 608, "position": "Senior Network Security Engineer", "company": "Salesforce", "date": "23 Oct 2016", "question": "Difference between public and private key", "answer": ["Is this something you ask a candidate for a senior network security position ? I answered it in the most simplest terms so that the interviewer could understand."]}, {"key": 609, "position": "Security Engineer", "company": "ComEd", "date": "18 Oct 2016", "question": "Nothing technical all about how I fit in team dynamics", "answer": ["personally"]}, {"key": 610, "position": "Security Engineer", "company": "F5", "date": "11 Oct 2016", "question": "If you had to compress something and encrypt it, which would you do first and why?", "answer": ["Compress first, then encrypt, or you'll end up with a file larger than you started with. Then talked about how compression algorithms / encryption inherently work. He wasn't listening to my answer, so I guess it didn't matter.", "Encrypt before compression, if you are forced to pick one or the other. Compressing after encryption is virtually pointless for data size but compressing before encryption leads to compression oracle attacks like seen in CRIME and BREACH."]}, {"key": 611, "position": "Security Engineer", "company": "Viasat", "date": "10 Oct 2016", "question": "Compliance process, network knowledge, pentesting knowledge.", "answer": []}, {"key": 612, "position": "Network Security Engineer", "company": "Cummins-Allison", "date": "6 Oct 2016", "question": "Tech specific questions, nothing to hard. the current network is very dated.", "answer": ["Simple short responses to questions asked gave insight to known vulnerabilities etc."]}, {"key": 613, "position": "IT Security Engineer", "company": "Arrow Electronics", "date": "4 Oct 2016", "question": "How will you make your network secure?", "answer": []}, {"key": 614, "position": "IT Security Engineer", "company": "Arrow Electronics", "date": "4 Oct 2016", "question": "What about yourself are you most proud of?", "answer": []}, {"key": 615, "position": "Senior Engineer, IoT Security", "company": "InterDigital", "date": "2 Oct 2016", "question": "Define security concepts, such as difference between encoding and encryption, purpose of TLS.", "answer": []}, {"key": 616, "position": "Senior Engineer, IoT Security", "company": "InterDigital", "date": "2 Oct 2016", "question": "Describe achievements in past job.", "answer": []}, {"key": 617, "position": "Senior Engineer, IoT Security", "company": "InterDigital", "date": "2 Oct 2016", "question": "Describe projects on which you have worked.", "answer": []}, {"key": 618, "position": "Senior Cyber Security Engineer", "company": "MITRE", "date": "1 Oct 2016", "question": "Number of years in industry", "answer": ["relative to experience in that point in time"]}, {"key": 619, "position": "Senior Cyber Security Engineer", "company": "VMD Corp", "date": "30 Sep 2016", "question": "How would I develop a knowledge management process/program. He inquired about my specific tool experience (Nexpose, Nessus, HP Fortify/WebInspect)", "answer": ["I laid out how I used the tools and why, which confirmed my knowledge of what the tool is, does, and is used."]}, {"key": 620, "position": "Information Security Engineer", "company": "Palantir Technologies", "date": "28 Sep 2016", "question": "I signed an NDA.", "answer": []}, {"key": 621, "position": "Senior Information Security Engineer", "company": "COMPASS Cyber Security", "date": "27 Sep 2016", "question": "Typical tech questions, but there was a focus more on my background, my community involvement; essentially who I was and how I could fit within COMPASS.", "answer": []}, {"key": 622, "position": "Information Systems Security Engineer", "company": "New Directions Technologies", "date": "26 Sep 2016", "question": "Do you understand that the Information System Security Engineer position is not a hands on technical position but one more of an auditor and that there would be a lot of documentation to support the customer security accreditation requirements?", "answer": ["Having served in the military, in another branch, for many years as a supervisor/manager and just recently completed a Masters degree in Cyber Security I am very used to gathering information and writing reports."]}, {"key": 623, "position": "Principal Information Security Engineer", "company": "ManTech", "date": "24 Sep 2016", "question": "Availability timeframe.", "answer": []}, {"key": 624, "position": "Junior Security Engineer", "company": "Homesite Group Incorporated", "date": "21 Sep 2016", "question": "How are your skills in coding and scripting?", "answer": ["Why Homesite Insurance?"]}, {"key": 625, "position": "Information Security Engineer", "company": "Twitch", "date": "12 Sep 2016", "question": "Typical \"think like an attacker for a moment...\" questions. Then the inverse, \"how would you detect unknown attacker activity.\" How to secure a web app; different web app vulnerabilities.", "answer": []}, {"key": 626, "position": "Senior Security Engineer", "company": "IntellecTechs", "date": "10 Sep 2016", "question": "Describe the security technologies you have hands on experience with?", "answer": []}, {"key": 627, "position": "Security Integration Engineer", "company": "Collabera", "date": "9 Sep 2016", "question": "When an ASA bundle as part of failover-only bundle how often does it reboot when the mate is not attached.", "answer": ["Once every 24 hours."]}, {"key": 628, "position": "Web Applications Security Engineer", "company": "Blizzard Entertainment", "date": "3 Sep 2016", "question": "Why are you leaving your current employer?", "answer": []}, {"key": 629, "position": "Web Applications Security Engineer", "company": "Blizzard Entertainment", "date": "3 Sep 2016", "question": "Why do you want to work specifically at Blizzard?", "answer": []}, {"key": 630, "position": "Web Applications Security Engineer", "company": "Blizzard Entertainment", "date": "3 Sep 2016", "question": "Do you know what XXE is?", "answer": ["XXE - XML External Entities vulnerability, it is a type of injection attack that occurs when an XML parser has the external entities DTD allowed for usage and does not properly parse the input given to it. As a result, an attacker can potentially inject malicious code to read files from the local system, perform other remote execution, and potentially expand to a DOS attack by using XML external entities expansion styled attack. To prevent XXE, if possible, try to disable external entities all together."]}, {"key": 631, "position": "Web Applications Security Engineer", "company": "Blizzard Entertainment", "date": "3 Sep 2016", "question": "Do you know what SSRF is?", "answer": ["Server side request forgery- an attack"]}, {"key": 632, "position": "Software Security Engineer", "company": "Rapid7", "date": "2 Sep 2016", "question": "Create a linked list in java that supported add and remove. Numbers are added in ascending order, so if the list was 1,3,5 and 4 was added it would look like 1,3,4,5.", "answer": ["Wrote out the code on the white board, almost had it perfect but would sometimes not work for certain inputs."]}, {"key": 633, "position": "Associate Information Security Engineer", "company": "Federal Reserve Bank of Chicago", "date": "31 Aug 2016", "question": "How would you handle a computer on your network being infected (general ideas not tech nitty gritty)", "answer": []}, {"key": 634, "position": "Security Engineer", "company": "PPL", "date": "31 Aug 2016", "question": "how well I knew Juniper firewalls from my previous positions.", "answer": []}, {"key": 635, "position": "Security Engineer", "company": "Citrix", "date": "26 Aug 2016", "question": "Describe different authentication mechanisms used in practice and detail the differences among the ones you select.", "answer": []}, {"key": 636, "position": "Security Assurance Engineer", "company": "FactSet", "date": "20 Aug 2016", "question": "For an application security position, they asked questions about the OWASP Top 10 and some secure design questions for software systems.", "answer": ["Gave how to test for the asked vulnerabilities, and how to resolve them. For the secure design questions, it was more open ended and they wanted to see how I would think through the steps in architecting a secure solution to various problems."]}, {"key": 637, "position": "Senior Information Security Engineer", "company": "TenFour", "date": "18 Aug 2016", "question": "experience", "answer": ["truthfully"]}, {"key": 638, "position": "Security Systems Software Engineer", "company": "Qualcomm", "date": "13 Aug 2016", "question": "Given a sorted array that can have both negative and positive integers, write an algorithm to sort the array of the squares of the integers. Optimize it.", "answer": []}, {"key": 639, "position": "Security Engineer", "company": "STONE Resource Group", "date": "9 Aug 2016", "question": "What is the process in which you add a certificate to an ASA?", "answer": ["Create a CSR, submit it to the Certificate Authority, then import the assigned certificate to the ASA and assign it to the specific roles in the ASA"]}, {"key": 640, "position": "Security Engineer", "company": "Check Point Software Technologies", "date": "8 Aug 2016", "question": "Describe policy creation, installation, management, log research and troubleshooting.", "answer": ["Will require a working knowledge of security and firewall fundamentals."]}, {"key": 641, "position": "Senior Cyber Security Engineer", "company": "Booz Allen Hamilton", "date": "7 Aug 2016", "question": "What CND tools do you knowledge or experience with?", "answer": []}, {"key": 642, "position": "Information Security Engineer", "company": "Netspend", "date": "5 Aug 2016", "question": "If you're going to compress and encrypt a file, which do you do first and why?", "answer": ["Compress and then encrypt, because encrypted files are not compressible."]}, {"key": 643, "position": "Security Engineer", "company": "Deloitte", "date": "4 Aug 2016", "question": "Anything regarding the role", "answer": []}, {"key": 644, "position": "Senior Cloud Security Engineer", "company": "Hilton", "date": "4 Aug 2016", "question": "Describe your experience as it relates to security in AWS?", "answer": []}, {"key": 645, "position": "Security Engineer", "company": "G2 Inc.", "date": "25 Jul 2016", "question": "Rate seven traits on from the most important to the least important and explain why. (Traits included Teamwork, Integrity, Curiosity, etc)", "answer": ["Being prior military, I was taught to always put integrity first."]}, {"key": 646, "position": "Security Engineer", "company": "Northrop Grumman", "date": "24 Jul 2016", "question": "What was your biggest struggle with network security and what was your fix action.", "answer": ["Unknown bug in network, developed a software tool to read over the pages of script logs."]}, {"key": 647, "position": "Information Security Engineer", "company": "Google", "date": "20 Jul 2016", "question": "Why system stack is not implemented in reverse order ?", "answer": []}, {"key": 648, "position": "Security Engineer", "company": "UnifyID", "date": "15 Jul 2016", "question": "Asked to design a public key infrastructure control flow in as much detail as possible.", "answer": ["Very very long conversation ensued, definitely interesting."]}, {"key": 649, "position": "EMS Cyber Security Engineer", "company": "El Paso Electric", "date": "6 Jul 2016", "question": "Why should we hire you , why El Paso Electric ? Witch cyber security systems do you know ? What was your last big challenge ? How would your co-workers describe your personality ?", "answer": []}, {"key": 650, "position": "Security Engineer", "company": "Google", "date": "4 Jul 2016", "question": "During lunch, I was asked about my career goals and how they fit with Google.", "answer": []}, {"key": 651, "position": "Security Engineer", "company": "Amazon", "date": "1 Jul 2016", "question": "Name a time when you had to deal with a difficult person, how did you resolve the issue?", "answer": []}, {"key": 652, "position": "Senior IT Security Engineer", "company": "Qualcomm", "date": "29 Jun 2016", "question": "How would you work in a team environment with a difficult co worker.", "answer": []}, {"key": 653, "position": "Information Security Engineer", "company": "Zapata Technology", "date": "27 Jun 2016", "question": "Have you worked with the team or the validator before?", "answer": []}, {"key": 654, "position": "Security Engineer", "company": "NCC Group", "date": "25 Jun 2016", "question": "None, it was a various security based challenge questions when they give you a USB stick or something and you have to complete levels (check on their site)", "answer": ["I didn't"]}, {"key": 655, "position": "Senior Embedded Software Engineer - Go!Control Security Systems", "company": "Nortek", "date": "22 Jun 2016", "question": "Using C++ code, write a function to calculate the sum of a vector of integers using N threads in parallel.", "answer": ["Wrote code to perform the task"]}, {"key": 656, "position": "Senior Embedded Software Engineer - Go!Control Security Systems", "company": "Nortek", "date": "22 Jun 2016", "question": "Using C++ code, write a linked list insertion method.", "answer": ["Wrote code to perform the task"]}, {"key": 657, "position": "Senior Embedded Software Engineer - Go!Control Security Systems", "company": "Nortek", "date": "22 Jun 2016", "question": "Using C code write a routine to find a 32 bit frame start sequence in a raw byte stream buffer.", "answer": ["Wrote code to perform the task taking care to understand byte alignment issues.", "Let buf be the buffer, BUF_SIZE be it's size, ref_frame be the reference frame int i = 0, j = 0; while(i"]}, {"key": 658, "position": "LLVM Security Tools Engineer", "company": "Qualcomm", "date": "14 Jun 2016", "question": "Describing few well-known security vulnerabilities Had to find the bugs present in the code", "answer": ["Talked about buffer overflows, syn flooding, vulnerabilities in Android Answered the possible output of the code correctly but failed to describe the cause."]}, {"key": 659, "position": "Associate Information Security Engineer", "company": "MorphoTrust USA", "date": "5 Jun 2016", "question": "Describe your approach to problem-solving.", "answer": []}, {"key": 660, "position": "Network Security Engineer", "company": "Atos", "date": "29 May 2016", "question": "I was asked no hard questions, mainly scenario based. When I did receive a complicated situation, the interviewer did not seem overly friendly nor someone with whom I would want to work.", "answer": []}, {"key": 661, "position": "Software Engineer- Security", "company": "A10 Networks", "date": "23 May 2016", "question": "For the face to face interview, be prepared to be grilled on your basics. Relating to socket programming, TCP/IP concepts, security actions you would take in certain scenarios and firewalls.", "answer": ["Thank you for taking the time to interview wtih A10 Networks and all of your great feedback!"]}, {"key": 662, "position": "Network Security - Incident Engineer", "company": "Insight Global", "date": "10 May 2016", "question": "Technical questions pertaining to the job. straight forward, real life questions. you either know what you are talking about or you don't.", "answer": ["to the best of my knowledge and the promise to research what I did not know."]}, {"key": 663, "position": "Engineer Software and Network Security", "company": "Palo Alto Networks", "date": "4 May 2016", "question": "Pointer in C and memory location etc.", "answer": []}, {"key": 664, "position": "Cloud Security Engineer", "company": "Twilio", "date": "25 Apr 2016", "question": "Basics on python", "answer": ["Read online aws python related scripts"]}, {"key": 665, "position": "Cloud Security Engineer", "company": "Twilio", "date": "25 Apr 2016", "question": "Basic questions on aws cloud security", "answer": ["Just read whitepapers on aws security"]}, {"key": 666, "position": "Security Engineer", "company": "Atlassian", "date": "6 Apr 2016", "question": "Code reviews of Java, Python, JS code and finding the vulnerabilities in the code.. If you know the common security problems in software you will have no problems with the reviews. Some were a bit more tricky but still nothing to difficult.", "answer": []}, {"key": 667, "position": "Network Security Engineer", "company": "Puget Sound Energy", "date": "6 Apr 2016", "question": "How would you design our network?", "answer": ["Used the white board to outline what the high level network might look like."]}, {"key": 668, "position": "Senior Network/Security Engineer", "company": "Oxnard", "date": "6 Apr 2016", "question": "Explain policy (refused to explain if this involves cyber security, Active Directory, firewalls, ...).", "answer": ["I provided answers for cyber security, Active Directory, firewalls, ..."]}, {"key": 669, "position": "Information Security Engineer", "company": "Cengage Group", "date": "5 Apr 2016", "question": "Entire setup and configuration process for a web application on cloud and all security measures to protect it. Use of tools like Burpsuite, Qualys, Splunk. Knowledge and understanding of cloud environment.", "answer": []}, {"key": 670, "position": "Cyber Security Engineer", "company": "MITRE", "date": "31 Mar 2016", "question": "There were very few technical questions and no coding questions at all.", "answer": []}, {"key": 671, "position": "Senior Applications Security Engineer", "company": "Etsy", "date": "28 Mar 2016", "question": "Can you computer?", "answer": ["Yes, of course I can."]}, {"key": 672, "position": "Network Security Engineer", "company": "Zions Bancorporation", "date": "24 Mar 2016", "question": "How do you handle a situation where you have multiple tasks to complete at the same time?", "answer": ["I see if there are any high priority tasks first. I then check all tasks to see if there are any that can be worked faster than the others. Finally I will work all tasks in the order they are received"]}, {"key": 673, "position": "Security Engineer", "company": "MassMutual", "date": "23 Mar 2016", "question": "What is XSS? How to prevent it. How do you configure wireshark? questions from resume", "answer": []}, {"key": 674, "position": "Security Engineer", "company": "Eventbrite", "date": "21 Mar 2016", "question": "Whiteboard the different security problems with the given code. A printed page of code was given and I was asked to find all the vulnerabilities in the code.", "answer": []}, {"key": 675, "position": "Applications Security Engineer", "company": "CA Technologies", "date": "17 Mar 2016", "question": "What's the shortest amount of time that you've seen between code submission and production? How would you implement security in our development cycle? What tools do you use?", "answer": []}, {"key": 676, "position": "Network Security Engineer", "company": "Cyberoam Technologies", "date": "9 Mar 2016", "question": "More related to security question . Firewall,Rule and NAT rule related. VPN", "answer": ["Answer"]}, {"key": 677, "position": "Senior Security Engineer", "company": "PlayStation", "date": "28 Feb 2016", "question": "Networking, Linux configuration and Security.", "answer": []}, {"key": 678, "position": "Cyber Security Engineer - Exercise Developer", "company": "Software Engineering Institute", "date": "25 Feb 2016", "question": "Describe your technical background. What additional technical training would you like to pursue, if given the opportunity?", "answer": []}, {"key": 679, "position": "Cyber Security Engineer", "company": "Sierra Nevada Corporation", "date": "21 Feb 2016", "question": "How did your project management experience help you as a technical SME and vice versa?", "answer": []}, {"key": 680, "position": "Information Security Engineer", "company": "Booz Allen Hamilton", "date": "17 Feb 2016", "question": "What are you doing in your current role?", "answer": ["I made sure to answer this at a high level but sprinkled with specific details. I always make sure to use power words when I am answering a question like this. I believe the use of power words will make the interviewer remember you more and be able to retain the information you tell them better. This gives you a better chance at getting the job because they can relay what you said easier to the hiring manager (if it isn't them themselves)."]}, {"key": 681, "position": "Information Security Engineer", "company": "Intercontinental Exchange", "date": "8 Feb 2016", "question": "why do you think you are qualified for this job. Why do you choose our company", "answer": []}, {"key": 682, "position": "Information Security Engineer", "company": "ZeniMax Media", "date": "8 Feb 2016", "question": "Few technical questions, more about process and get to know you questions.", "answer": ["Answered with the best respectful but laid back attitude possible."]}, {"key": 683, "position": "Security Engineer", "company": "Verizon", "date": "30 Jan 2016", "question": "Explain the difference between TCP and UDP. Which is more secure? Why? What is the TCP three way handshake? What is process 1 in Unix/Linux? (init) why is it 1? It is the parent of all processes. What are the steps to compile a program using GNU make? README, read configure check it for needed adjustments. ./configure, make, make install, make clean.", "answer": ["Provided above"]}, {"key": 684, "position": "Network Security Engineer, Team Lead", "company": "FactSet", "date": "26 Jan 2016", "question": "Is ARP UDP or TCP?", "answer": ["This was from the guy who came in late...."]}, {"key": 685, "position": "Senior Staff Security Engineer", "company": "Blackhawk Network", "date": "23 Jan 2016", "question": "What is a Cross-Site Request Forgery attack.", "answer": ["Well, I answered what a CRSF attack is, and how to combat it."]}, {"key": 686, "position": "Information Security Engineer, Compliance Analyst", "company": "Facebook", "date": "13 Jan 2016", "question": "Why are you interested in the position you are interviewing for?", "answer": ["Do not try to mug up for this question. keep pointers in your mind which should be used to make sentences which make sense and which creates a story around your resume."]}, {"key": 687, "position": "Network Security Engineer", "company": "Agero", "date": "12 Jan 2016", "question": "Did you actually do all of the PCI review work?", "answer": ["Yes. I attempted to explain in detail, but was interrupted by cries of \"being confused\"."]}, {"key": 688, "position": "Security Support Engineer", "company": "Venafi", "date": "6 Jan 2016", "question": "They asked me technical questions based on my resume to determine the depth of skills in the various areas. Knowledge of PKI and SQL was a common theme throughout the different interviewers.", "answer": ["I learned that there are a lot of things I thought I knew that I could not recall."]}, {"key": 689, "position": "Security Engineer", "company": "Spotify", "date": "4 Jan 2016", "question": "How would you explain XSS to a non-technical person.", "answer": ["XSS or Cross Site Scripting, is a way for an nefarious actor to add some code to execute on a website when accessed by other users, usually unknown to the author of the website."]}, {"key": 690, "position": "Security Engineer", "company": "NTT Corporation", "date": "1 Jan 2016", "question": "The sent me an online personality questionnaire from Predictive Index.", "answer": ["I declined."]}, {"key": 691, "position": "Security Support Engineer", "company": "Amazon", "date": "27 Dec 2015", "question": "Have you ever experienced a project that failed?", "answer": ["Personal response"]}, {"key": 692, "position": "Security Support Engineer", "company": "Amazon", "date": "27 Dec 2015", "question": "Explain how you would build a web site that could secure communications between a client and a server and allow an authorized user to read the communications securely.", "answer": ["HTTPS-enabled web form that transmitted to a web app that stored data in a database. Went down the rabbit hole regarding TLS, database security, and encryption-at-rest"]}, {"key": 693, "position": "Security Support Engineer", "company": "Amazon", "date": "27 Dec 2015", "question": "Why or what got you interested into information technology and security?", "answer": ["Personal response"]}, {"key": 694, "position": "Security Support Engineer", "company": "Amazon", "date": "27 Dec 2015", "question": "What is Cross-Site Scripting and how would you use it and how would you protect for it?", "answer": ["Escaping and encoding special characters that can serve as threat vectors"]}, {"key": 695, "position": "Security Engineer", "company": "Check Point Software Technologies", "date": "18 Dec 2015", "question": "What is a connection table on a firewall?", "answer": []}, {"key": 696, "position": "Security Engineer", "company": "Check Point Software Technologies", "date": "18 Dec 2015", "question": "What experience do you have with firewalls including Check Point?", "answer": []}, {"key": 697, "position": "Systems Security Engineer", "company": "CGI", "date": "10 Dec 2015", "question": "How would you conduct a security code review?", "answer": []}, {"key": 698, "position": "Information Security Engineer", "company": "InteliSecure", "date": "9 Dec 2015", "question": "I was asked about Windows programming experience.", "answer": ["I had no previous Windows programming experience."]}, {"key": 699, "position": "Senior Security Engineer", "company": "T-Mobile", "date": "8 Dec 2015", "question": "What is the difference between tcp dump and FWmonitor", "answer": ["Tcpdump add layer 2 information but does not capture"]}, {"key": 700, "position": "Security Engineer", "company": "NORCAL Mutual Insurance", "date": "2 Dec 2015", "question": "Tell me why you'll be successful at this job. Tell me why you'll be a good fit for the NORCAL culture.", "answer": []}, {"key": 701, "position": "Cyber Security Engineer", "company": "MITRE", "date": "30 Nov 2015", "question": "Describe the process of analyzing a web application", "answer": []}, {"key": 702, "position": "Web Security Engineer", "company": "Aspect Security", "date": "29 Nov 2015", "question": "What\u2019s the difference between Java and Javascript?", "answer": []}, {"key": 703, "position": "Security Engineer", "company": "Qualcomm", "date": "25 Nov 2015", "question": "Suppose a member from Team A phones in and inquires about securing product B. How would you handle the situation?", "answer": ["Discuss the product and requirements to develop and understanding about what 'securing' means in this context."]}, {"key": 704, "position": "Security Engineer", "company": "Check Point Software Technologies", "date": "22 Nov 2015", "question": "How does a router differ from a switch?", "answer": ["i began to describe NAT, nailed the buzzword and was cut off.", "Switches create a network. Routers connect networks."]}, {"key": 705, "position": "Senior Systems Security Engineer", "company": "Technica", "date": "6 Nov 2015", "question": "Had you work with certain security tools", "answer": []}, {"key": 706, "position": "Security Engineer", "company": "WePay", "date": "5 Nov 2015", "question": "Differentiate XSS and CSRF. What are the protection mechanisms. Describe SSL handshake. How does OAuth work. The second interview focussed more on session management.", "answer": ["I was able to answer the first round well. The second round went good. But i did not manage to clear it."]}, {"key": 707, "position": "Security Engineer", "company": "Riverbed Technology", "date": "5 Nov 2015", "question": "how would you go about doing a penetration testing for a devi.ce? Another was like say a vulnerability occurs, how do you go forward in patching it. Some questions from my resume. Threat modeliing, Architectural reviews (Secure SDLC), Basic cryptography and questions related to OAuth.", "answer": ["I was able to answer almost all the questions. They help you when you get struck."]}, {"key": 708, "position": "Security Engineer", "company": "Emerson", "date": "3 Nov 2015", "question": "Why should Emerson Hire me above all other people?", "answer": ["Really? Such a worn out question. It reflected the overall culture of the company. Old and worn out."]}, {"key": 709, "position": "Senior Embedded Security Engineer", "company": "TracFone Wireless, Inc.", "date": "30 Oct 2015", "question": "all the questions were related to embedded security topics especially the radio.", "answer": []}, {"key": 710, "position": "Senior Security Engineer", "company": "CSC", "date": "25 Oct 2015", "question": "I was asked when was the last time I had worked with the current security product.", "answer": ["Just over a year ago."]}, {"key": 711, "position": "Security Developer", "company": "Hewlett Packard Enterprise | HPE", "date": "21 Oct 2015", "question": "knowledge about security", "answer": []}, {"key": 712, "position": "Security Engineer", "company": "Cenzic", "date": "7 Oct 2015", "question": "How do you drive SDLC?", "answer": []}, {"key": 713, "position": "Security Engineer II", "company": "SAP Concur", "date": "6 Oct 2015", "question": "Can you describe at a high level what a typical incident response process should look like?", "answer": []}, {"key": 714, "position": "Software Security Engineer", "company": "Datawise.io", "date": "4 Oct 2015", "question": "implemented memory cache - get object from cache, create new one using a provided callback if not present, if cache full make space by writing least used cache to disk", "answer": []}, {"key": 715, "position": "Information Security Engineer", "company": "Umbel", "date": "30 Sep 2015", "question": "Tell me about your work history related to security", "answer": []}, {"key": 716, "position": "Systems Security Engineer", "company": "Qbase", "date": "11 Sep 2015", "question": "How long have you been in cyber security?", "answer": []}, {"key": 717, "position": "Security Engineer", "company": "Community Health Systems", "date": "27 Aug 2015", "question": "What was my experience with threat intelligence tools.", "answer": ["That in practice I have (school work) and the things I have used the tools of the teams since I had began the internship."]}, {"key": 718, "position": "Senior Security Engineer", "company": "Guardian Life", "date": "26 Aug 2015", "question": "Why was I looking to leave my current position?", "answer": ["Looking for advancement in my IT career."]}, {"key": 719, "position": "Security Engineer", "company": "G2 Inc.", "date": "24 Aug 2015", "question": "How would you go about defeating that design to access workstation A? (whiteboard)", "answer": []}, {"key": 720, "position": "Security Engineer", "company": "G2 Inc.", "date": "24 Aug 2015", "question": "Draw a network design, using whatever implementation you'd like, to secure workstation A (whiteboard)", "answer": []}, {"key": 721, "position": "Cyber Security Engineer", "company": "Ethernautics", "date": "23 Aug 2015", "question": "Describe OWASP Top 10 Cyber Risks", "answer": ["I named and described the top 10 list and identified mitigations strategies for each."]}, {"key": 722, "position": "Network Security Engineer", "company": "Rackspace Technology", "date": "16 Aug 2015", "question": "Write out a Cisco ASA firewall configuration on the white board to allow three networks unfiltered access, 12 networks limited access to different resources on different networks, and 8 networks to be blocked altogether.", "answer": ["Using netgroups, a solution was provided in a 40 line configuration."]}, {"key": 723, "position": "Senior Network Security Engineer", "company": "Dell Technologies", "date": "13 Aug 2015", "question": "What was the hardest situation you were in that you had to troubleshoot an issue and how did you handle it.", "answer": ["I spoke about a situation, communication and documenting the issue for lessons learned."]}, {"key": 724, "position": "Senior Security Engineer", "company": "Syniverse", "date": "10 Aug 2015", "question": "Why do you want to work with our group?", "answer": []}, {"key": 725, "position": "Transport Security Engineer", "company": "Apple", "date": "9 Aug 2015", "question": "Explain man-in-the-middle attacks", "answer": ["With an example on how Diffie-Hellman was susceptible to the attack."]}, {"key": 726, "position": "Information Security Engineer", "company": "Booz Allen Hamilton", "date": "3 Aug 2015", "question": "Tell us about yourself and work history", "answer": []}, {"key": 727, "position": "Associate Consulting Engineer \u2013 Security Assessment - Entry Level Position", "company": "CDW", "date": "1 Aug 2015", "question": "Q.Tell me about yourself? Q.Why we hire you? Q.what r u do to update yourself for technology?", "answer": []}, {"key": 728, "position": "Senior Cyber Security Engineer", "company": "American Institutes for Research", "date": "28 Jul 2015", "question": "What sort of anomalies would you look for to identify a compromised system?", "answer": ["I used a whiteboard to draw out a basic network architecture including security technologies like IPS/IDS, Firewalls, AV, etc, and described the type of traffic and logs I could use to identify a compromised system."]}, {"key": 729, "position": "Cyber Security Engineer", "company": "NortonLifeLock", "date": "28 Jul 2015", "question": "Explain what information is added to a packet at each stop of the 7 layer OSI model.", "answer": ["Wow, I'm in high school and I know the answer"]}, {"key": 730, "position": "Senior Information Security Engineer", "company": "Netflix", "date": "24 Jul 2015", "question": "Describe a time where you had to lead a project, the project fail, and how did you overcome?", "answer": []}, {"key": 731, "position": "Information Security Engineer", "company": "Juniper Networks", "date": "23 Jul 2015", "question": "Knowledge about AWS services, and how would you use those services for any of your course project.", "answer": ["Listed all the services that were useful for a data mining project."]}, {"key": 732, "position": "Information Security Engineer", "company": "G2 Inc.", "date": "21 Jul 2015", "question": "Disassemble this puzzle ball and reassemble it in 60 seconds.", "answer": []}, {"key": 733, "position": "Senior Security Network Engineer", "company": "Proficio", "date": "21 Jul 2015", "question": "Describe IPSEC Phase 1 and Phase 2.", "answer": []}, {"key": 734, "position": "Senior Cyber Security Engineer", "company": "Travelport", "date": "21 Jul 2015", "question": "13. What\u2019s the difference between Diffie-Hellman and RSA?", "answer": ["google it"]}, {"key": 735, "position": "Network Security Engineer", "company": "Tata Consultancy Services", "date": "20 Jul 2015", "question": "If I know Checkpoint Firewall?", "answer": []}, {"key": 736, "position": "Security Engineer", "company": "SMS Data Products Group", "date": "13 Jul 2015", "question": "I was asked about security related troubleshooting and my thoughts on team dynamics.", "answer": []}, {"key": 737, "position": "Security Engineer", "company": "Netflix", "date": "7 Jul 2015", "question": "Some technical, other personality. They are big on their culture slides. Definitely know how to code. Python will especially be a ++", "answer": []}, {"key": 738, "position": "Senior Security Engineer", "company": "CBTS", "date": "2 Jul 2015", "question": "What is your experience with the Security Software", "answer": ["I went through the breadth of knowledge I have accumulated through 10 years of experience with the software."]}, {"key": 739, "position": "Senior Security Engineer", "company": "CBTS", "date": "2 Jul 2015", "question": "What is your knowledge of the Host Intrusion Prevention System Software, and what would you do to properly manage the software over an enterprise of 100k + systems", "answer": []}, {"key": 740, "position": "Security Engineer", "company": "Security On-Demand", "date": "30 Jun 2015", "question": "What was your most significant accomplishment at your last position and why?", "answer": []}, {"key": 741, "position": "IT Security Engineer", "company": "Mindbody", "date": "28 Jun 2015", "question": "They asked me character questions and networking security questions on the OSI model and different network attacks.", "answer": ["Used my knowledge to answer as well as I could"]}, {"key": 742, "position": "Security Engineer", "company": "Intel Corporation", "date": "28 Jun 2015", "question": "related to computer security. Can't get into details", "answer": ["Went through my thought process which is what they were looking for."]}, {"key": 743, "position": "Senior Security Engineer - Ethical Hacking", "company": "Cerner", "date": "22 Jun 2015", "question": "What a security program consist of?", "answer": []}, {"key": 744, "position": "Senior Security Engineer - Ethical Hacking", "company": "Cerner", "date": "22 Jun 2015", "question": "What is threat, vulnerability & risk(definition)", "answer": []}, {"key": 745, "position": "Security Engineer - Contractor", "company": "VA Health", "date": "18 Jun 2015", "question": "simple questions about network security", "answer": []}, {"key": 746, "position": "Security Engineer", "company": "Check Point Software Technologies", "date": "17 Jun 2015", "question": "What is firewall", "answer": []}, {"key": 747, "position": "IT Security Engineer", "company": "ReliaQuest", "date": "14 Jun 2015", "question": "What methods do you employ to maintain a working knowledge of the information security field as well as contribute to the field?", "answer": []}, {"key": 748, "position": "Information Security Engineer", "company": "CHI", "date": "10 Jun 2015", "question": "Do you know how Single Sign-On works?", "answer": []}, {"key": 749, "position": "Information Security Engineer", "company": "CHI", "date": "10 Jun 2015", "question": "Do you know about Active Directory?", "answer": []}, {"key": 750, "position": "Security Engineer", "company": "Rakuten", "date": "31 May 2015", "question": "Why Rakuten?", "answer": ["What was the code statement in coding round", "The key in these questions is to cover the fundamentals, and be ready for the back-and-forth with the interviewer. Might be worth doing a mock interview with one of the Rakuten or ex-Rakuten Security Engineer experts on Prepfully? They give real-world practice and guidance, which is pretty helpful. prepfully.com/practice-interviews"]}, {"key": 751, "position": "Security Engineer", "company": "Inflection", "date": "20 May 2015", "question": "What were my feelings on the Edward Snowden disclosures?", "answer": []}, {"key": 752, "position": "Information Security Engineer", "company": "CACI International", "date": "7 May 2015", "question": "What are your present and future goals?", "answer": []}, {"key": 753, "position": "Security Engineer", "company": "MX", "date": "6 May 2015", "question": "Are you familiar with the OWASP top 10?", "answer": []}, {"key": 754, "position": "Security Engineer", "company": "MX", "date": "6 May 2015", "question": "How do you audit Rails applications?", "answer": []}, {"key": 755, "position": "Information Security Engineer", "company": "MFS", "date": "28 Apr 2015", "question": "They asked very technical questions that I didn't think they would and you really had to prove to them that you knew what you were applying for.", "answer": []}, {"key": 756, "position": "Software Security Engineer", "company": "Amazon", "date": "25 Apr 2015", "question": "ask me about SQL injection and XSS attack and XSF attack; question about network security", "answer": []}, {"key": 757, "position": "Security Engineer", "company": "Verizon", "date": "18 Apr 2015", "question": "What network port is used for DNS", "answer": []}, {"key": 758, "position": "Network Security Engineer", "company": "bareMinerals", "date": "14 Apr 2015", "question": "Do you consider yourself a Senior?", "answer": ["Yes", "Yes."]}, {"key": 759, "position": "Information Security Engineer", "company": "Raytheon Technologies", "date": "26 Mar 2015", "question": "Very basic knowledge questions, ones I'd have expected to be asked to a much junior person, not one with decades of experience. Made me question the depth of knowledge of the interviewer(s).", "answer": []}, {"key": 760, "position": "Security Engineer", "company": "iSEC partners", "date": "13 Dec 2014", "question": "Think like an attacker and explain all possible things that you can do, once you're inside a Company's Private Network?", "answer": []}, {"key": 761, "position": "Security Engineer", "company": "Google", "date": "13 Dec 2014", "question": "All aspects of information security were covered in the interviews. However, most of the questions were very broad in scope and open-ended.", "answer": []}, {"key": 762, "position": "Network Security Engineer", "company": "Verizon", "date": "6 Dec 2014", "question": "Analyze this raw payload data and tell us what the attacker tried to do and when.", "answer": []}, {"key": 763, "position": "Security Engineer", "company": "Google", "date": "31 Oct 2014", "question": "Questions tend to be vague and broad in scope. They want you to demonstrate depth and breadth of knowledge, or watch you hang yourself trying.", "answer": []}, {"key": 764, "position": "Applications Security Engineer", "company": "Bank of America", "date": "16 Oct 2014", "question": "I was asked about XSS, SQL Injection, Tools I have used for pen testing.", "answer": ["Cross-site scripting (XSS) is a type of computer security vulnerability typically found in Web applications. XSS enables attackers to inject client-side script into Web pages viewed by other users. A cross-site scripting vulnerability may be used by attackers to bypass access controls such as the same origin policy. - SQL injection is a code injection technique, used to attack data-driven applications, in which malicious SQL statements are inserted into an entry field for execution (e.g. to dump the database contents to the attacker)."]}, {"key": 765, "position": "Network Security Engineer", "company": "Boston Scientific", "date": "27 Aug 2014", "question": "Most were pretty straight forward in the entire process with questions ranging from your resume and experience on the technologies you have worked with as an intern or in school.", "answer": []}, {"key": 766, "position": "Cryptographer/Security Engineer", "company": "Ripple", "date": "26 Aug 2014", "question": "The position involved understanding a lot of fundamentals regarding cryptocurrencies, cryptology, application and web security -- it's hard to pick out something specific, but overall they were very thorough. Overall, the position required a strong background in mathematics and computer science, both theoretical and applied.", "answer": []}, {"key": 767, "position": "IT Security/Firewall Engineer", "company": "Knowledge Consulting Group", "date": "25 Aug 2014", "question": "What are some ways to prevent an SQL injection?", "answer": ["The most important precautions are data sanitization and validation."]}, {"key": 768, "position": "Information Security Engineer", "company": "Booz Allen Hamilton", "date": "12 Aug 2014", "question": "What is your biggest weakness.", "answer": []}, {"key": 769, "position": "Security Engineer", "company": "HMS Holdings", "date": "20 Jul 2014", "question": "It will depend on the position interviewing for. We have several questions that I am not able to present here, but be prepared for procedural and technical questions. The questions are difficult for a reason and we don't tend to advertise them because we use them in a rotating manner.", "answer": []}, {"key": 770, "position": "Senior IT Security Engineer", "company": "Timken", "date": "6 May 2014", "question": "There were no difficult or unexpected questions", "answer": []}, {"key": 771, "position": "Security Software Engineer", "company": "NetApp", "date": "8 Apr 2014", "question": "Puzzle", "answer": []}, {"key": 772, "position": "Security Engineer", "company": "Neustar", "date": "4 Apr 2014", "question": "Surprisingly there were no really hard technical questions", "answer": []}, {"key": 773, "position": "Security Engineer", "company": "Amazon", "date": "25 Mar 2014", "question": "They wanted to know about my ideas about digital currency and how I, without any recon or knowledge of Amazon infrastructure, would hack them.", "answer": []}, {"key": 774, "position": "Senior Security Engineer", "company": "Naval Information Warfare Center Atlantic", "date": "16 Mar 2014", "question": "Interview is not very organized... Questions are generic and most decisions are made from your resume info and your overall personality.", "answer": ["n/a"]}, {"key": 775, "position": "Senior Information Security Engineer", "company": "Xoom", "date": "14 Mar 2014", "question": "I was asked about database security which was out of my scope of experience. No specific questions other than what would I do to improve DB security. Wasn't really a screening question other than to see how I think.", "answer": []}, {"key": 776, "position": "Network Security Engineer", "company": "BB&T", "date": "13 Mar 2014", "question": "Nothing unexpected really.", "answer": []}, {"key": 777, "position": "Security Engineer", "company": "CSC", "date": "3 Mar 2014", "question": "Nope. Just hung out with the lead.", "answer": []}, {"key": 778, "position": "Security Sales Engineer", "company": "Check Point Software Technologies", "date": "21 Feb 2014", "question": "Nothing was difficult even though it was a bit odd presenting materials I didn't have experience with.", "answer": []}, {"key": 779, "position": "Information Security Engineer", "company": "AUSGAR Technologies", "date": "12 Feb 2014", "question": "More like the most awkward question and that \"So why do you want to leave your current employer?\"", "answer": []}, {"key": 780, "position": "Security Engineer", "company": "Google", "date": "8 Dec 2013", "question": "Revealing questions in the interview process for Google is strictly prohibited. I will say that I had heard from folks that had interviewed with Google that interviews for all technical positions were heavily programming-based; although programming knowledge is definitely a must for working there, it was definitely not the end-all be-all questions-wise for my interviews.", "answer": []}, {"key": 781, "position": "Applications Security Engineer", "company": "Riot Games", "date": "21 Sep 2013", "question": "What games do you play besides League of Legends and why do you like them?", "answer": ["Play Dota 2 because i think it requires much more thinking and its a lot of fun"]}, {"key": 782, "position": "Security Engineer", "company": "Facebook", "date": "9 Sep 2013", "question": "Thought process is important so is width of knowledge. Signed the NDA and will respect that.", "answer": ["At least, could you please mention the domain of questions? Were it related to algorithms and data structure? Or general coding question?", "Following"]}, {"key": 783, "position": "Cyber Security Engineer", "company": "IntelliGenesis LLC", "date": "23 Aug 2013", "question": "Nothing really technical or business related in terms of any specific positions, just general thoughts on specific skill sets and areas of interest.", "answer": []}, {"key": 784, "position": "Senior Security Engineer", "company": "Trans-Tel Central", "date": "22 Aug 2013", "question": "Whether I was willing to help the company find additional work, despite not having specific Project Management experience.", "answer": ["Of course! Learning is part of the game, and the more difficult the job position, the better I'll be for it."]}, {"key": 785, "position": "Security Engineer", "company": "NIKSUN", "date": "31 Jul 2013", "question": "They will ask about your willingness to work. what this means is are you willing to work unpaid overtime, nights, weekends, and any time something goes wrong without compensation.", "answer": ["No."]}, {"key": 786, "position": "Senior Security Network Engineer", "company": "Apple", "date": "28 Jul 2013", "question": "Nothing as such, it was very straightforward", "answer": ["I answered 80% to their questions. Got a feedback that I am good in security but they are looking for someone with routing experience too."]}, {"key": 787, "position": "Information Security Engineer", "company": "Twitter", "date": "25 Jul 2013", "question": "Can't recall any questions that stood out as difficult or unexpected.", "answer": []}, {"key": 788, "position": "Senior Security Engineer", "company": "Securonix", "date": "10 Jul 2013", "question": "In the Technical round, Questions related to Security were asked. Like what kind of Java objects would you use to tackle a situation, when you wish to Find the maximum number of intrusions happened, looking at the application log.", "answer": []}, {"key": 789, "position": "Security Engineer", "company": "Rackspace Technology", "date": "28 Jun 2013", "question": "If you have a good foundation in information security, most of the questions shouldn't be anything too unexpected. Questions will range from both architectural-level (designing secure systems or breaking them) to sys-admin level (e.g., the use of 'netcat').", "answer": []}, {"key": 790, "position": "Senior Security Engineer", "company": "Sentara Healthcare", "date": "26 Jun 2013", "question": "Define a corporate policy for web application security (which was an AWESOME QUESTION)", "answer": ["Too lengthy to answer."]}, {"key": 791, "position": "Cyber Security Engineer", "company": "Boeing", "date": "21 Jun 2013", "question": "The Program Manager did not want my support, and it took months to turn that around.", "answer": []}, {"key": 792, "position": "Identity Security Engineer", "company": "Verizon", "date": "10 Jun 2013", "question": "How would you handle theoretical situation X.", "answer": ["The question had some nuances, and I tried to be as comprehensive as I could be."]}, {"key": 793, "position": "Security Engineer", "company": "Apple", "date": "22 May 2013", "question": "How do you build a tool to protect the entire Apple infra?", "answer": []}, {"key": 794, "position": "Mobile Security Engineer", "company": "Mozilla", "date": "8 May 2013", "question": "Do you think the App vetting process (appstore) for Firefox OS would scale?", "answer": []}, {"key": 795, "position": "Senior Cyber Security Engineer", "company": "Corporate Risk Solutions (Kansas)", "date": "25 Apr 2013", "question": "They are so rigid in their interview process that I beleive they overlook talent and are focused on people passing Dr. Mercer's tests", "answer": ["three of the people I interviewed with were somewhat disgruntled with the company... overworked.", "At the end of a 3 hour interview that went perfectly, I was told I'd meet the president of the company. Prez came in and said, \"I have 5 minutes.\" He showed me a bad photocopy of the company's core values... status quo. I said, Yes! I agree. He asked me, \"The client is always right. True or false?\" I said, \"Well, the short answer is 'yes, of course! But for the past decades there's a much larger understanding of customer relationships... and it involves developing a partnership and strong supply chain\" . They never called me to inform me of the interview result. I reached out the the company director who never took or returned my calls. No wonder that outfit had a non-stop search for production supervisors and process engineers. The company will be gone in a few years."]}, {"key": 796, "position": "Network Security Engineer", "company": "Federal Resources", "date": "24 Apr 2013", "question": "How long the contracts lasted. Of course this depended on the government renewing options on the contracts.", "answer": []}, {"key": 797, "position": "Electronic Security Design Engineer", "company": "M.C. Dean, Inc.", "date": "22 Apr 2013", "question": "Can you pass a credit check", "answer": []}, {"key": 798, "position": "Security Engineer", "company": "Ettain Group", "date": "22 Apr 2013", "question": "Describe what your firewall experience has been up until now.", "answer": []}, {"key": 799, "position": "Product Security Engineer", "company": "Qualcomm", "date": "2 Apr 2013", "question": "Why should we hire you", "answer": []}, {"key": 800, "position": "Software Security Engineer", "company": "Allscripts", "date": "20 Mar 2013", "question": "technical questions", "answer": []}, {"key": 801, "position": "Network/Security Engineer", "company": "Palo Alto Networks", "date": "19 Mar 2013", "question": "nothing much on networks i.e. TCP/IP or sub netting. No ques related to security also", "answer": []}, {"key": 802, "position": "Security Engineer", "company": "ServiceNow", "date": "16 Feb 2013", "question": "None were difficult. If you know Unix you will rock all tech questions easily. And the typical management questions.", "answer": []}, {"key": 803, "position": "Senior Security Engineer", "company": "Delta Dental Plans Association", "date": "15 Feb 2013", "question": "Many technical questions around everything from port numbers to sub-netting. I was surprised to see so many system administrative questions on a test for a security position. an example of one specific question was the port that LDAP runs on be default.", "answer": ["389 by default 636 over SSL"]}, {"key": 804, "position": "Security Engineer", "company": "Articon-Integralis", "date": "8 Jan 2013", "question": "Firewall, Linux, OSI, Subnetting, routing protocols, VPN, TCP.", "answer": []}, {"key": 805, "position": "Information Security Engineer", "company": "Barling Bay", "date": "5 Jan 2013", "question": "How can you fire someone with any notice or being written up.", "answer": []}, {"key": 806, "position": "Software, Security & Systems Engineer", "company": "SAIC", "date": "26 Sep 2012", "question": "lots of questions on networking, Encryption, and Unix/Microsoft Server Systems", "answer": []}, {"key": 807, "position": "Security Engineer", "company": "NTT Ltd.", "date": "23 Aug 2012", "question": "During the technical interview, the second interview asked, \"How would you configure trace route in a cisco firewall for a group of windows users?\" I repeated the question to make sure I heard it correctly, and he responded with, \"Windows fundamentally handles trace route differently than Unix does.\"", "answer": ["The answer to the question is obviously, You configure ICMP through the cisco appropriate syntax for the windows users. I was thrown off by him saying what he did about Unix and was not even given a chance to actually answer the initial question. so my question is, If you wanted to know the answer to the first question, why would you even ask the second one basically replacing the first question? How is anyone supposed to know which to answer or what the person asking the question is actually looking for?", "The problem is that your answer of \"You configure ICMP through the Cisco appropriate syntax for the windows users\" is incorrect. (Or, at best, incredibly vague.) It's definitely a fair question. While Windows uses ICMP for traceroute, it's important to note that Linux technically uses UDP. Therefore, the responses they get from the devices along the path is different, depending on which source device you used to initiate the trace. As such, the required configuration is equally different on the Cisco device. For Windows, you'd need an inbound rule allowing icmp time-exceeded. For Linux, you'd need an inbound rule allowing icmp unreachable. For both, you'd also need to add an \"inspect icmp\" statement. Looking at his question as well as his explanation after you repeated it, it's safe to say that there was nothing wrong with the way he asked it. The problem is that you didn't know the answer. In fairness though, it IS a trick question that gets asked of all of us, even myself when I applied.", "Here is my problem with the question. I know that linux/unix/solaris/AIX all utilize UDP. some of the more modern and updated unix based operating systems do utilize icmp instead of UDP. My issue is not with the fact that he asked this. Yes I did get quite flustered and it threw me off, but had he simply stated how would you configure a cisco firewall for a specific group of windows users, I would have quickly and easily stated that you would create the appropriate network object group containing the subnet(s)/IP(s) of the users and allow icmp time-exceeded. I could have easily sat down in front of a cisco ASA or PIX and had it implemented and working, I would say, easily in less than 15 mins. That would also be dependent on the subtnet(s)/IP(s) that needed to be added after creating the network object group. So yes it is a trick question, and was very confused as it seemed he wanted to know how to configure it for linux/unix, not windows even though that is what he asked. I have worked with numerous network devices from numerous vendors and so the exact syntax for each one sometimes escapes me, but I am more than technically competent enough to find the syntax and implement it with no help. I guess the most insulting part of the interview process is that based off of this interview, the recruiter stated, \"You are just average, and we need someone that is exceptional. so we can't proceed with your submission.\" That is a direct quote. I have made it further in my career with no degree, minimal college education and through my blood, sweet and tears, metaphorically, in less time than most hope to with a bachelors degree. I work with SMEs and collegues with 15+ years experience as their equal. That is not \"Just average.\" I have written SLAs, OLAs, technical manuals, disaster recovery plans, training plans, training material, and numerous other things for the DoD, TSA, Banks, and municipalities. I have been working on global networks for over 5 years as well. I have solved problems that engineers with at least twice as much experience as myself, that they were unable to solve. I have run into issues that have stumped Microsoft themselves for over two weeks. If this is the career of an \"Average\" engineer, then by all means, I am just average.", "It's unfortunate that the way you were dismissed was a little bit unprofessional and seemingly misinformed. Also, in fairness, it's probably never a good idea to tell a candidate that they're \"just average\", even in cases where they really are. For what it's worth, I'd like to apologize on behalf of DD (as much as I'm technically allowed to do so) for the way it was handled. However, regarding the original point, the interview itself is specifically designed to fluster you. We actually expect most people to get this particular question wrong. The idea is not for us to see if you know it all but more specifically how you deal with questions you don't know the answer to. (Bonus points if you DO know, obviously.) We certainly don't expect candidates to know everything offhand, we just like to see whether or not you're going to try to BS your way through an answer. Since I wasn't on this particular call, I have no idea how it went for you but I can guarantee that the decision wasn't based on this question alone but was more likely an overall view of your skills based on all of your answers. I do realize that it's no picnic when you're on the phone but for the most part, they do try to take that into consideration. (I was hired over the phone as well, all the way from South Africa.)", "I do understand what you have said, and I greatly appreciate the apology. I was very excited about this opportunity. I believe based off my experience and my knowledge of the position that I would have been a great asset to the team. I honestly do not know why the engineers I interviewed with or the recruiter would have felt the way the recruiter did. I know that the engineers I spoke with told me that the recruiter would call me with the next steps and I answered every question that they asked, except the afore mentioned question. The following link is my linkedin profile (http://www.linkedin.com/profile/view?id=10589063&amp;trk=tab_pro). This is about all I can say. I was excited and looking forward to the opportunity, but obviously I was not considered. Thank you for your time, response, and consideration. I wish you the best.", "In window you use tracert which works with icmp echo and reply message and in cisco environment you use traceroute command undp as well as icmp. But you have to configure for firewall to allow icmp replies"]}, {"key": 808, "position": "Security Engineer", "company": "Oracle", "date": "24 May 2012", "question": "Describe SSL in detail.", "answer": ["1. SSL Handshake: Symmetric Encryption a. Client Hello b. Server Hello c. Server sends its certificate and requests certificate from client. Server also sends its asymmetric public key d. If certificate was requested by client, client sends it to the server. f. Client Key Exchange Message: Client protocol version (prevents rollback attacks), Pre-master secret which is encrypted using server's asymmetric public key. Pre-master secret is 48-byte client-generated number. g. Server receives the Pre-Master Secret. Server and client compute the master secret locally and derive the session keys from it. h. Client sends \"Change cipher spec\" notification to server to indicate that the client will start using new session keys for hashing and encrypting messages. Client also sends \"Client Finished\" message. i. Server receives \"Change cipher spec\" notification from client and switches its record layer security state to symmetric encryption using the session keys. Server sends \"Server Finished\" message to the client. 2. SSL Certificate: Asymmetric Encryption More detail goes into this answer. But the above answer is a sign that you know something."]}, {"key": 809, "position": "Embedded Software Engineer Device Drivers, Embedded Software Security Engineer", "company": "Qualcomm", "date": "1 Dec 2011", "question": "how does a bootloader work? what is priority inversion and how it is solved ?compare the ways", "answer": []}, {"key": 810, "position": "Embedded Software Engineer Device Drivers, Embedded Software Security Engineer", "company": "Qualcomm", "date": "1 Dec 2011", "question": "puzzle: if there are 72 legs in total and there are 28 animals involving chickens and horses , how many are horses and how many chickens, solve without using equations? How does a vending machine work, describe blocks and what are funtions just to see if I can break down problem into small modules and analyse", "answer": ["There are 8 horses and 20 chickens. My method was immediately assume we have 14 chickens and horses. This equates to 84 legs, and we want 72 legs, so we need to subtract 12 legs from them, so if we remove 6 horses, and add 6 chickens, we will lose 12 legs, and end up with (14-6) == 8 horses + (14+6) == 20 chickens. Of course, I would rather solve with a set of linear equations: h+c == 28 and 4h+2c == 72, solve for h or c in the first equation, plug that equation in to the second, and solve."]}, {"key": 811, "position": "Embedded Software Engineer Device Drivers, Embedded Software Security Engineer", "company": "Qualcomm", "date": "1 Dec 2011", "question": "how does a packet travel between two hosts connected in same network?what is subnet mask?", "answer": []}, {"key": 812, "position": "Embedded Software Engineer Device Drivers, Embedded Software Security Engineer", "company": "Qualcomm", "date": "1 Dec 2011", "question": "how to make an OS real time ? name few RTOSs how to make memcopy fast? code was written over board and had to identify problems in it like memory leak , accessing memory location which is not allocated", "answer": ["I would say that you would make more use of high-resolution timers, and minimize the number of tasks for the embedded system. For memcpy, I would just have a loop that immediately stores the bytes in the src in the dest. Memory leaks are ez4ence to find, just make sure you are freeing memory when you are done using it."]}, {"key": 813, "position": "Embedded Software Engineer Device Drivers, Embedded Software Security Engineer", "company": "Qualcomm", "date": "1 Dec 2011", "question": "what is volatile, static ? how would it affect if the static keyword used for big array inside a function? what are sections of memory and what kind of variable is stored where?", "answer": ["if Volatile used then the compiler dont consider to optimize that variable . Assume that a variable changed at the time of running . But some compiler optimized .to avoid that we use volatile. Static is the keyword which is used to initialized to once that means extra burden for a compiler to keep the variable .and permanantly allocate space in stack.if you diclare static array then stack overflow will occur.", "Just clarify one thing, the static variables within a function are not allocated to the function or thread's stack, instead, they are allocated to BSS area, just like other global variables. so it won't affect their function too much.", "static variable is not stored on stack."]}, {"key": 814, "position": "Product Security Engineer", "company": "Qualcomm", "date": "4 Nov 2011", "question": "Encryption modes, CTR, ECB, CBC.., How HMAC works, why HMAC is designed in that way", "answer": ["In cryptography, a keyed-hash message authentication code (HMAC) is a specific type of message authentication code (MAC) involving a cryptographic hash function and a secret cryptographic key.", "Hash-based message authentication code (HMAC) provides the server and the client each with a private key that is known only to that specific server and that specific client. The client creates a unique HMAC, or hash, per request to the server by hashing the request data with the private keys and sending it as part of a request. What makes HMAC more secure than Message Authentication Code (MAC) is that the key and the message are hashed in separate steps."]}, {"key": 815, "position": "Product Security Engineer", "company": "Qualcomm", "date": "4 Nov 2011", "question": "Describe your PhD and master thesis as well as one of your paper", "answer": []}, {"key": 816, "position": "Senior Security Engineer", "company": "MS Technologies", "date": "8 Sep 2011", "question": "Why are you considering M&S", "answer": ["I answered by informing them about the potential for growth and the challenge doing something new would bring to the table."]}, {"key": 817, "position": "Senior Security Engineer", "company": "MS Technologies", "date": "8 Sep 2011", "question": "Why did you leave your previous employer?", "answer": ["I really didn't want to give too much detail for fear of badmouthing my former employer who had been very good to me."]}, {"key": 818, "position": "Security Engineer", "company": "Vigilant", "date": "23 Aug 2011", "question": "How would you handle multiple projects at the same time?", "answer": []}, {"key": 819, "position": "Product Security Engineer", "company": "Qualcomm", "date": "18 Jul 2011", "question": "You have a paper, describe about it?", "answer": []}, {"key": 820, "position": "Product Security Engineer", "company": "Qualcomm", "date": "18 Jul 2011", "question": "Explain your work in Hardware Security", "answer": []}, {"key": 821, "position": "Information Security Engineer", "company": "HireRight", "date": "9 Jul 2011", "question": "What are the ways to secure a LInux system?", "answer": []}, {"key": 822, "position": "Information Security Engineer", "company": "HireRight", "date": "9 Jul 2011", "question": "Tell me about cross site request forgery and why should I care.", "answer": []}, {"key": 823, "position": "Systems Security Engineer", "company": "Booz Allen Hamilton", "date": "27 Jun 2011", "question": "Nothing really serious was really asked.", "answer": []}, {"key": 824, "position": "Systems Security Engineer", "company": "Booz Allen Hamilton", "date": "27 Jun 2011", "question": "Pay Expected", "answer": ["90,000"]}, {"key": 825, "position": "Vuln/Security Engineer", "company": "Qualys", "date": "7 Jun 2011", "question": "XSS , CSRF , SQL Injection , puzzle (water jug) , writing simple regex , scripting TLS/SSL etc", "answer": []}, {"key": 826, "position": "Security Engineer", "company": "Century 21 Stores", "date": "3 Jan 2011", "question": "In what area do you feel you are the strongest?", "answer": ["Security Architecture"]}, {"key": 827, "position": "Security Engineer", "company": "Starbucks", "date": "7 Nov 2010", "question": "Why are you really leaving your present employer?", "answer": ["Realized that I didn't need to leave my current employer and that this job was not right for me. Great question that made me think."]}, {"key": 828, "position": "Security Engineer", "company": "Starbucks", "date": "7 Nov 2010", "question": "What do you really want to do?", "answer": []}, {"key": 829, "position": "Information Security Engineer", "company": "Booz Allen Hamilton", "date": "28 Sep 2010", "question": "Why have you only been with your existing company for only one month?", "answer": []}, {"key": 830, "position": "Security Engineer", "company": "Google", "date": "31 Aug 2010", "question": "No technical questions were asked.", "answer": []}, {"key": 831, "position": "Security Engineer", "company": "T-Mobile", "date": "30 Aug 2010", "question": "Given a sample packet capture - Identify the protocol, the traffic, and the likelihood of malicious intent.", "answer": []}, {"key": 832, "position": "Network Security Engineer", "company": "Microsoft", "date": "24 Apr 2010", "question": "Why do you want to work at Microsoft?", "answer": []}, {"key": 833, "position": "Lead Security Engineer", "company": "The Home Depot", "date": "6 Apr 2010", "question": "Describe the differences between symmetric and asymmetric encryption, and scenarios where one is more appropriate then the other.", "answer": ["Not that difficult if you understand symmetric (private key) vs. asymmetric encryption (public key)."]}, {"key": 834, "position": "Security Engineer", "company": "Rackspace Technology", "date": "26 Feb 2010", "question": "What protocol/port is AH, ESP, etc.", "answer": []}, {"key": 835, "position": "Network Security Engineer", "company": "Ascend One", "date": "5 Feb 2010", "question": "How many bits do you need for a subnet size.", "answer": ["Need to know subnetting off top of your head.", "If number of addreses required in a subnet is \"N\" , then you need 2 more (network and bcst addreses) in addition to \"N\". So \"N+2\" is rounded of to Next 2 to the power . For e.g if we need 64 addresses in a subnet then , 66 rounded to next 2 to the power is is 2**7 ie 128. so number of bits required is 7.", "The minimum addresses needed is 2 bits for 4 addresses 2^(# of addresses) = 2^2 which used for pint to point links. Max addresses can go as much as class A IP address /8 so for maximum bits is 32-8 = 24 bit"]}, {"key": 836, "position": "Security Engineer", "company": "McAfee", "date": "20 Jan 2010", "question": "Command syntax of Unix commands, and exact system file locations", "answer": []}, {"key": 837, "position": "Security Engineer", "company": "Google", "date": "31 Aug 2009", "question": "Explain traceroute in detail.", "answer": ["Involved answer, google traceroute."]}, {"key": 838, "position": "Security Engineer", "company": "Google", "date": "31 Aug 2009", "question": "Write a function that can determine if an input number is a power of 2.", "answer": ["Multiple answers. Powers of 2 only have a single 1's bit, rest will be 0's. Use that fact. X (LOGICAL AND) (X - 1) = 0 i.f.f. is a power of 2.", "Indeed, it is as the previous poster stated. Quite simple -- my initial thought would have been repeated division by 2 looking for a remainder, but that is much heavier lifting. int is_power_of_2 (int val) { if (!(val &amp; val -1)) { return 1; // val is a power of 2 } else { return 0; } }", "Sure, but every number is a power of 2, or a sum of powers of 2. For example, 16 is (2^4), and 33 is (2^5 + 2^0). If we want to just see if it is divisible, like Brian mentions, well, modulus operator works fine, but I don't think that is entirely the jist of the question. (X % 2) = 0 =&gt; divisible by 2, but not necessarily a power of 2, but in stead a sum of powers of 2.", "I like the idea of the `val &amp; (val - 1)`, but it only works for positive integer powers of two. The internal representation of floats ( 2 ^ -3, for example) does not give you a sensible answer when using bitwise and. What you might note is that `log_2(n)` will be an integer if n is a power of 2. In python you can just do this: ```import math def is_power_of_2(n:int) -&gt; bool: return math.log2(n).is_integer()``` Also, even if we're limiting values to nonnegative powers of 2, the log_2 method is fast: ```import math val = 2**4096 - 1 def is_power_of_2_log(n:int) -&gt; bool: return math.log2(val).is_integer() def is_power_of_2_and(n:int) -&gt; bool: return val &amp; (val - 1) == 0 %%timeit is_power_of_2_log(val) # 468 ns \u00b1 32.1 ns per loop (mean \u00b1 std. dev. of 7 runs, 1000000 loops each) %%timeit is_power_of_2_and(val) # 766 ns \u00b1 12.6 ns per loop (mean \u00b1 std. dev. of 7 runs, 1000000 loops each)```"]}, {"key": 839, "position": "Systems Security Engineer", "company": "BAE Systems USA", "date": "18 Aug 2009", "question": "The questions were fairly routine and simple. They presented a hypothetical scenario and asked that I describe a high-level architecture that addresses the security and why I chose that architecture.", "answer": []}, {"key": 840, "position": "Security Engineer", "company": "Google", "date": "14 Jul 2009", "question": "Describe HMAC in detail.", "answer": []}, {"key": 841, "position": "Security Engineer", "company": "Stillsecure", "date": "8 Jul 2009", "question": "On a white board a network was drawn out. Then an issue was described and I had to discover why the issue existed.", "answer": ["The problem was that the network was routing traffic incorrectly."]}]